Previously on
"The Vampire Diaries..."
For over a century
I have lived in secret-
Until now.
I know the risk,
- But I have to know her.
- Elena...
She's a dead ringer
for Katherine.
You have no idea of the
future I have planned for us.
You, me, and Damon.
Our love for Katherine
wasn't real, Damon.
Katherine never compelled
me. I knew everything.
It was real for me.
I'm going
to bring her back.
Tell me how to get
into the tomb.
- The Grimoire.
- Where is it?
Check the journal,
Jonathan Gilbert's.
Can I borrow
your ancestor's journal?
I gave it to
my history teacher.
- Alaric Saltzman.
- Damon.
So the Grimoire,
that as Emily's, right?
That's what you need
to reverse the spell?
- I'll help you.
- Ok.
I told Damon that I'd help
him get Katherine back.
But it was a lie.
I can't let him do it.
Then don't. And I'll help
you. Whatever it takes.
Please!
Please, help us!
Please, my husband,
he's been hurt!
Please help him!
What are you doing out her
in the middle of the night?
It's not safe.
No. No, sir.
And that's how
it's done.
What happens
to the bodies?
Well, I'll take them
into the woods
And the other animals
will finish them off.
Are you sure
you're ready for this?
I'm ready.
I want you
to turn me.
When it's time.
Kiss me.
You should get a taste.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
Soon you won't be able
to get enough.
Sync & edits by: Don4EveR
(subscene/addic7ed.com)
Mmm.
Mmm, good morning.
I could get used
to this.
Rise and shine,
sleepyheads.
- Damon! Please!
- What are you doing?
Oh, stop being smutty.
Seriously,
get out of here!
If I see something
I haven't seen before,
I'll throw a dollar at it.
Now listen,
We have some very important
business to discuss.
And it has to be
right now?
Well, we have lots to do,
now that we're all friends
and working toward
a common goal.
So, in order
to open the tomb,
We need to find the journal
to get the Grimoire
to open the spells.
First things first-
since you are Elena Gilbert,
you're on journal duty.
Since when
am I helping?
Well, Stefan's helping,
and you've taken up residence
in Stefan's bed, ergo...
You don't have to do
anything you don't want to do.
- I'll look for it tonight.
- Good.
How do we know
that this journal
will hold the location
of the Grimoire?
We're really going to take
the word of this vampire?
In lieu of any other options.
Ok, what exactly is
a Grimoire, anyway?
It's a witch's cookbook.
Every spell
that a witch casts
is unique unto itself,
so every witch
would document their work.
Yeah. Cookbook.
What about our
mystery vampire?
Dimwit obviously
wasn't working alone,
So whoever's out there
knows who we are.
And I don't like that
disadvantage, so...
Chop, chop.
You know, I really like this whole
ménage-threesome team thing.
It's got a bit
of a kink to it.
Don't screw it up.
He does have-
Oh, right, yeah.
Ok.
Oh! No, come here.
- We shouldn't...
- Shh.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Make me.
Yes?
Excuse me, miss Katherine.
Miss Pearl
is here to see you.
I'll be down soon.
Please ask her to wait.
Thank you, Emily.
- Fun's over.
- Hmm, no.
It's good
to see you, Pearl.
Perhaps we could
talk outside.
Emily, would you please
tell Mr. Salvatore
That I've stepped away?
Which one?
Both.
How long do you plan on
staying with the Salvatores?
People talk,
Katherine.
You, carrying on
with both brothers,
doesn't help
the situation.
The salvatores have been
kind to take me in.
As far as everyone here knows,
I'm a poor orphan girl
from Atlanta,
lost her family
in the fires.
A match you lit,
no doubt.
Honey, please
be careful.
Honorary Fell came by
the apothecary yesterday
With a case
of this elixir.
She asked that it be
sold at a reduced rate.
- I don't follow.
- Try it.
- What in hell?
- Vervain.
Why is there-
They know.
They're trying to find us, and
they're getting crafty about it.
The townspeople
ingesting vervain?
Well, that's inconvenient.
It might be time for us
to move on again.
No. I like it here.
I'm not interested
in leaving just yet.
Can we go, mama?
Is something wrong?
Hey, it's me again.
Anna.
Soccer chick
and foosball
champion.
I'll be at the grill
later, if you want,
you know, a
rematch, or whatever.
Who are you calling?
Jeremy Gilbert.
You're not, like,
into him, are you?
I need him for
something. Get over it.
Oh! Mmm!
Damn it!
Dude, you gotta stop
doing that.
I know. I just-
I keep forgetting.
You're new.
You'll get it.
You found
the Gilbert journal?
Does that look like
Well, it's old and musty,
and how am I supposed
to know the difference?
I don't know, I figured
maybe, just maybe,
you've been paying a little
bit of attention since we met.
You know, you don't
have to talk down to me.
I'm not stupid.
Here.
Drink.
I don't want you getting
itchy around the witch.
She can sense
if you're weak.
When can we
go hunting again?
This tastes old.
I want fresh blood.
When we get that tomb open,
you can kill
anyone you want.
For now,
just stay focused on Bonnie
while I try to get the journal
back from Jeremy's teacher.
Why did you choose me?
I needed someone in a position
to be my eyes and ears.
Small town bartender
fit the bill
There are plenty of
bartenders to choose from.
Why me?
You were sad then.
You lacked purpose.
You needed me.
Do you think Damon
really believes us?
That we're both
trying to help him?
I don't think Damon
knows what to believe.
Trust isn't something
that comes naturally to him.
You know...
I rely think
that Damon believes
that everything he's done,
every move that he's made,
he's done for love.
It's twisted,
but kind of sad.
There are other ways
to get what you want.
You don't have
to kill people.
Damon has no regard
for human life.
He enjoys inflicting
pain on others.
For 145 years,
Every single time that I
have let my guard down
And let Damon
back into my life,
He's done something
to make me regret that.
I'm not going to make
that mistake again.
So what do you think
will happen
if the tomb gets opened
and Damon gets Katherine back?
I think that no matter
what Damon promises,
A lot of people
will die.
That's Jonathan Gilbert.
What's this?
What are you guys doing?
Hey. Just going
through some stuff,
feeling sentimental.
Dad had this whole family
journal from years ago.
I thought
I'd dig it up.
Jonathan Gilbert's journal?
Yeah, what do you
know about it?
I just did
a history report on it.
Oh. So where is it now?
I gave it to Mr. Saltzman.
He wanted to see it.
I met Barnett and
Giuseppe this evening.
I saw the skepticism in their eyes
when I showed them the compass.
We're supposed to believe
that can track one of them?
What is it, magic?
It's science.
I'll believe it
when I see it.
I've been thinking
about this church idea.
I believe
it could work.
Excuse me, father.
I didn't know
you had guests.
We'll be done
in a few minutes, son.
I'll come back.
Forgive me, Mr. Gilbert,
Mr. Lockwood.
Have you told them?
Not yet.
Giuseppe, we need all
the men we can get.
I'll tell them.
You can count
on both my boys.
Hello?
Someone there?
You shouldn't have
done that.
Have a seat.
What is this,
compressed air?
Did you make it
yourself?
Who are you?
I'm not going
to hurt you...
unless you
try that again.
Now...
Who are you?
I'm a teacher.
Are we going to have
to do this the hard way?
I'm also a historian.
And while researching
Virginia, I-
made a few discoveries
about your town.
So you show up
like Van Helsing.
Come on.
Tell me the truth.
My wife
was a parapsychologist.
She spent her life researching
paranormal activity in this area.
It was her work
that led me here.
Where's your wife?
Dead.
A vampire killed her.
Where's
the Gilbert journal?
- What do you want with it?
- Where is it?
- It's on my desk.
- No, it's not.
It was on my desk.
Anything?
Not yet.
Just a lot of gibberish.
Yeah, some people
just shouldn't journal.
I thought this Gilbert
was the brains.
Don't you have a date?
Yep.
Wish me luck.
Ehh.
I saw her again today-
The most beautiful woman
in town,
With a name just
as pretty, Pearl.
Have you thought any more
of what I've said?
We'll leave soon,
Pearl, I promise.
I need to take care
of a few things first.
You're going to turn
both of them, aren't you?
Katherine, please.
Be careful.
We'll all be safe,
I promise.
Mr. Gilbert's
coming.
Quick, your cheeks.
Perfectly rosie.
Miss Pearl.
May I have a moment?
Yes Mr. Gilbert.
I'm still
waiting for you
to explain
that comet in the sky.
Your mother
has an admirer.
As descendants of
the founding families,
they'll want to know that
they can count on you.
Of course they can.
Is there any doubt?
I'm not sure
your bother Damon
understands
the importance of duty.
Damon left the
confederacy on principle.
It was his choice
and should be respected.
You'll forgive me if I have
trouble respecting a deserter.
Well, I never asked
for your respect.
Good for you, Damon.
Because all I have
is disappointment.
You said the town
is in trouble?
There's been too many deaths.
It is time for us
to fight back
and stop these killers.
Killers? What are you
talking about?
We live amongst demons.
You're being cryptic
now, father.
Why don't you just
say the word?
Vampires.
They exist.
And they live amongst us.
But we have
a plan to kill them.
And you're going
to help us.
My father never approved
of anyone I dated,
which only made me
want them more.
Of course.
What about you?
There were
a few guys.
Logan isn't the only
loser I've dated.
They ever find him?
Or is he still missing?
He's not missing.
He's in the Bahamas
working on his tan.
Very entitled,
that one.
Marches
to his own drum.
He's foul.
They're all snooty.
Hello, Elena.
Hey. Where have you been?
We're cooking dinner.
Is Stefan with you?
He'll be here soon.
How long have you been
aware of me?
I learned just recently.
What about your brother?
You met Damon.
Who do you think
killed my wife?
Are you certain
it was Damon?
I witnessed it.
If you're here
for revenge,
this is going to end
very badly for you.
I just want to find out
what happened to my wife.
I thought you just said
that Damon-
Yeah.
I saw him
draining the life
out of her.
He must have heard me
coming.
He just...Disappeared.
So did her body.
They never found her
Damon can never know
why you're here.
He'll kill you
without blinking.
I can take care
of myself.
No,
you can't.
I can help you.
If you let me.
Whoa. Mmm.
Don't do that.
Do what?
You know what.
That move was deliberate.
Well, yeah, I was
deliberately trying
to get to the sink.
Speaking of Stefan,
where is he?
He's missing
family night,
which I am enjoying
immensely.
Is it real?
Is what real?
This renewed sense
of brotherhood.
Can I trust him?
Yes, you can trust him.
I'm wearing vervain, Damon.
It's not going to work.
I'm not
compelling you.
I just want you
to answer me.
Honestly.
Of course you can.
You can
trust me, Mr. Salvatore.
I would never cheat.
I'm losing over here.
Again!
She's good.
I almost believe
she genuinely likes him.
Perhaps she does.
She knows father would have
her killed if he knew the truth.
Not if we talk
to him;
explained how we feel.
He could help us
keep her safe.
Have you gone mad?
No, no, father would
drive the stake in her himself!
That's not true.
We can trust him.
No, no, not with this.
Please, promise me
you won't tell him, Stefan.
I promise.
There was a time when
I trusted him more than anyone.
Trust breeds trust.
You have to give it
to get it.
Are you lecturing me?
Do you need
to be lectured?
I just want her back.
I'm sure you can
understand that.
I can understand that you
would do anything for her, yes.
Then you understand
what I will do
if anyone
gets in my way.
You said you never
played this thing before.
I'm a fast learner.
Quick reflexes.
Who are you dodging?
This girl Anna.
She can be, uh,
persistent.
Is she hot?
Yeah yeah,
but she can be weird.
Hot trumps weird,
trust me.
He is
ridiculously hot!
Shh!
He's an ass.
What are you doing
with all this stuff?
I thought there
might be something
about my birth
parents.
Have you told
Jeremy?
I will.
When the time is right.
That's Stefan.
Dude!
Well?
Admit it.
I can't sing.
No. You were great.
Come on, totally trashed
a Metallica song.
Well, first mistake,
Metallica karaoke?
Well, at least
I could admit it.
The woman with
the tattoos loved you.
Yeah, well, next time,
I'm going to throw out
my pearl jam.
Next time?
Yeah.
So, uh,
What are your friends
up to tonight?
They're all doing
their own thing.
Caroline's at her dad's,
Elena's with her boyfriend.
Elena Gilbert, right?
Yeah, I remember.
You guys used to hang out.
She's my best friend.
Yeah, my friends, they all
moved away after graduation,
and I didn't.
So we just kind of
drifted apart.
Oh. Elena and I are
bonded for life.
I can't imagine it
either way.
That tight, huh?
She's my sister.
I mean, I'd die for her.
Huh.
- Who took it?
- I don't know.
You know what,
it's that teacher.
There's something
really off about him.
No, he doesn't know
anything.
Somebody got to him
right before me.
Who else knew it was there?
No. Damon,
leave him out of it!
Why, what's
the big deal?
Damon!
So...
I heard you found
a really cool journal
from back in the day.
- Who else did you show it to?
- Huh?
Don't ask questions,
just spill.
You're kidding me, right?
Jer, did you tell anyone
other than Mr. Saltzman
about Jonathan Gilbert's
journal?
Why is everybody
so obsessed with that thing?
Who else did you tell?
- Just that girl Anna.
- The hot weird one?
- Yeah.
- Wait, who is Anna?
That's what I want
to find out.
How do you know her?
I just know her.
She wants me to meet her
at the grill tonight.
Perfect. I'll drive.
- Come on.
- Ok.
Ok, I'm alone.
Give me all the deets,
Bonnie. I'm dying.
It's going great.
He's a perfect gentleman.
- Gentleman, huh?
- I know!
Boring, huh? I just want to
grab him and lay one on him.
Why don't you?
'cause I'm a chicken.
You're a
powerful witch goddess.
Come on, seize the day,
Broom Hilda.
Ok.
I'm going to text you later
with more details.
You better.
Where's Damon?
He left to track down
Jeremy's friend Anna,
see if there was
anything there.
Aren't you going
to go with him?
If he gets to the journal
before we do, then...
Doesn't matter.
- What is that?
- It's a copy of it.
How did you get it?
Well, Mr. Saltzman
made a copy
And was kind enough
to loan it to me.
He did?
Not exactly, but I got it.
You just couldn't
live without me, huh
Well, I kinda miss my daily
dose of cute stalker chick.
Oh, funny.
Let's play.
The sheriff
was here earlier.
He bought large volumes
of the vervain elixir.
Did he try to put his hands
on you again?
- Doesn't he always?
- She's saving herself
For Jonathan Gilbert.
I'm beyond saving.
We know that.
How can you be so calm?
They're getting closer
to you every day.
We are the respectable ladies
of Mystic Falls.
Thanks to Emily, we walk
the streets in daylight.
No one will ever suspect us.
Not unless
a human tells them.
I'd sooner die.
And soon enough, you will.
Mrs. Fell is approaching.
Thank you,
Annabelle.
Here's a reference that
he wrote about Emily.
"The Fell family
believed it should be I,
"not them, who protected
the witch's spell book.
But I feared she would
haunt me from the hereafter.
They mocked my fear,
but it was Giuseppe Salvatore who..."
- Is that your father?
- Yeah.
"It was Giuseppe Salvatore
who removed my fear.
"He told me he would protect
the secret of the spell book.
He said he would carry it
to his grave."
Stefan.
To what do I owe
this pleasure?
Did I interrupt
your writing?
These are the dull musings
of my troubled mind.
A great mind.
Still. I will carry
the real secrets with me-
To your grave.
And a full grave
it will be.
Now, speaking
of troubled minds,
what's on yours?
I have concerns about
your plan for the vampires.
And why is that?
We are making the assumption
that all vampires
are as evil as they've
been characterized,
but what if that's not true?
Do you have any evidence
to the contrary?
Do you know
of any vampires?
No. No, of course not.
But are we to take
what others say
at face value?
You always taught us
so differently.
Stefan...
These creatures
Are of the darkest parts
of hell.
They have the ability
to control your mind,
seduce your spirit.
They are deadly.
They must be destroyed.
Those who stand
with them;
those who bring shame to their
families will be destroyed as well.
I know where it is.
Ok, I give.
Damn.
You're strong
for a little thing.
I was wondering how long it
would take you to find me.
Why isn't your father
buried in your family's tomb?
It wasn't built
until well after he died.
Are you sure the Grimoire's
in there with him?
As sure
as I could be.
Great.
Elena.
I can do this
on my own.
And I said I would do
whatever I can to help.
I know, and I appreciate
that, but-
This town is my home, Stefan.
My friends and family
are here. You're here.
I don't want that tomb
opened any more than you do.
I'm sorry that you have
to do this.
What is that?
Gift.
From Damon?
From Emily, actually.
And when will you stop
worrying about Damon?
I want you all
to myself.
Just as he wants me,
but I'm the one who gets
to make all the rules.
And why is that?
Because I'm spoiled.
Yes, you are.
- And selfish.
- Mmm.
And because I can do this.
Ahh.
And this.
What?
Vervain.
Katherine!
Go get the sheriff.
Tell him we have a vampire.
What? No!
Do as I say, son!
Nothing that you feel
for her is real.
She's a vampire, Stefan!
A monster!
I fed you vervain hoping
that it would expose her.
How did you know?
Your sympathy
for their plight.
I didn't raise my sons
to be so weak.
The sheriff, now.
Go, quickly!
Now, son!
How long have you been here?
I arrived around
half-past comet,
watching you screw up every
chance you had to open that tomb.
How did you know
about the spell?
I didn't say much
back then,
which means
I heard everything.
So if you've been here
the whole time,
then why are we just
crossing paths right now?
I like to use others
to do my dirty work.
Like Logan Fell?
Oh, yeah, thanks
for that, by the way.
Little bastard shot me.
- Logan was an idiot.
- Mm-hmm.
We slipped him some blood
when he started getting
all poser slayer
with that comps.
I needed his family's journal.
I couldn't let him die.
What'd you want
with the Fell journal?
I thought it contained
the location
of the witch's spell book.
I was wrong.
According to her journal,
Honorea gave the Grimoire
of Jonathan Gilbert.
And, according to this...
He gave it
to your father.
So now you're going
to help me find it.
Why would I help you?
'cause you and I both
want that tomb open.
Hmm.
Sorry.
I work alone.
Well the check's paid.
I'm all yours tonight.
What do you want to do?
This.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. Sorry.
I just should have waited until
the end of the night to do that.
I didn't mind.
You know,
I'm starting to get tired.
Do you want go?
I was going to say let's
have some more coffee,
get a caffeine buzz,
and, I don't know,
go out,
do something crazy.
Hmm, like what?
Like anything.
Ok. I'm going to
run to the restroom.
- Ok.
- All right.
What?
Not many girls
can say they've done this.
Is that it?
Well,
what do you know?
This is an interesting
turn of events.
I can't let you
bring her back.
I'm sorry.
So am I.
For thinking
for even a second
that I can
trust you.
Oh. You're not capable
of trust.
The fact that you're here
means that you read the journal
and you were planning on
doing this yourself.
Of course I was going
to do it by myself,
because the only one
I can count on is me!
You made sure of that
many years ago, Stefan.
But you...
You had me fooled.
So what are you
going to do now?
Because if you try
and destroy that,
I'll rip
her heart out.
You won't kill her.
I can do one better.
Give me the book,
Stefan.
Or I'm stabbing
her neck.
And you and I will have
a vampire girlfriend.
Let her go first.
The Book.
I'm not going
to give this to you
until she is
standing next to me.
The problem is,
I no longer trust
that you'll
give it back!
You just did the one thing
that ensures that I will.
Stop! No
don't take her!
Do you know
what they'll do to you
if you're branded
a sympathizer?
You'll be killed
along with them!
Just let me be killed!
My head supposed
to hurt like this?
Oh, you'll be fine.
That was just
a small amount of blood.
It should pass out of
your system by tomorrow.
Are you ok?
Damon was right.
This is, uh...
This is my fault.
Damon!
Damon! Stop, stop.
I'll help you.
- We'll get her back.
- Help me?!
Don't you think
you've done enough?
You promised
you wouldn't tell him!
I didn't think
this would happen.
You did this.
This is your fault.
I put my faith
in my father,
but Damon
put his faith in me,
and I destroyed that.
This is my fault.
You didn't do
anything wrong.
Don't forget that.
Ok.
I'm going to get you
that aspirin.
Ok.
You know you're not
staying the night, right?
We're just going
to hang out
- for a little while.
- You're lucky I like you.
Keep the door open.
You got it.
Hey, do you have any aspirin?
Yeah.
Oh, hey, Stefan.
Where'd she go?
- She went to the bathroom.
- Where'd who go?
- He has a friend over.
- Anna.
What's happening?
Get Emily.
Stay hidden.
I'll get us out of here.
- Pearl!
- Jonathan!
Do you see all this?
The town's gone mad
running after the demons.
You!
Jonathan...Please.
I beg you!
I've got another one
over here!
- Mother!
- Shh, shh!
Come on!
This way!
Shh!
It'll be all right.
You're going
to see her again.
I already know
how protect them.
I'm going
to protect them
Elena!
Sync & edits by: Don4EveR
(subscene/addic7ed.com)
www.tvsubtitles.net