Previouslye on "the vampire diaries"...
For over a century, I have lived in secret,
Until now. I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
Elena, she's a dead ringer for katherine.
Our love for katherine wasn't real, damon.
I'm gonna bring her back.
I'm anna. Uh, jemy.
You know, my grea
t-grandfather actually showed me
A journal. He had written all of this
Creepy stuff about vampires.
Your tur
Any sad relationship stories?
Fell in love, married young...
Wifeied.
I've never been in your room before.
Elena?
Who am I  you?
You are not katherine.
Why do I look like her?
You were adopted.
Aah! How you doin' in there?
Stefan, who was that man in the road?
I don't know. Do you remember
anything else about him?
I wish. I never really saw his face.
He was wearing a hoodie.
All I caremember is that there was
these black boots coming towards me.
I brought some vervain
For, um-- for you and jenna.
And, um, I made this bracelet for jeremy,
Few extra on for friends.
You can put it in jewelry,
Or you can even put it in food or drink,
But as long as it's in you or on you,
A vampire cann control you.
Wow. So mucho remember.
I know, but there's another vampire in tow
So until we find out who
it is and what he wants,
We have to be careful.
Hey.
It's gonna be $22.
Elena, I need the money!
Uh, here. Come in. Just put it on the table.
Hi.
Um, keep the change.
Thanks.
And you have yourself a good night.
What are you lookin' for, damon?
Not your concern.
No, but putting elena in harm's way,
That is my concern. Heh heh.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about atlanta.
Oh, yeah. Elena and I haa blast.
I get it.
You're just bitter because onof us
Gets to be with the person that we love,
And poor katherine is just out of reach.
Unless there's anoth way for
you to get into that tomb.
Is that what bree said?
You're pathetic when you're fishing.
You're transparent when you're deflecting.
Don't you have school?
Surprised? It's a good essay.
Your thoughts are clear,
and your argument is well laid out.
It's just, uh, you don't actually
Think the are vampires in mystic falls.
No. I mean, I think
statistically there's been
More animal attacks, mystious deaths, uh,
People gone missing,
more than any other place
In the whole commonwealth of virginia.
It's conjecture,
But creative, which is why you got the "a."
I just wouldn't get too, uh, caught up
In the whole conspiracy theory of it all.
Ah, I won't.
All right.
Oh, uh, jeremy,
The source that you cited
For the 1860s info, uh, jonathan gilbert...
Uh, my ancestor's journal?
I'd really like to see that sometime.
Really?
A first-person account
Of the civil war? That's like, uh,
Porn for a history teacher.
You think my essay's creative,
Wait till you get a load of this thing.
Thank you.
It's so pretty.
God, it'll go with, like, everythi.
At's the occasion?
No occasion. Just a little friend gift.
Lesbian friend necklace?
'cause we're freaky like that?
Your friendship is important to me.
Why aryou being so mushy?
Because you've been avoiding me,
And I wanted you to know that whatever
Is going on with you and matt, it's ok.
I was gonna talk to you about that.
I was,
But there's just not much to say.
We've hung out a couple times.
That's it, but...
I just feel like we've peed as friends.
This is weird.
I shouldn't be talking you about this.
It's weird. It's weird, ght?
It's a little weird, but--heh.
If it's what you and matt want,
then it's not about me.
But it's all about you.
Matt's not over you, and we all know it.
I'm with stefan w.
Matt understands that.
He kno he has to move on.
Matt donovan. What do you know?
Ben mckittrick. What's up, man?
Rough season, bud.
Yeah. It's kind of rd to recover
When you have to forfeit half your games.
You gonna be workin' here?
Yep, followin' in your footsteps,
Minus the ate championship.
Well, can't all be football gods.
Yeah.
So what's the plan? Cook line?
Busboy.
I n't believe you're adopted.
I never saw that coming.
And it gets weirder.
I looked at my birth certificate.
It lists miranda and grayson
gilbert as my birthparents.
None oit makes any sense.
Which is why you should ask jenna.
First of all, the elena I know
Would always want the
real truth, good or bad.
And second of all?
You just found out your
boyfriend is a vampire,
So unless your birthparents are aliens...
How bad could it be?
Ah, ok, look, I have to go to the store.
My outfit for the dance is
severely lacking accessories.
Ok, I'll pay the bill.
Ok. Bye.
Bye.
What do you want from me?
I think we need a fresh start.
You tried to kill me.
But I didn't, and if I wanted to,
I would have.
Does that not count for anything?
You know, I can start fires with my mind.
Fires kill vampires, right?
Just stay the hell away from me.
Everything ok over here?
Yeah, we're fine.
I wasn't talkin' to you.
Heh.
Thank you.
Ytime, bonnie.
Wait. Yoremember me?
I didn't graduate thatong ago.
You're makin' me feel old.
Sorry. I didn't--
I didn't mean that.
I just-- I didn't know you knew me.
I always know a pretty face.
Hello.
hello, elena.
Hey, who's this?
You hit me with your car.
Is that a new one?
You got away from me.
You won't next time.
Why me? What does he want with me,
A-and if he's trying to kill me,
Then why call first?
That's because we're predators, ena.
We hunt. We stalk.
It's often as exciting as the kill.
I want you to take this.
This is jeremy's pocket watch.
How did you get it?
I took it from damon,
who took it from logan,
Who must have taken it from you.
What happened to it?
Well, it's n just a watch.
It's a-- it's a sort of compass,
But it points to vampires.
Why did my father have it?
Gilberts were one of the founding families,
And back in 1864, th were among those
Who sought to eradicate the vampires.
The compass was used to find us.
Did you know them?
Yes.
I want you to keep this.
That way, you'll know if
you're ever in danger.
I've nevereen you such a mess.
don't talk smack.
I mean, I just thought that you
told everyone else what to do.
Well, I do that, too,
But if you want something done right,
You gotta do it yourself.
You know, I just like
that we're hanging out.
Who knew--you and me?
Well, who knew yocould be fun?
So what are you wearing to
this dumb dance, anyway?
Should we color-coordinate?
Uh, I'm not goin'.
Why not?
I gotta work, bussin' tables at the grill.
Since when are you a busboy?
It's a job.
You know, some of us have to work, caroline.
With our mom in and out,
things are tight, so...
I didn't mean it like that.
I just meant that I
didn't know you had a job.
Well, I do.
I gotta go.
Hey.
How'd it go?
What?
The paper.
Oh. I got an "a."
Thanks for the artles. They really helped.
Cool. So what'd he say about the vampir?
Did he believe it?
I don't even believe it.
It's just a paper, anna.
Anyways, I, uh-- I gotta get goin'.
Uh, hey, um...
D-do you wanna do something later, maybe?
Uh, sorry. I'm stuck on punch
duty at the school dance.
Oh. How'd you get stuck with that?
Well, I'm failin' english,
so I copped a plea.
Maybe, you know, tomorrow or something.
I'm being pushy again, aren't I?
Heh.
Well, thanks for the help. I'll--
I'll see you around.
Spoke to the insurance company.
Car's totaled.
You can keep using mine for now.
So you're coming to the dance?
Alaric askede to help chaperone.
Why didn't you tell me, jenna?
Your mom was gonna do it eventually.
I never thought I'd have to.
If my mom were here right now
And I asked, she'd tell me the truth.
Your dad was about to
leave the office one night
When this girl showed up.
She was 16, a runaway,
and about to give birth.
He delivered her baby,
and he gave her a place to stay,
But a few days later, she disappeared.
And there you were.
Your parents were trying
so hard to have a baby.
I-it just wasn'tappening.
All miranda ever wanted was to be a mom.
Well, why were my parents'
names on the birth certicate?
Your dad was a doctor, elena.
He took care of it.
They didn't wanna lose you,
so they kept it quiet,
Told as fepeople as possible,
But if anyone ever wanted proof,
they had documtation.
What else do you know about her?
The girl.
Just her name.
Isabelle.
You got the hair right.
Why are you bringing me dad's journa
'cause you were looking for it.
D why would I want it?
Gee, I don't know, damon.
Maybe you wanna do a little
bit of posthumous bonding.
Go ahead. Enjoy it. Read it.
I have. Nowhere in it does it
say anything about katherine
Or the tomb or how to open it.
I'm not surprised.
Man could rely spell his own name.
I'm really sorry
That it won't be of any help with
Your diabolical plan, the sequel.
You know, I could help you.
You, help me?
Aw, I don't know.
Seems a little unnatural.
I'll do anythingo get you out of this town,
Even release katherine.
What about the other 26 vampires?
No, no, no. They can't come.
They have to stay put, but katherine,
I would consider that.
What are you doin'? Hmm?
What's your angle?
Think about it.
Why would I trust you?
See that's your problem, damon.
You apply all of your
shortcomings to everybody else.
If history's any indication,
There's only one liar among us.
Hey,enna.
Jenna?
Jeremy?
Stefan's phone. How mai help you?
Where is he?
He's on his way to you,
Forgotis phone.
thank god. This compass was spinning.
Stefan must be here. Thank you.
You're welcome.
aah!
Are you ok?
Ok.
How did he get in?
He was invited in.
He posed as a pizza delivery guy last night.
Well, he gets points fothat.
Did he say what he wanted?
No. He was too busy trying to kill me.
And you have no idea who this is?
No.
Don't look at me like that.
I told you we had company.
You think there's more than one?
We don't know.
Damon, he was invited in.
Then we go get him tonight.
You up for it?
What do I have to do?
Let your boyfriend take you to the dance.
Wel see who shows up.
That's a bad idea.
Till we get him, this house isn't safe.
For anyone who lives in it.
It's worth a shot.
I'll do it.
I'll be with the o of you. I'll be safe.
Alaric.
Hey, look at you.
I figured I'd stand out
less if I dressed up.
Heh heh. Liar.
Ok, I'm a sucker for the decade dance.
I went to school here, you know.
They do the sixts and seventies, too, fyi.
Oh. Can't wait.
Can I get you a drink?
I hear the punch is real boss.
Heh.
Having fun?
No, but this took about 2 hours,
So I'm at least staying half of that.
What's damon doing here?
He wanted to come.
I promise. He'll behave.
So what is this, like, a threesome now,
You and the salvatore brothers?
No, but if I'm gonna be with stefan,
Then I have to learn to tolerate damon.
It's not like I can kill him.
There's a thought.
Mmm. I'll help.
I'm really starting to
see a change in jeremy.
Finally.
Uh, losing someone you love so suddenly,
The, uh--the trauma and the grief ther
Are some of the tougher
things 'll face in life.
From someone who knows.
You have no idea what happened?
That's the hard part, not knowing.
Is it ok to talk about your wife?
Heh. There's not much to talk about.
Th must be impossible to deal with,
not having any answers.
I'd be lying to you if I told you
it didn't keep me up at night.
Wondering why, by who,
Maybe one day.
Hope so.
Hi, bonnie.
Wanna dance?
I'm out of here.
Please give me another chance.
Back off, damon.
Where did ey go?
I don't know.
What'd you say to 'em?
I was perfectly polite.
Elena...
Would you like to dance?
I would love to.
May I have is dance?
Shouldn't u guys be able to
sense each other or something?
No. Doesn't work that way.
See him anywhere?
Not unless he has a pompadour.
Heh. Wow. Was not one of
the better fashion trends.
Come on. I'm sure you
looked great back then.
Are there pictures?
No. Burned. Buried.
Seriously, what was it like, the fifties?
'cause in my mind,
I have this picture of somewhere
Between "american bandstand," "grease."
It's all varsity sweaters and milkshakes.
Well, that and, you know, mccarthyism
And segregation and nuclear arms race.
Ok, but there were poodle skirts.
There were poodle skirts.
You're so teaching me
how to do the hand jive.
No. That's not gonna happen.
Ooh!
You neglected to mention
this was a theme party.
What are you doin' here?
Well, seeing ayou also
neglected to invite me,
I took matters into my own hands.
You're doin' that thing again.
What thing would that be?
That thing where you pretend we're dating,
Even though we're not.
Oh, you mean stalking. Yeah.
Heh. Get over yourself.
Come on. I've never been
to a school dance before.
Humor me.
Let's sit up there.
Be a little more obvious, bonnie.
Don't rain on my hot-guy parade.
What? It's just a drizzle.
Ben mckittrick? Really?
He's hot.
He's a washed-up jock who
pours drinks for a living.
You could do way better.
Y.
What's up?
Yeah, I don't recognize you.
How'd you get roped into chaperoning?
Alaric saltzman.
I'm the new history teacher.
Ah, the, uh, cursed faculty position.
So I've been told.
Damon. Salvatore.
Salvatore, as in, uh, sfan?
He's my little brother
I'm his legal guardian,
hence the chaperoning.
I hear he's very bright,
Not that I've had a
chance to see for myself.
Well, his attendance
record's a little spotty.
Family drama.
Arents?
Mm, it's just the two of us now.
You, uh--you live here your whole life?
On and off.
Travel a bit.
Really? Where?
Around the states?
Heh. I'm sorry.
I'm nosy. I--I don't mn to pry.
Look, it was nice meeting you.
You, too.
Enjoy the rest of the dance.
Tonight was so much better on paper.
Ah, you're just feeling sorry for yourself.
Go and tk to him.
Be bold and fearless.
Yeah, this coming from the girl who's
Been eye stalking the bartender.
You're right.
Hi.
Twice in one day.
Lucky me.
I'm proving something to my friend.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
That you don't have to sit around and
wait for a guy to come up to you.
Does that mean that you're
asking me out on a date?
Does that mean you want me to?
Well, what did you have in mind?
Do you like karaoke?
No.
But I would really like
to go on a date with you.
Seriously?
Is that for me?
Do you see anyone else in the vicinity?
Do you need something?
Are you mad at me or something?
No, care. I'm not mad. I--
Well, then why are you being so weird?
I'm not. I'm working.
You're avoiding.
No. I have a table to clean.
You know, that's the kind of thing
That washed-up jocks do to make a living.
You don't go to school here.
You know, you don't have to help.
Oh, I don't mi.
It's fun.
Oh, um, yeah. Before I forget,
Can I borrow your anctor's journal?
Why?
You said I could read it.
Uh, I don't have it.
Oh. Ll, obviously you didn't bring it here,
Uh, but I can walk you home.
No. I mean, I gave it to my history teacher.
Wait. Why did you give it to him?
Because he wanted to read it.
You know, you shouldn't be
giving that to just anybody.
But I should give it to you?
Loan. Loan it to me.
Well, I loaned it to mr. Saltzman.
Maybe he's in his classroom.
We can get it back.
What's the big deal with the stupid journal?
Your eye.
Um, there's something in it.
Forget it. I gotta go.
Maybe he's not gonna show.
You mean we did all this
dancing for nothing?
Ahh. The horror.
I'm really sorry for all this.
It's my choice.
I decided to be here.
I officially signed up for it,
So I don't wanna hear
you apologizing anymore.
Show me how it's done in the fifties.
Uh, no.
Come on. One move?
Now you remember that,
Because it's never gonna happen again.
What a you doin' here?
Trying to get the journal,
as in sticking to the plan,
Something you're not doing.
leave thgirl alone.
I like her.
She looks like katherine.
She's not katherine.
Ok, katherine is in the tomb.
I know, but until we open that tomb,
I got her to play with.
Dot be stupid.
That girl is with the salvatore brothers.
Th don't scare me. They never have.
Please, no. Don't do this.
You're gonna ruin everything.
You got noth' to worry about.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
You will get what you came for.
Just let me have my fun.
She looks like katherine.
You really can't take him anywhere, can you?
Uh, no.
Stefan,
The back corner.
Get damon.
What did I do?
Where ise?
I was getting a soda,
Anthen this guy gave me his hoodie.
hello, elena.
Here's what you're going to do.
There's an exit door behind you.
You have 5 seconds.
No. Or your brother dies.
I can snap his neck so fast I
bet there's not even a witness.
Start walking.
Don't you dare touch him.
Keep walking.
Through the door.
Ahh!
Yaah!
Hey, dickhead.
Nobody wants to kill you. Just wanna talk.
Now you feel like talkin'?
Screw you.
Wrong answer.
Why are you doing this?
Cause it's fun.
What do you want with elena?
She looks like katherine.
You knew katherine?
Oh. You thought you were the only ones.
You don't even remember me.
Tell me how to get in the tomb. Hmm?
No.
Uhh!
The grimoire. Where is it?
Check the journal. The journal.
Jonathan gilbert's.
Who else is working with you?
Who else is the?
No.
You're gonna have to kill me.
What do we--how are you
gonna find the others now?
He had to die.
But...
Elena, he's been inted in.
Go. I got this.
y.
What were you doing?
Looking for ms. Hilden.
Why are you in mystic falls?
I got a job as a teacher.
Do you know what I am?
You're my student's brother.
Is everything you're telling me the truth?
Yes.
Then forget we had this conversation.
There's no way that idiot was workin' alone.
You are.
So the grimoire...
That was emily's, right?
That's what you need to reverse the spell.
When the founding families burned her,
they took her things,
And you were hoping that dad's
journal would tell you where it is.
Look at u puttin' the pieces together.
Good for you.
I was half-right.
Well, it's out there now.
Let the games begin.
My offer still stands.
Yeah, with some hidden caveats, no dou.
No. Nothing hidden about it.
No lies. No deception.
I'm there when you open up that tomb,
You and katherine go,
And the other 26 vampires die.
If I agree I'll help you.
Why should I trust you?
Because I'm your brother.
No, that's not gonna cut it.
Because I want you gone.
Ok.
Looki said something stupid.
I'm sorry, but I wasn't
even taing about you.
Yes, you were, caroline.
Ben could easily be .
We're just alike.
That's not true.
Are you seriouy mad about this?
Matt, you know me.
Ok, I say stupid things without thinking,
And then I have to apologize
and take it back, and...
I'm a terrible, awful person,
but I'm rking on it.
Look, can we just not do this right now?
Ok.
When do you get off?
Look, this thing we've got,
It's nice, and it feels really good,
And I know you wna take the next step.
How do you know that?
Have you even asked me?
I'm--I'm not over elena.
I mean, I don't know if I am,
but if we go there,
Then it could mess things up,
and we might lose this,
And this is the only good thi
I've got going for me right now.
So if it doesn't work,
I'll just disappoint you
And hurt you, and I don't wanna do that.
Well, big problem, matt,
Because you took the next
step all by yourself,
And you played the whole
thing out in your head,
And you decided to bail
before even giving it a shot.
So this really great thing that we have,
Don't worry about losing it,
'cause it's already gone.
Thank you.
I needed that.
Well, thank you for--for coming.
I--I really appreciate it.
You made the evening much more...
Well, you made it, period.
I'm glad I could help.
And thank you for puttinup
with all that wife talk.
I--I gotta stop doin' that.
It doesn't bode well for dating.
Is that what this was, a date?
No, definitely not a date.
Oh.
But Friday...
You, me, and dinner and a movie,
That could be a date.
How 'bout it?
Works for me.
Heh.
Uh, you can talk about
your wife all you want.
It's gonna take time to heal.
We should just be ourselves.
Still, I think I'll keep the
isabelle talk to a minimum.
Isabelle?
Yeah. That was her name.
Where was isabelle from?
Virginia. I mean, not too-
-not too far from here, actually.
Caroline!
Care, get in the truck.
What?
This'll never work.
Doin' ok?
Is it weird if I say yes?
Is it true?
I should feel more upset
Or scared or something, but I...
Feel kind of exhilarated.
It's the adrenaline.
You'll crash soon enough.
Yeah, I gus.
I fought back tonight.
It felt good.
I wish you didn't have to fight at all.
Still...
I need to tell you something,
And I don't know how
you're gonna feel about it.
What?
I told damon that I'd help
him get into that tomb
To get katherine back.
But it was a lie.
I let him believe that he could trust me.
Well, then why would you be
worried about telling me?
Because he can be very persuasive,
And you two have bonded lately.
hat doesn't mean I trust him.
It's gonna take a lot more than
just a road trip and a rescue
For me to forget who damon
is and everytng he's done.
I don't wanna be his enemy, elena,
But I can't let him do it.
Then don't,
And I'll help you, whatever it takes.
Ok?
Ok.
Come here.
Don't sneak up on me.
You love it.
Where's noah?
His obsession got the best of him,
And so did the salvatore brothers.
They killed him?
Tortured and staked.
You're not very upset.
I warned him, ben,
And he was just gonna
screw everythingp anyway.
Let's be honest. He wasn't exactlan asset.
How'd you do?
Oh, the witch is totally crushing on me.
Did you get the journal?
No, but I know where it is, and I'll get it.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net