Previously
on "the vampire diaries"...
Stefan: for over
a century, I have lived
in secret until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to know her.
What are you?
I'm a vampire.
You said you don't
kill to survive.
Animal blood
keeps me alive,
But not as strong
as damon.
Hello, brother.
damon.
Stefan finally fessed up.
Stay away from me.
That necklace contains
an herb called vervain.
It protects you
from being compelled.
I will keep
your secret,
But I can't be
with you, stefan.
What is that?
It's a very important crystal.
Are you psychic
or clairvoyant?
Technically,
grams says I'm a witch.
There was a time when
this town was very much
aware of vampires.
5 bodies
all drained of blood.
They've come back.
Aah!
You just don't
wanna die, do you?
Stefan:
she's transitioning.
Into what?
a vampire.
I don't know
what's wrong with her.
She'll be fine.
vicki: no.
We'll all be fine.
Vicki!
I will make sure that
she does not hurt anybody,
Elena, I promise you.
[clunk]
Hi, ty.
Whoa!
Vicki?
Everyone's
looking for you.
I know.
What's wrong, vic?
I'm so cold.
Are you on drugs?
Everyone thinks
you're off on a bender.
I wish.
What happened
in those woods, vicki?
Those kids
that were killed,
What did you see?
I'm so scared.
Come here.
It's ok.
I'll take you home.
I can't control it.
Control what?
I am so hungry, ty.
And it won't go away.
What are you on?
what drugs did you take?
I want it.
I'm so hungry, ty.
Ok, look, I'll get you
something to eat.
just sit back.
Look, let's just
get you home. vicki!
Ok, what is
wrong with you?
Aah! let go of me!
What's going on
here, stefan?
what's wrong with her?
You don't talk.
Screw you, dude.
"dude"? really?
"dude"?
Damon, don't.
Oh, come on.
who's gonna miss
this idiot?
Ohh! don't you hurt him.
Forget what you
saw here tonight.
None of us
were here.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Sorry.
Oh, no, it's cool, I'm done.
You're up early.
Where are you going?
Police station.
they're organizing
The search party
for vicki, so...
Wait. shouldn't you
be going to school?
What? you're kidding me, right?
You shouldn't
skip school.
If they find her,
we'll know.
That's what
cellphones are for.
Yeah, your lips keep movin'.
I don't know why.
[cellphone rings]
Yeah?
Matty?
Vicki, where are you?
are you ok?
Yeah. I'm ok.
Tell me where you are,
and I'll come get you.
No. matty, I just need some time
to figure things out.
Just know that I'm ok,
ok?
Please don't
worry about me.
[beep]
I don't understand why I have
to stay cooped up here.
Why can't
I just go home?
Because you're changing,
vicki,
And it's not something
you wanna do alone.
There's nothin' about
that logan guy I killed in here,
Not a word.
Someone's
covering it up.
What is that?
This is a very special,
very old compass.
What was logan fell doing with it?
aren't you curious?
Well, if you're so worried
that somebody's onto you,
Why don't you
just leave town, damon?
We should all
be worried.
Hey, um, I'm hungry.
do you have anything to eat?
Here.
What is it?
It's what you're craving.
Heh. don't lie
to the girl.
It's so not
what you're craving,
But it'll do
in a pinch, right, stef?
What is it?
Yeah, what is it?
is it skunk?
Saint bernard? bambi?
Go on.
give it a try.
She's new.
she needs people blood.
she can't sustain
on that stuff.
Yeah, why can't I
have people blood?
yeah.
Because it's wrong
to pray on innocent
people, vicki.
You don't have to kill
to feed.
Just find someone
really tasty
And then erase
their memory afterwards.
it's so easy.
No, no, no.
there's no guarantee
That you can
control yourself, ok?
It takes years
to learn that.
You could easily
kill somebody,
And then you have to
carry that with you for
the rest of your life,
Which, if I haven't made clear,
is eternity.
Don't listen to him.
He walks on a moral plane
way out of our eye line.
I say snatch, eat, erase.
Hey, look at me.
We choose
our own path.
Our values and our actions,
they define who we are.
Ok, count deepak.
I am outta here.
Can I have
some more?
[bell rings]
Is stefan here?
Yep.
Where is he?
And good morning
to you, little miss
"I'm on a mission."
How can you be
so arrogant and glib
After everything
that you've done?
And how can you be
so brave and stupid
To call a vampire
arrogant and glib?
If you wanted me dead,
I'd be dead.
Yes, you would.
But I'm not.
yet.
Where is stefan?
He's upstairs
Singing
"the rain in spain."
Knock yourself out.
Stefan.
[creak]
Stefan?
Yes.
Where is vicki?
She's upstairs.
What happens now?
Because my brother is
out there searching for her
with the rest of the town.
What do I tell him?
I'm working
with her, but it's
gonna take time.
She's a very volatile
and impulsive
personality.
She's a drug user.
I mean, all that's
Gonna play a part
in how she responds
to this.
So she's a vampire
with issues?
what am I supposed to do?
Because I am lying
to everyone that I care about.
what's gonna happen to her?
I'm gonna keep her
here with me until
I know that she's safe.
Vicki: how long is that?
We can talk
about that later.
Hey, vicki, how are you?
How am I?
You're kidding, right?
Was our family burned
in the witch trials?
No, the girls that
were persecuted in salem
were entirely innocent.
You have to have
more than ignorance
to trap a real witch.
How did we end up
in mystic falls?
Our family
fled salem in 1692
and relocated here.
our ancestors lived
in secrecy for over
a hundred years.
It's important
that we still do.
Well, grams, everybody
knows you're a witch.
They also know
it's absurd,
Can't be true.
I'm just
a kooky lady
That teaches occult
at the university.
No one
really believes.
They just poke fun.
And let 'em.
Just don't let 'em
know the truth.
[sighs]
Where's the witchcraft?
I mean, you've been
talking history for 2 days.
I wanna get
to the fun part.
It's not meant
to be fun.
it's real,
and it's serious,
And you must
understand it before
you practice it.
Aren't you
late for school?
We never should have
trusted that logan...
Weasel with the watch.
How many are
we dealing with?
Well, the coroner
thinks one.
Somethinabout
the wound radius
and the jaw pattern.
Are we in danger?
I mean, if it
found the watch,
Then it knows we know,
and could it come after us?
A-and should I even
be saying, "it"?
Or--or is it
a he or a she?
If it has any historical
knowledge of the town,
Then it'll know where
the watch came from,
So, yes, we could
very much be in danger.
So what do we do?
Just keep it quiet.
we can't have
The entire town
aware of this.
We need to find him
before he finds us.
[music playing]
Hey, man.
Hey.
I heard they're putting together
a search party for vicki.
She just called.
she's ok.
Oh, good.
That's great. I figured
you must have been goin'
out of your mind.
Little bit, yeah.
I was just gonna offer,
You know, if there's
anything I could do.
I appreciate it.
I have got your costume.
It's all here.
Seriously?
Come on.
Can someone please be excited
that it's halloween?
I just wanna have fun,
you know,
Just some silly,
fluffy, damon-free fun.
Hey, isn't this the one
you got from damon?
Yep. wear it.
toss it. I don't care.
I just want it gone.
Hey, have you seen elena?
Do we know
what she's wearing?
I was with grams
all weekend.
I haven't
talked to her.
Maybe she's
with stefan.
Riding to his castle
on his white horse.
Don't be bitter.
it provokes wrinkles.
[scoffs]
Coffee is our friend.
it's the caffeine.
It circulates
through our veins,
And it warms our body
so we're not so cold
to the touch.
Well, what if I wanna
drink human blood?
You're gonna have
to learn to live
with that urge
And fight it
on a daily basis
one day at a time.
Oh, god, don't start
with that whole 12 steps thing.
School counselor
has been down that road,
And it doesn't
work for me.
It can work.
it's your choice, vicki.
So you've never
tasted human blood?
Not in a long time.
How long?
Years and years.
I'm not proud
of my past behavior.
[sighs] does this
sketchy feeling ever go away?
It's like I have
a massive hangover.
This daylight thing
is a bitch.
[sighs] I need more blood.
Where's your bathroom?
I have to pee.
Why do I have to pee?
I thought I was dead.
I'm going to, uh--
I'm gonna get her
some more.
All right.
I'll be quick.
[sighs] false alarm.
My body's feeling
really funky.
It's a good funk,
but it's weird.
Hmm.
Who are you calling?
Jeremy.
Vicki, you can't
see jeremy anymore.
Oh, come on.
don't you start.
I'm gonna see
whoever I wanna see.
Even though
you could hurt him?
I would never
hurt jeremy.
I know you think that,
But I can't
take that risk.
You're gonna have
to let jeremy go now.
Ohohreally?
And how long
have you been preparing
A "you're not
good enough" speech?
I'm presuming it predates
the whole vampire thing.
All I'm saying is jeremy
is not getting involved
in any of this.
I mean it, vicki.
Or what?
Let's get one thing straight,
you perky little bitch.
You had my brother whipped
for 15 years,
15 years,
and then you dumped him.
When I look at you,
that is all I see,
just so you know.
And I'm gonna see jeremy
whenever I wanna see jeremy,
Because I have
some fun new toys to play with,
And I won't think twice about
ripping your little head off.
You got it?
[coughs]
She threatened me.
She's on edge.
Imagine every sense
in your body operating
at super speed.
I mean, she's uncomfortable
in her own skin,
And then when you
throw in her other issues--
How long
before it settles?
Hours? days? weeks?
There's no rule book.
Well, how long
before you learned
to control it?
A while,
But I didn't have
anybody helping me.
I had to do it
on my own.
The thing is it's hard
to resist certain people,
Especially when you're new.
it's difficult
to separate your feelings.
Love, lust, anger, desire--
it can all blur into
one urge, hunger.
What does that mean?
It means that jeremy
can't see her,
Not now. she might not
be able to resist him,
And she could hurt him.
Or worse.
I'm not gonna
let anybody get hurt.
I need to get going.
Elena--
Please, stefan.
There's only
so much I can take.
[music playing]
What are you doing?
Just contemplating
the next hundred years.
Why did you do it?
I was...
Bored.
You did this to me
out of boredom?
It's one of
the pitfalls
of eternity.
Now I'm bored.
And all I can
think about is blood.
I just want some blood.
I can't think
about anything else.
What is that about?
That'll ease up.
You've just been
cooped up all day.
Let's go.
Where?
Your life was pathetic.
Your afterlife
doesn't have to be.
What are you doing?
She's been cooped up
in your room all day.
She's not anne frank.
No, no, no.
hey, hey...
Now's not the time
for this.
If you're gonna
teach her, teach her.
Show her
what it's all about.
She could hurt someone.
I'm not takin' her
to disneyland.
We're goin'
in the front yard.
Come on.
Bad idea, damon.
She's a vampire,
stefan.
she should know
the perks.
Like what?
Like...
Whoa.
how did you do that?
[whistles]
Ho ho ho ho.
Come on, vicki.
live a little.
No pun intended.
[rustle]
Uh...
Tcch.
My bad.
Matt.
Vicki?
Is that you?
Hey.
Get in here.
In a minute. I--
Please come inside.
I've been worried.
Thank god you're ok.
Where were you, vic?
It's no big deal.
drop it already.
3 people
were murdered
in the woods.
The cops were
lookin' for you.
They wanna
question you.
They know where I live.
Everyone was
worried about you.
I'm back now.
just let it go.
Are you kidding?
I had a freakin'
search party out
lookin' for you
While you were off
on your crazy drug trip,
And you want me
to let it go?
My head hurts.
You think?
[doorbell rings]
Stefan, what are
you doing here?
Is vicki home?
Yeah.
can I see her, please?
Don't let him in.
I don't want him in here.
Did he do
something to you?
No. I just don't
want him in here.
Just let me come in
so I can explain myself.
Look, I don't know
what's going on,
But I think
you should leave now.
Matt--
please, now, stefan.
You gotta call me, vic.
I don't get it.
what's going on with you?
Just--just call me, please.
Hey.
So, um, do you wanna
hang out tonight?
We could go to the, uh,
halloween thing at school.
Could be fun.
Cool. sure.
sounds, uh--sounds fun.
Can't wait.
I know you're upset
about vicki.
I heard she called matt.
but you can't be with her.
She needs to get better.
The best thing you can do
for her is let her go.
What does that even
mean, "let her go"?
Oh, ok, sure.
Since we're such
experts on letting
people go, right?
I know you may not see it,
but trust me, jer.
it's for the best.
Look, for months
after mom and dad died,
I felt like crap,
Like "nothing really
even mattered" crap.
Now all of a sudden,
I get these moments,
And things
started to feel just
a little bit better,
And vicki was in every
single one of 'em.
So you may not see it,
but trust me.
Keeping me away
from her is not
for the best.
[cellphone vibrates]
Cider for the ladies?
It's a lockwood special.
No way. last year, I was
hung over until thanksgiving.
Lightweight.
I am going to drink
Until someone
is hot enough
to make out with.
Sounds like a plan.
How many martinis
have you had?
Ohh. don't start with me.
Can we go now?
We're late
for the halloween party.
let's go.
So go ahead.
I'd like to finish
my drink.
Let me guess.
Daisy buchanan.
Heh.
I love a good
"gatsby" look.
I've met you before.
Aren't you
caroline forbes'
boyfriend?
Ah, she had
a schoolgirl crush on me, but--
It was cute, but I had
to let her down easy.
It's damon, right?
Ah, you remember.
Well, you have a face
that's hard to forget.
What's your last name,
damon?
Salvatore.
Salvatore?
mm-hmm.
Are you any relation
to zach?
Zach's my uncle.
How do you know zach?
Are you ok?
Yeah. I think there's
something in my eye.
Well, I know zach from
the founder's council.
You know, the salvatores
were one of this town's
original settlers.
Yes, they were.
I wasn't aware
that zach was a member.
I just recently
moved back home
And haven't really
had a chance to meet
many of his friends.
Well, will you tell him
to return my calls?
I've left
several messages.
Zach went out of tow
for a bit.
But if it's
about the vervain...
You know about
the vervain?
Well, I'm a salvatore.
Of course I do.
Of course.
Hmm.
Cheers.
[music playing]
Aah!
aah!
You went with last year's
costume, too, huh?
Yeah. I didn't know
that I was coming
till an hour ago.
Me neither.
[laughs]
And you're going as...
you?
He's not talking
to me right now.
we got into a fight.
Yeah, I got into it
with vic, too,
when she got home.
I'm trying not
to smother her tonight,
But part of meididt
wanna let her out of my sight.
She's here?
Yeah. you can't miss her.
she's a vampire.
Where did jeremy go?
Elena, what's the matter?
I-I've gotta find him.
[music playing]
[gasps]
What, you're
following me now?
You didn't really give me
much of a choice.
You let me out of here.
You shouldn't be here,
vicki.
Crowds like this,
it makes it even harder
For you to keep yourself
under control.
I'm fine.
Really?
mm-hmm.
No headache?
Your stomach's
not screamin' at you?
you're not
feeling lightheaded
Or anxious or cranky,
Like if someone looks
at you the wrong way,
You could just rip
their head off?
Do youanna know
what that's called?
It's called hunger,
And it's only gonna
get worse and worse
Every minute that
you pretend like it's
not controlling you.
So you need vervain?
Yes. my husband and I
only have left
What his parents left him,
And zach had promised that he
could supply us with more.
Well, I talk to him
all the time,
So why don't
I just ask him?
Hmm.
mmm.
How much do you need?
I mean, how many people,
u ththk?
Well, there's our children,
of course.
Of course.
And, um, friends, family,
And everyone
on the council.
The council?
Zach knows how many.
Hmm.
But I am so late.
My husband is not going
to be happy with me.
well, are you happy
with your husband?
You're flirting with me.
you flirted
with me first.
True. [laughs]
Let me escort you
to the school.
It's not safe
out there alone.
I mean, I've seen
10 vampires tonight.
Heh. well, if only
the real ones were
as easy to find.
How's that search goin'?
Oh, we had the founder's party,
And anyone who arrived
during the day
Was eliminated
as a suspect.
Oh.
And all the rest were
just dead ends, so mmm.
Mmm.
mmm, I gotta go.
Ok.
Thank god.
What's the matter?
I lost track
of jeremy.
I was worried.
What's goin' on?
Hey. uh, everything's fine.
I told you
to quit bothering me.
No. vicki,
don't do this.
Matt, he won't
leave me alone.
You need
to back off, man.
Matt, it's--
it's ok.
No, it's not ok.
What the hell is
your problem?
Stefan.
I'm trying
to help her.
[recorded scream]
[creature roars]
Whoa!
Vic, you scared
the hell out of me.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Come on. come on.
Ok.
So where--where'd
caroline run off to?
Do yourself a favor, damon,
and don't ask me about caroline.
Oh, bonnie.
So loyal.
Just stay away from her.
Where'd you get that?
From a friend.
Caroline.
You know that's mine,
don't you?
Not anymore.
Funny.
I'd like it back,
please.
I'm not giving it to you.
I'll give it to caroline,
and she can give it to you
If she feels like it.
Or I could just
take it right now.
[sizzles]
[gasps]
[music playing]
[growls]
[recorded scream]
Jeremy.
I was so worried
about you.
I'm fine now, but...
I gotta leave.
Wh-what?
Where?
I gotta get
out of here, j.
I just--I can't live
at home with matt.
He just doesn't get it.
No, you can't.
you can't just leave.
Come with me.
If you come
with me, we can be
together forever.
Ok.
Yeah.
Ow.
You're taking that costume
a little too far.
What? what is it?
Vicki! vicki,
what the hell?!
Oh, my god.
No! stop! vicki!
no! aah!
Vicki, no!
Jeremy: vicki!
Go. get inside.
Go!
Aah!
[screaming]
Vicki!
[gasps]
Vicki.
Vicki!
Get him out of here.
[beep]
What?
Need your help.
[lock turning]
[panting]
What happened to you?
I did something.
I don't know.
It came from my necklace.
Where'd you get that?
It's part of my costume.
it's a piece of junk.
That piece of junk
belonged to one
Of the most powerful
witches of our family.
Let me show you.
There she is.
Emily bennett,
Your great-great-
great-great-grandmother.
And there's your necklace.
[elena crying]
You should go.
I got this.
You did this.
This is your fault.
You confuse me
for someone with remorse.
None of this
matters to me,
None of it.
People die around you.
How could it not matter?
It matters,
and you know it.
Mmm.
You need to leave.
Your wounds are bleeding,
and you need to leave.
[sighs]
Elena!
hey, have you seen--
Whoa. wh-what happened?
Nothing. some idiot
with some fake blood got me.
I'm gonna go home
and shower.
I--I can't find vicki.
She totally
bailed on me.
I don't know where she is.
Is this
what I'm in for,
A lifetime of
worrying about her?
You're a good brother, matt.
Maybe she went home.
Maybe.
Where is he?
Inside.
Do you understand
what happened tonight?
No.
I don't understand.
I mean, I know
what I saw, but...
I don't understand.
She was going
to kilme..
Now she's dead.
vicki's dead.
I'm so sorry, jer.
Make it stop.
it hurts.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
it's ok. it's ok.
Why does everybody
have to die on me?
Oh, my god. come here.
[music playing]
Are you ok?
I, uh--I wanted to help her.
But instead, uh...
How's he doin'?
He's a mess.
I don't want him going
through this again.
He's just a kid.
Elena, what can I do? I--
What can I do to help?
I'll do anything.
Can you make him forget?
Elena...
Stefan, please.
I don't know how he'll
ever get past this.
I just want him
to forget everything
that happened.
If I did it, there's no
guarantee that it would work--
Because of who I am,
because of how I live.
I don't have the ability
to do it right.
Damon: I can do it.
If this is
what you want...
I'll do it.
It's what I want.
What do you
want him to know?
I want you to tell him
that vicki left town
And she's not coming back,
That he shouldn't
look for her or
worry about her.
He's gonna miss her, but he
knows it's for the best.
Part of me wishes that
I could forget, too...
Forget meeting you,
Finding out what
you are and everything
that's happened since.
If that's what you want.
Yes, it is.
Because I don't
want it to be like this.
I don't wanna
feel like this.
But I can't.
With everything
that's happened...
I can't lose the way
I feel about you.
It's done.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net