Stefan:
for over a century, i have lived
in secret until now.
I know the risk,
but i have to know her.
Damon: elena, she's
a dead ringer for katherine.
Hello, brother.
damon.
There's nothin'
about that logan guy
i killed in here.
Someone's coverin' it up.
It's a small circle,
founding families,
few city officials.
I of course will do
anything i can to help.
Alaric saltzman.
i'm your new
history teacher.
That's a cool ring.
Thanks.
it was my father's.
I have to leave.
too many people
have died.
I can't be a part
of your life anymore.
Don't go, stefan.
Good-bye, elena.
You know what?
i'm not gonna invite you in.
Some other time, then.
I was dumped.
yeah, well, logan's a jerk.
[doorbell rings]
Hello, jenna.
logan.
Aren't you gonna
invite me in?
Why are you here, logan?
I missed you.
I was out of town. i--
Yeah. i got that e-mail.
You got an e-mail?
You didn't send
an e-mail?
I can explain.
Just invite me in,
and i'll tell you
everything.
I'm not gonna invite you in.
forget it.
Come on, jenna.
it's me.
The answer's no.
I know you.
You're always
one step from a maybe,
A tiny nudge to yes.
Heh. you just pointed out
that i have no self-control.
Clever strategy.
Evening.
[running footsteps]
Hey.
You're that guy
from the news, logan fell.
I watch you every night.
Well, i used to.
i mean, you've been
missing from my tv.
I took some time off.
I noticed.
I'm daphne.
Hey, you know
somethin', daphne?
No. what?
Aah!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
"i live in fear.
"it consumes me.
"in the early evening
when i see the sun begin
to fade, the fear comes,
Because i know that
the night brings death."
[music playing]
Jeremy's got
his sketch pad out.
You're kidding.
Nope, but don't
say a word.
The minute
we encourage him,
he'll put it away.
Psychology major.
check that.
You and stefan?
Update?
He knows how i feel
and where i stand,
And i know where
he stands, but it
doesn't matter.
He's leaving,
moving away.
where's he going?
I've stopped
asking questions.
The answers get scary.
Yours leaves.
mine returns.
Logan?
He's back.
ucch.
I didn't let him
past the front door.
Hope you slammed it
in his face.
Ah, medium slam.
3-strike rule, jenna.
You're not even allowed
to watch the news.
Exactly. no more
logan "scum" fell.
So any idea
of where you'll go?
I don't know.
London, maybe.
See some friends.
You don't have
any friends, damon.
You're right, stefan.
i only have you, so...
Where are we goin'?
"we" are not
going anywhere.
I'm gonna live my life
as far away from you
as possible.
But we're a team.
we could travel
the world together.
We could try out for
"the amazing race."
Hmm. that's funny.
Seriously,
where are you goin'?
'cause we're not
staying in this town.
[bell rings]
I'm here to see damon.
Uh, sure. ok.
Sheriff.
What a surprise.
Sorry to bother you,
but we need to talk.
Come in.
Um, i hope you understand
the secrecy.
Stefan doesn't know
about this yet.
I'd like to keep it
that way.
Of course. kids are
too young to be
brought into this.
So, what do you need?
There's been
another attack--
A female victim,
her throat torn out,
Completely drained
of blood.
It fits the pattern.
I-i'm sorry.
i don't understand.
I thought we solved
that problem when i...
Staked the blonde one.
I'm thinking she must
have turned someone
Or multiple someones.
i don't know.
The story for
the town is another
animal attack,
But i'm not sure
how long we can keep
lying to them.
The council's
in an uproar.
We thought
we were past this.
So, uh, what do we do?
You're the only one
who's ever taken on
a vampire.
We were hoping
you could tell us.
Matt: and then the ballet dancer
and the krumper did the salsa.
Well, i was awake
for that part.
Well, i don't know
when you fell asleep.
Um, did you see
the celine dion waltz
about cancer?
Those always
make me cry.
Yeah. and then the loud
judge kept screamin',
and i couldn't take it,
So i turned it off.
I sat through
"family guy,"
So you owed me.
Did i miss something?
They've been hanging out.
Kind of weird,
don't you think?
She needs
someone nice like him,
As opposed
to a homicidal vampire
like damon.
Yeah. how are you
doing with all that?
I'm freaked out.
Damon attacked me.
i could be dead right now.
But i'm also grateful.
What?
To stefan.
He sed my life, and...
Have you seen him?
Not since he told me
was leaving.
for all i know,
he's already gone.
He wouldn't leave
without saying good-bye.
Yes, he would.
He thinks
he's protecting me.
Clean break
and all that.
So what are you
gonna do?
What am i
supposed to do?
I already begged him
not to go.
If i ask again,
i'm being selfish.
It is what it is.
Well, maybe it's
for the best.
What? why?
I mean, what kinof f fure
could you have had with him,
Even if he stayed?
Did you just--
No, i swear.
Damon: thank you
for stopping by.
Let me know
what you come up with.
Absolutely.
What is wrong with you?
you killed somebody?
Get off of me.
A--don't touch me.
B--if i had,
i wouldn't havbeen
so obvious about it.
C--there's another
vampire in town.
That's impossible.
Obviously not.
Then who could it be?
Ah, what do we care?
We're leavin'
anyway, right?
No, i can't leave now,
and you know that.
How are we supposed
to find this person?
Let the adults
handle this, stefan.
See you later, ok?
Bye.
bye.
Hi.
We need to talk.
So what's up
with you and forbes?
Nothin's up.
I saw you two
in the hall today.
Don't even try
and deny it, bro.
You're tappin' that.
No, it's not like that.
Never is
till you become "we people."
[music playing]
"we people"?
Yeah.
"we can't make it
to the party."
"we'll never
miss a game."
"we don't like
the color red."
We hung out,
like, twice.
Like i said, "we."
So you have no idea
who it could be?
None.
But it must be
somebody new,
Because leaving
a body like that,
They're
either sloppy,
Or they're trying
to send a message.
And u're sure
it's not damon.
Well, i'm never
sure about damon,
But he's been
trying to keep
a low profile lately,
So it just doesn't
make any sense to me.
So what are you
gonna do?
Damon's tracking them
right now.
Look, i promised you
the truth,
So i wanted to tell you.
I want you
to be careful.
When i saw you, i...
Thought you were coming
to say good-bye.
Ah.
Not yet.
[footsteps]
Hey, what do
you think?
Creepy.
Found this old journal
in dad's stuff--
Jonathan gilbert
from the 1800s.
He's kind of
a freak show.
he wrote about demons
And all these people
getting slaughtered
and--
Yeah, he was a writer--
short stories, horror stuff.
Oh, he wrote fiction?
Figured he was just
a lunatic or a drunk.
Well, he was a gilbert,
Probably
a little bit of both.
So what do i do now?
Damon: just wait.
i'll be there in a minute.
Can you hurry?
i have things to do.
You could
give me that.
So why did you
need me to do this?
Because i interfere
with the signal.
Can i go now?
This has blown,
like, half of my day.
You do that.
Get in your car.
go home.
Forget i asked you
to do this.
Ok. bye now.
Bye.
[gunfire]
[groaning]
I have tons
of these wooden bullets,
So nothin' funky.
You don't wanna do this.
trust me.
Aah! ow!
That's what you get.
For what?
You made me like this.
I killed you.
i didn't turn you.
See, i know what you
and your brother are.
I've been watchin'
the two of you.
I knew
you'd show up here,
And i'm glad you did,
'cause i have
some questions.
Me first.
who turned you?
How should i know?
Last thing
i remember is i'm about
to stake your brother,
And then you grabbed me.
that's it.
Until i wake up
in the ground
Behind a used-car
dealership on highway 4.
Somebody buried me.
It happens. ow.
You bit me.
Damn it.
It had to be you.
You have to have vampire blood
in your system when you die.
I didn't do that.
Some other vampire
found you,
Gave you their blood.
[groans]
Who?
That's what i wanna know.
Dude, it's not like
the welcome wagon
Was waiting
with a bundt cake
and a handbook.
It's been
a learn-as-you-go
process.
You know, one minute,
I'm a small-town
on-the-rise news guy,
And next thing
i know, i can't get
into my house,
Because my foowowon'
go through the door.
You have to be
invited in.
I know. i live alone.
Ah. heh heh.
that sucks.
So now i'm
at the ramada watchin'
pay-per-view all day,
Eating everything
in sight,
Including housekeeping.
It could be worse.
All i can
think about is blood
and killing people.
I can't stop
killing people.
I keep killing.
heh heh.
And i like it.
I'm conflicted.
Welcome to the club.
Wait a minute.
Cops only found
one body.
I left one. i was tired.
But i've been hidin'
the st o othe bodies.
They're
right back there.
You're kidding.
They're just pilin' up.
[music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
So what do we know?
Nothing new
to report yet.
My highly
reliable deputies
are all on alert,
But if you feel the need
to be more proactive,
By all means,
grab a stake
and have at it.
What extra precautions
can we take?
For right now, there's
nowhere safer than
a crowded public place,
And for once, mayor,
we actually know
where our kids are.
What do you want?
Hey. uh, just surprised
to see you here.
Art usually implies culture,
And culture implies,
well, not you.
Go to hell.
Still wanna be
an astronaut?
I can't believe
you remember that.
I can remember
the tinfoil that
you wore on your head.
I was 8.
How are you doing?
I've had it easier.
You?
Uh, i heard some things.
So it's true
that you and stefan...
Yeah, it is.
What about you...
Matt donovan?
I heard about caroline.
Aw, man, not you, too.
Hey.
We're friends.
It's not a big deal.
No?
No.
Why am i
so overly emotional?
All i can think about
is my ex-girlfriend.
I wanna be with her
and bite her and stuff.
Well, you probably
love her.
Anything you felt before
will be magnified now.
You're gonna have to learn
how to control that.
What about
walkin' in the sun?
I'm a morning person.
You can walk in the sun,
which, by the way,
Is pretty cool.
Council'd never
suspect you.
It's not
in the journals.
The journals?
Yeah,
the founding fathers,
They passed down
journals to their kids.
Come on, man.
you gotta tell me.
How can you walk around
in the sun?
Who turned you?
How do you walk
in the sun?
Who turned you?
You know, i've been
really nice so far,
But i will kill you.
Then you'll never know.
You're not answering
my question.
You first.
Seems we're at a bit
of an impasse then, doesn't it?
I have things to do,
people to kill.
Guess i'll be needing
a little head start.
Aaaah!
Ow.
Ahh. damn it.
I'm guessing you're not here
to plan the path
for your future.
You're looking out
for me.
Hope that's ok.
You know, i wanted
to be a doctor
Before everything
happened, but, uh,
Then i couldn't,
cause...
The blood.
Yeah.
I've dabbled in a bunch of different
things, though.
Didn't love anything
enough to stick to it?
No, i--i loved it all.
I just--i had to
move on before
Anybody could notice
that i wasn't getting
any older.
How long before
th would happen?
Few years, usually.
Sometimes shorter.
And you always left.
I didn't have a choice.
So what about--
what about you?
What are your, uh,
plans for the future?
I don't wanna talk
about my future, stefan,
Because everything
you're saying is making it
perfectly clear
That you're
not gonna be in it.
Elena, it's not that
i don't wanna  in it.
You can' i get it.
I heard you the first me
and the second time,
And i appreciate you
looking out for me,
But, please, if you're
gonna leave, then just go.
Hide me.
What's going on?
The scum fell
has landed.
Logan's here.
Wait. logan fell?
Stefan, what's going on?
Jenna, are you
dodging me?
It's a form of
self-preservation.
Um, elena, why don't
you and jenna go
somewhere else.
Let's go.
What are you
doin' here?
You know, your brother
asked me the same thing.
In fact, why don't we just skip past
all that who-turned-me stuff
And get the answer
that i want?
How can i turn into
a daywalker?
Damon and i are the only 2
that i know of.
But you're both very cagey
on the how,
Which tells me
that there is a way.
You know, in case
you hadn't noticed
I'm quite the celebrity
in this town.
It would be very, very easy
for me to expose you.
You wanna know how you can
walk around in the sun?
I do.
You can't.
Don't ever
threaten me again.
When logan came to the house,
what did he say?
[groans] fake flattery.
stupid, dimpled grin.
Puppy dog eyes.
I'm serious, jenna.
How did he act?
what did he say?
He was the usual logan,
was charming,
Little more manic
than usual.
He kept trying to convince me
to let him in.
Ok, listen to me
very carefully.
Do not,
under any circumstances,
Talk to him again.
i'm serious, jenna, like, ever.
Hey. elena.
Jenna.
Hi, mr. saltzman.
Yeah, i was hopin'
to, uh, see you tonight.
Career night
is the new bowling.
Ah. heh heh.
Ok. um, excuse me.
Damon:
logan fell's
a vampire,
And when i find him
again, i am gonna
destroy him
Limb by limb.
What happened? you ok?
No. i'm not ok.
i was ambushed.
I was shot.
Now i'm vengeful.
just gotta find him.
Well, there's no need.
he's here at the school.
You're kidding me.
Why the hell
is he there?
He's workin' the crowd.
Well, i'll be
right there.
So anything
you'd like to share?
What are you doin'?
Following my future.
Broadcast
journalism?
Yes.
Broadcast journalism.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
You don't even
read the paper.
Liz.
Logan.
What are you gonna do,
stake me?
Bury me in another
shallow grave?
What would the e-mail
say this time?
I didn't have a choice.
You bitch.
I died for you,
for this town.
You've known me
since i was 6,
And you swept me
under the rug like dirt.
You knew what you
were getting into.
I was one of you.
And now you're
one of them.
Watch your back,
sheriff.
Get a backup team
to the school
immediately.
Keep it within
the circle. it's a v5.
I didn't know you drew.
It's an elective.
'cause it's good stuff.
you like graphics?
'cause that's, uh--
that's kind of my thing.
Whoa. whoa.
what are you doin'?
Well, it's just
something else
we have in common.
And what's
the other thing? vicki?
Let's hang out because
we did the same chick?
Go be friends with
one of the many other
guys that she screwed.
There's
no shortage of 'em.
Whoa. whoa.
hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey. hey.
All right, work it out,
tough guy.
You two,
follow me.
Excuse me, mayor.
Where are you
takin' 'em?
I'm gonna talk to 'em.
All fights should end
in handshakes, don't you think?
Bonnie, where are you?
i'm ready to go.
I'll be outside.
Hey, damsel in distress.
Need a ride?
Oh, my god.
logan fell, channel 9,
is that you?
I used to baby-sit you,
caroline forbes. don't mock me.
Well, i was supposed
to go home with bonnie,
But i can't find her.
It's not a problem, really.
it's on my way.
Ok.
You know,
this is fate.
And why is that?
'cause i'm interested
in broadcast journalism.
So can i ask you
a couple questions?
Anything you want.
First, buckle up.
Matt: hey.
Hey, have you seen logan fell,
the news guy?
Yeah. he just
gave caroline
a ride home.
Stay here.
Ok.
Let's get this
out of your system.
Go ahead. fight.
You want us to what?
I'm not gonna
fight him, dad.
I don't think so, sir.
You don't fight
in there like pansies.
You take it outside, fight your battles
like men, and move on.
Best lesson
my dad taught me.
So let's settle it.
Fight.
Come on, dad.
It's not gonna happen.
I said fight!
Whoa. what's
goin' on out here?
Just lettin'
these 2 kids work it out.
We're good here.
go back inside.
I don't wanna go
back inside.
What i want
is an answer
to my question.
What's goin' on
out here?
Who do you think
you're talkin' to?
Do i look like
a student?
No, you look like
a full-grown
Alpha-male
douche bag.
You don't talk
to me like that.
I can have your job
like this.
Ahyou do that.
Then it'll be
you and me
In this parking lot
working things out.
You cool with that?
You just
marked yourself.
Ok.
You all right?
[cellphone rings]
Where are you?
Your daughter has
expressed an interest
in journalism.
I think it's important
to foster young minds.
What do you want?
The satisfaction
of turning your daughter
into a vampire.
Payback's a bitch,
isn't it?
Get her out of here.
Liz: logan,
what happened?! logan!
Sheriff.
i-it's damon.
Where's caroline?
She's ok.
i-i'm on elm street.
[groaning]
Gonna try this
one more time.
Who turned you?
I told you
i don't know.
This tire iron here
could take your head
clean off.
Is that
your final answer?
How can you side
with them?
I don't side
with anyone.
You pissed me off.
I want you dead.
Who turned you?
i don't know!
oh, well.
you're screwed.
Wait, wait! i do know.
you're lying.
You think
you're the only one
that wants to get
In that tomb underneath
the old church?
If you are lying to me,
i will end you.
I am not lying.
there's another way
to break the spell.
We can help you.
[siren]
Meet me
at the old church.
Take me down.
make it look real.
Where is she?
She's ok.
Oh, god.
My brother's
taken her home.
I'm sorry, sheriff.
I just wasn't
strong enough.
Caroline?
She's ok.
i took her home.
She was shaken up,
but all she knows
Is logan attacked her.
nothing else.
Where's logan?
Damon's dealing with it.
As in...
You saw what happened
today, right?
I mean, you understand
why we can't...
Be together?
you see it?
Yeah, i'm starting to see
a lot of things, stefan.
Come on. i'll, uh--
I'll give you a ride.
Uh, i can get home.
I know.
All right.
that'd be nice.
Hey.
What do you want?
I don't know.
I, uh--i thought that
was weird with your dad,
What he did.
Is he like that
all the time? is that--
is that what you
gotta go through?
Man, i--i get it.
I get it.
What's your problem?
Look, i don't need
your pity.
Seriously, you don't
have to be like this.
You don't.
just go.
What's your problem,
man?
I don't knowokok
I don't know.
What i said before
about you leaving,
it was harsh.
No, no.
You--you had
every right.
You asked me what i
wanted my future to be.
I wanted to be a writer.
My mom sort of pushed me
into that direction
From the time
i was able to read.
She supported me,
encouraged me,
Bought me
my first journal,
And then she died.
And i can't see myself
being a writer anymore.
That was something
that we shared.
i know that you think
that you brought
All of this bad stuff
into my life,
But my life
already had it.
I was buried in it.
This is different.
It doesn't make it
any less painful.
I know that it's--
that it's hard to understand...
But i'm doing this for you.
[door closes]
Elena: no.
You don't
get to make that
decision for me.
If you walk away,
it's for you,
Because i know
what i want.
Stefan, i love you.
[music playing]
Don't.
Elena, i can't.
Yes, you can.
Don't hide from me.
Who are you?
A friend of jenna's.
Jenna sent you?
I came on my own.
Ah. i get it.
Well, buddy, i know
you think this makes you brave,
But actually it makes you
pretty stupid.
Either way, here i am.
What do you want?
Ah, jenna's
a good person.
she deserves the best.
I'm here to make sure
she gets it.
Was that supposed
to be a threat?
Couldn't you throw a punch?
Maybe provoke me
a little?
I'm not a violent guy
by design.
Well, you're not
a very smart one,
either.
How's that?
'cause you have no idea
who you're talking to.
I need a ride.
Sure.
Look, i like caroline.
She's got this thing,
this--this way about her,
And i like her, ok?
And i'm not gonna defend it
or apologize about it.
Ok.
So stop your little
bromance bitch act.
Ok.
[music playing]
[cellphone rings]
Yeah.
I'll be right there.
I've never been
in your room before.
Hmm.
Well, hasn't changed
much over the years.
Do you leave everything here
when you come and go?
It's the only place
that--that has
remained constant.
This room holds
every memory
That i ever thought
was important enough
to hold on to.
A lot of memories.
Yeah.
You thirsty
or anything?
A little.
You?
Uh...
Heh.
I'm fine.
Let me get you
something to drink, ok?
Ok.
[music playing]
[music fades out]
[cellphone rings]
Hello.
Liz: i just wanted
to say thank you.
I don't know
how you did it.
Uh, not following.
We found logan's body
out by the old
fell warehouse.
It's been disposed of.
He was hoarding bodies,
innocent victims.
What?
This town
owes you so much.
So do i.
Elena.
[gasps]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net