Previously on
"the vampire diaries..."
For over a century,
I have lived in secret- until now.
I know the risk,
but I have to knower.
Damon: Elena, she's a
dead ringer for katherine.
Our love for katherine
wasn't real, damon.
It was real for me.
I'm going to bring her back.
There's a tomb
underneath the church.
A spell sealed katherine in
that tomb, protecting her.
Tell me how to get in the tomb.
The grimoire.
Where is it?
Check the journal.
Jonathan gilbert's.
The grimoire. It
w emily's, right?
That's what you need
to reverse the spell.
I'll help you.
You just couldn't
live without me, huh?
Your eye!
Where'd she go?
Where'd who go?
Anna.
Elena!
[dog barking in distance]
[gasping]
[click]
I wouldn't.
[gasps]
Don't try to escape.
Don't even move.
Do you uerstand?
I understand.
Seriously?!
I told her
not toove!
I did that eye
thing you taught me.
You forgot the lesso
about vervain.
She takes a vampire
venom, duh!
Who are you?
What do you want?
Doesn't matter.
[breathing heavily]
[electricity flickering]
Bonnie?
[gasping]
Oh, my god!
Sync by JesKa
http://www.addic7ed.com/
Anna took elena.
Yeah, I got that from
your 600 voicemails.
Damon, all night long,
every single street in town,
I've been searching.
What if your blood hasn't
passed out of her system?
Well, then at least you
know you'll see her again.
Please.
What do you know?
You were with anna. You
st know where she's living.
Just tell me
where I can find her.
Nope.
You can go.
Really.
You know, all I can
remember is hating you.
There might have been a time
when that was different,
But your choices have erased
anything good about you.
But see, I also know that youave
just as much reason to hate me.
This all began with me.
Katherine got taken away
from you
Because me.
And I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
So please,
Ju tell me what you know.
Huh.
It's elena, damon.
If you know something...
Tell me.
[sighs]
I mean this sincerely.
I ho elena dies.
Bonnie.
Elena?
Oh, you're ok!
My head...
Come here.
Oh, my god! Ben is a-
Shh. [whispering]
they can hear.
I was so stupid!
Oh, he had all
of us fooled.
What's going on?
Why are we here?
It mt have something to do with
the tomb and emily's spell book.
Spell book?
Damon said that
it could be used
To open the tomb.
Why didn't I know
about any of this?
I was trying
to keep you out of it,
Hoping it would never
come to this.
Come to what?
They need a witch...
To break the spell
anlet the vampires out.
No way.
I know-
You're wasting your time.
I'm not going
to help you.
That's why she's here.
Motivation for you
to behav
You know, you shouldn't
be so desperate.
You made it too easy.
[elena groaning]
she needs to talk to you.
[grunting]
Elena gilbert.
You really are
katherine's doppelganger.
You must have
the salvatore boys reeling.
Whare you?
I'm anna.
Your brother may have
mentioned me.
I mean, we're, like,
practically dating.
Ten kegs?
You know how much damage
we could do with ten kegs?
Duke's got it all
hooked up.
Duke's a douche.
Yeah, a douche
with ten kegs.
Aka, my new best friend.
What's the problem,
gilbert?
Don't have one,
lockwood.
Yeah, I didn't
think so.
You ever get bored of it?
Of what?
Yourself?
Keep laughing, buddy.
Hey, jeremy.
Where is elena?
I have been texting
heand bonnie
All day about
duke's party.
Uh, she went somewhere
with stefan.
[sighs] I am so not going
to be one of those girls
Who disappears just because
she has a new boyfriend.
Who is duke?
Some guy that graduated
a couple years ago.
And he throws a party every
time he comes home from duke.
Wait, duke goes to duke?
His real name
is bob or something.
He's a total ass.
But he buys the beer.
Maybe you should come.
Uh, yeah. -
I don't think so.
No, seriously.
Everyone goes.
Even quiet loner
little brothers.
Think about it.
Hey!
Hey.
So I have speech.
It is fully scripted
and well-rehearsed.
Are you ready
foit?
You wrote a speech?
Yes.
It's a "you kissed me
And I don't want things
to be weird" speech.
It's pre-emptive.
[chuckles] pre-emptive.
Yeah, you know, in case you
were having second thoughts
Or regrets
Or were,ike,
ooged out-
Ooged, huh?
[chuckles]
Can I just get on
with the speech part?
Yeah, go for it.
So I know that
you don't think
That this is going to
work out between us.
I just want to let you knowhat
right here and right now,
I'm offering you an out.
Like an escape clause.
Why are you giving me
an escape clause?
I don't want to make assumptions
about what it is we are doing here.
Got it.
So, if you would
like to exercise it,
Just let me know.
I'm good, but thanks.
Ok.
Good.
Yeah.
So...
See you for duke's
tonight. Yeah.
[chuckles]
Yes?
Hi there.
I'm looking for bonnie.
She's not here.
Oh, do you know
when she would
Never.
[chuckles]
You have quite an opinion
for someone who doesn't know me.
You got some nerve knocking
on a bennett witch's door
And asking her
for anything.
What'd I do?
Spirits talk,
mr. Salvatore,
And so does
my granddaughter.
You are no friend to us.
Now get off
my porch.
Step outside and say that.
[groaning]
I am not bonnie.
You don't want
to mess withe.
Bonnie's not going
to open the tomb.
Oh, I think
she will.
Do you really want
katherine out that bad?
Trust me.
No one I know wants
to see that girl again.
Except damon,
the lovestruck idiot.
Then wt is it?
Or who is it?
My mother's in there.
Katherine couldn't
help herself.
She just had
tooy around
With both
of the salvatore brothers.
And when she g caught,
So did my mother.
I watched jonathan
gilbert take her away.
I'm sorry.
You really mean that,
don't you?
[chuckles]
Yeah, I think
wel skip
The dead mom bonding so you
can start serving a purpose.
Which is what?
Leverage.
This belong to you?
Ah, ah.
[dialing]
Hmm.
Elena, are you ok?
She's fine,
for now.
Tell me you have the
grimoire and she'll stay fine.
I can get it.
Which means
your brother has it.
And I have the witch.
So one of you
had bettereet me
In the very public
town square in 30 minutes
So we n safely discuss
How fun it's going
to be to work together.
Go ahead.
Grovel again.
Oh, wait, no.
I don't care.
I'm leaving.
Keep them buttoned down.
Compsion won't work.
Just use violenc
right.
I got that.
Sit. Behave.
You're the key
to this.
Literally.
The one who opens
the door.
Tell me, how long
have you been a witch?
Is there anything
to drink here?
Are you offering?
There's water
on the nightstand.
Hey. Can I have a sip?
Whoa! [gasping]
Come back in,
shut the door!
Don't hurt her!
Don't make me!
Lock it.
Anna!
Hey, what, uh,
What happened to you
last night?
Sorry,
I had to leave.
I told your sister
to tell you.
Oh, I haven't seen her.
Well, I gotta run, so-
Hey, do you want to go
to a party tonight?
Do I what?
The guy that's throwing it
is a total douche,
But it's, uh,
it's supposed to be fun.
I figured, you know,
safety in numbers.
[chuckles] so you're finally
ready to go out with me, are you?
It's been a while
since I've been to a party,
And I kindwant
to get back out there.
And not be such a lor.
And, uh, I like you.
You're fun,
and you're also kind of
Strange and lurky, but,h,
I guess I like that, too.
So, yeah, you should
come to the party. With me.
It's in the woods
by that old cemetery.
Oh.
It's there, huh?
That sounds cool.
Uh, I'll meet yo
Oh-ok! Great!
Cool.
Ok! [chuckles]
Got a hot date,
Or are you just planning on
nabbing the entire gilbert family?
A party, right next
to the old cemetery.
Isn't that nice
of them?
Lots of warm bods
for starving vampires.
I told you.
I work alone.
Yeah, so do I.
But you're
minus a witch
And I'm minus
spell book.
So what do you say?
Stefan will come after you,
you know that.
For messing with elena.
Then he won't be too
happy if I kill her
When I don't get
what iant.
[groans]
When do you want
to do this?
[exhales]
God, it's like 1864
all over again.
You salvatores are truly
pathetic when it comes to women.
Tonight. After sundown.
Meet at the church.
Witches don't have
eternal life, right?
So you guys can die.
Yeah, we can die.
Ah.
That sucks.
[screaming]
Stefan!
Let's get outside.
[groaning]
When the sun goes down,
Leave town.
If I ever
see you again,
I will kill you.
[gasping]
[birds chirping]
How did you know
where we we?
Many things can
el a witch's power.
Worry, anger.
After stefan told me that they
had taken you, I had a lot of both.
Simple locator spell
was easy after that.
I'm sorry.
About all of this.
Not as sorry
as they're gonna b
So what do we do now?
For now, you need
to stay here.
A prisoner,
in my own home?
I don't think so.
I can't protect you
if you leave the house.
We'll protect
ourselves.
We need to let him
have katherine back.
He's not going to stop
until he gets her.
If we help him,
maybe that ends it.
No! He doesn't deserve
to get what he wants.
What other choice
do we have?
Witches being pulled
down by vampire problems.
As much as we tried
to do to stay out of it.
I'll open the tomb.
You get
your brother'sirl,
And destroy the rest
with fire.
Then this will be
all over.
We still have to get
damon to agree.
He already agreed once.
Yeah, and then we
double cross him.
So now he's angr
He's hurt.
There's a difference.
I think I know
what I have to do.
[chuckles]
You've got
to be kidding me.
It was stefan.
There was nothing
I could-
Shut up!
Stop talking.
Without the witch,
We don't have damon
or the grimoire.
Damon's not going
to stop.
He'll find a way
to get in.
And we're going to be
there when he does.
I'm going to have
to change the locks.
Did you stage
a jailbreak?
Stefan.
Oh, brother.
Ever the white knight.
I convinced bonnie
to help you.
I doubt that.
I'm not going to say
that I'm sorry
We got the grimoire
without you last night,
Because I'm not, really.
Well, at least you're honest.
I was protecting
the people I love, damon.
But so were you,
In your own,
twisted way.
And as hard
as it is to figure,
We're all on
the same side,
After the same thing.
Not interested.
Yes, you a.
Because you were willing
to work with us yesterday.
Foole once,
shame on you.
Ok, when we were
in atlanta,
Why didn't you use
your compulsion on me?
Who's to say I didn't?
You didn't.
I know you didn't.
But you could have.
You and I...
We have something.
An understanding.
And I know that
my betrayal hurt you,
Different from how it is
with you andtefan,
But I'm promising you
this now,
I ll help you
get katherine back.
[groans]
I wish I could believe you
Ask me
if I'm lying now.
No animal will stop,
by the way,
No matter what I do.
Then we'll deal
with it.
I didn't compel you in atlanta
because we were having fun.
I wanted it to be real.
I'm trusting you.
Don't make me regret it.
The duke party.
I forgot.
I hope they stay
clear of the church.
Your hope, n mine.
Matt: Elena, hey.
Elena, oh, my god.
Where have you been?
Long story,
no time to tell it.
Wasn't talking to you.
Sure you were.
We haven't met.
I'm matt.
Matt, there's a reason
we haven't met.
You and I are
going that way.
Ahhh. I'm sorry,
you guys.
Cleared the debris away.
Set the torches
like you asked.
We can get down now.
Elena: What is that?
It's everything I need
to destroy them.
Are you sure damon
will come back with her?
[damon whistles]
Brother, witches.
Everything ok?
I just want
to get this over with.
Are we ready?
I guess so.
[all cheering]
[rock music playing]
Done!
[laughter]
Hey, uh,
I'll be right back.
Hey, man.
Uh, you got any weed?
Wait, you're kidding me,
right?
You act like a total dick
every time we cross paths,
And now you want
to party witme?
[indistinct] I'm just
asking question.
Dude, I don't geyou, man.
It's aarty.
You're a partier, ok?
There's no need
to psychoanalyze it.
I don't party anyme.
And even if I did,
it wouldn't be with you.
No problem.
Carry on just standing
there, by yourself.
All alone.
The enemy of fun.
Do you even have
any friends?
[chuckles]
Thank go
Weird hello, but ok.
What's the matter?
Uh, nothin'.
Nothing, just...
It's nothin'.
Come on, let walk.
Air.
Earth.
Fire.
Water.
That's it,
just water from the tap?
As opposed
to what?
I just figured maybit
would have to be blessed
Or mystical
or something.
What's that?
It's for katherine.
Gotta have something
to get her going.
Unless your girl's
offering a vein to tap.
[sighs]
Admit it-
You can't wait
to get rid of me.
[chuckles]
I can't wait
to get rid of you.
Hmm.
You ready?
[indistinct chatter]
This place is wild.
You kinda like
dead people, huh?
I'm strange, remember?
You ok?
Yeah, yeah.
Uh...
This place makes me
think about someone.
A dead someone?
No, no, just...
Someone I used
to know.
So, uh, hey.
[chuckles]
We made it all of, what,
37 minutes in that party?
Not your scene?
No, I'm not really su
what my scene is anymore.
Hmm.
So what do you say?
You want to be
part of my non-scene?
I would happily
be a part of your non-scene,
Except, uh,
I'm leaving.
Wait, what?
Yeah. My mom and I
are moving away.
Oh, uh...
That's-
that's a bummer.
Yeah?
Well, yeah.
So...
Guess this is good-bye.
I guess it is.
Anna, your face!
It's nothing.
It didn't look like
nothing.
[sighs] you didn't have
to hit him that hard.
Yes, I did.
Grab him,
and let's go.
I'm taking him
to meet my mother.
Where's your date?
Who knows?
Ah, is the honeymoon
over already?
Maybe.
After all that grief you
gave me about liking her.
I figured it would have lasted
longer than five minutes.
Look, I just
- I don't know if I can do the whole public couple thing.
She-she seems like
she might be a little clingy.
Well, good.
I need my boy single
anyway.
Ooh.
Incoming.
Hey.
There you are.
Here I am.
Yeah, well, I'm not
drunk enough,
So I'm just going
to go get another beer.
So...
So.
I have
another speech.
Ok.
The hand thing
with elena,
It was lame.
Well, I was lame.
And, hey, your feelings
for elena aside,
Damon wathere,
And he was always
such a jerk to me.
And...
I wanted to show off that
I was with the good guy.
So, anyway,
I was lame.
So...
Forgiven?
Yeah, course.
Yeah.
[chanting
in foreign language]
What's happening?
It worked!
Of course
it worked.
Weave some fires
to build.
I'm gonna go get the
gasoli, I'll be right back.
You ready?
What?
You think I'm going
to go in there by myself
So you can seal me in?
Don't take her in.
I'll bring
the walls down.
You'll bring walls down if
I don't. Yothink I trust you?
As much as I trust you.
Enough!
Both of u.
Look, he needs
leverage.
He needs to know
that you're not going
To shut the door
when he gets inside.
I get it.
I'll go.
May I?
Dark down there?
I thought I told you
to leave.
I considered it.
Then I thought,
screw you.
Anna: Hey, hero.
I'm going down there
to get my mother.
Can't let you
do that.
Well, ben's about to
make a main course
Out of elena's
little brother,
So y can stop me
or him.
Your choice.
[clattering]
What is that?
They can sense you.
Where is she?!
Damon!
Hey, you're not
going in tre.
You think you can
stop me?
Bonnie...
Why did you
let her go in?
Because she isn't
coming out, baby.
None of them are.
Do
hmm?
You're disposable.
I don't care. She already
gave me what I want.
You're going to say
"eternal life"?
You're really
that stupid?
You know,
I've heard about you.
You don't feed.
You're not strong enough
to beat me.
[both grunting]
Is that all you got?
No.
I got this.
Damon?
Damon!
Where's elena?
Damon took her
inside.
What?!
Stefan!
If you go in there,
you won't come out.
What did you do?
Opening the door
didn't remove the seal,
It just opened the door.
What's the sea
Some seals keep vampires
from entering.
This one
eps them from...
Coming out.
Elena's human.
She can leave.
Anna and katherine can't.
Damon can't.
You weren't even planning
on breaking the spell,
Were you?
I told you.
I ll protect my own.
Elena can get out.
That's all that matters.
You must have
a taste for it.
You scream and shriek
and even bother to escape,
But then you just come
right back to it.
Oh, oh!
Mother!
Your boyfriend
did this, you know.
His father did.
And jonathan gilbert.
Made a choice
a long time ago
That iwould be
gilbert blood
That brought
her back to life.
I had jeremy
all ready to go,
But...
[gasping]
[screaming]
Stefan!
You can't just leave him
inhere, grams!
He made his choice!
Here.
Just tell me what
to do. I'll do it!
We areot strong enough.
Even if we were able
to bring the seal down,
There's no guarantee that
we can get it back up again.
You said it
yourself-
Many things can fuel
a witch's power.
Help me!
Or I'll do it alone.
[both grunting]
Please don't!
[groaning]
Let her go!
No!
Go, go. I'll be
right behind you.
Pearl: Anna!
Where am I?
Elena, stefan...
He's right behind me.
Efan,
what are you doing?
It's gonna be ok.
We'll fix it.
What is it?
I can't.
Can't?
Can't what?
The spell's still up,
we can't get them out.
Yet.
You went in there
not knowing
If you could
come back out?
Oh, my god.
I heard you scream.
We can't leave him
in there.
We promised him,
both of us.
I know.
Even if we're able
to break through the seal,
Weon't be able
to hold it for long.
[grunting]
She's not here!
Damon.
She's not here.
What?
She's not here!
[chanting
in foreign language]
I think it's working!
I just wanted
my mother back.
Jeremy's fine. He's
outside. We won't touch him.
Keep going!
You better hry.
Stefan, they can't
hold it much longer!
[gasping]
Damon, we need
to get out of here.
It doesn't make sense.
They locked her inside.
If we don't leave now,
We're not getting out.
How could she not
be in here?
It's not worth spending
all of eternity down here!
She's not worth it!
No!
Elena: Damon!
Please.
[chanting
in foreign language]
[gasps] oh, my god!
I can't!
You can!
Is this for real?
Is what for real?
You being all cool
and honest and open?
Speech number three?
I want this to work.
And I'm scared that you're
going to change your mind
And you're not
going to want it.
I don't want
to mesit up.
to mess it up, either.
[owl hooting]
He's ok.
He's all right.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Hey, let me help you.
Oh, m fine.
You don't need
to coddle me, baby.
It was a big spell, grs.
I could tell it took
a lot out of you.
I'll be fine.
How's your head?
, it's, uh,
it's all right.
I just-I wish I knew
how I pass out.
I didn't drink
that much, I swear
And you don't
remember anything?
The whole thing's
pretty cloudy. I just...
I know
how this looks.
I'm-I'm sorry.
No, remy,
don't be sorry.
You didn't do anything, ok?
Ok.
I've gotta head over
to bonnie's for a little bit,
But is there anything
that you need?
Oh, no, I'm just-
I'm gonna crash.
Ok. Well, jenna's here,
and I'll be back soon.
You knew katherine
wasn't in there.
You wouldn't
have helped me.
No!
Why do you get happiness?
Damon, please, you wouldn't have
helped me! You know you wouldn't!
Why do you get it
and I don't?!
The guard,
the way of the judge,
They really
want this thing!
She promised to turn him
He was oessed
with her.
She had him under her
spell, like everybody else!
He let her go.
[gasping]
The last I saw her
Was chicago.
1983.
She knew where
you were, damon.
She didn't care.
Sorry.
[music playing]
I just got tbonnie's.
Everything all right? Yeah.
How's damon?
Is he going to be ok?
I don't know.
Can I call you later?
Yeah, of course.
Grams?
Grams, wake up!
Grams!
Grams?!
[sobbing] elena!
Help!
Wake up!
She's not breathing!
Please, wake up!
I'm gonna fix it!
Yes, I need
an ambulance.
It's ok, I can fix this.
It's an emergency.
No, no!
I can fix this!
Grams, I can fix this!
Bonnie!
http://www.addic7ed.com/
www.tvsubtitles.net