Woman: Previously on
"the vampire diaries"...
Stefan: For over a century,
I have lived in secret
Until now.
I know the risk.
But I have to know her.
Elena--she's a dead ringer
for katherine.
I want the invention.
Don't have it.
But damon does.
And yore gonna
get it for me.
I'm not gonna
give the device to isobel
So she can give it
to john who's gonna
turn around and kill me.
But it'll be useless
bonnie can take
the spell off.
You took
a risk with damon.
How did you know
that he was going
to give it to me?
'causee's
in love with you.
I couldn't do what
she wanted me to do.
It wasn't right.
But when elena
finds out...
She's never going
to forgive me.
Ow. This dress hurts.
Humph.
Suck it in, baby.
[music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
Mrs. Lockwood:
No, no, no, no.
This lineup
is all wrong.
The marching band
should be in front of
the historicalociety.
Matt, time to get
on your float.
Boys, I asked you
to put the chair
on the founder's float.
Ladies, time to get
on your float.
Look at you,
all retro.
What are you
doing here?
Why wouldn't I be here?
Bonnie deactivated
the gilbert inventn.
Isobel's gone. Heh.
And it's founder's day.
I'm here to eat cotton candy
and steal your girl.
Don't start with me, damon.
Oh, you started it, stefan,
With that whole "I'm insecure,
leave ena alone" speech.
I'm just enjoying that.
As long as you heard it.
Huh? What?
[chuckles]
You have
noense of humor, stefan.
Actually, I just
have no see of
damon humor.
Damon humor--
hey, look.
I get it. I get it.
I'm the better, hotter,
superior choice,
And you're scared now that
katherine's out of the picture
That I'm gonna turn
all my attention to elena.
But don't worry.
Elena is not katherine.
You're right.
She's not.
Anna.
Look at you.
Heh. I know,
it's stupid, huh?
I'm part of
e parade.
But how are you?
I've been--I've been
so worried,
And I feel awful.
Why?
You didn't kill my mother.
Your uncle did.
Are you sure
it was him?
Who else
would have done it?
He doesn't
understand, anna.
It's who he is.
He hates
all vampires.
He's just doing
what he thinks is right.
Are you defending him?
No. No way.
It's just--
I do understand
where he's coming from.
He's convinced
all the tomb vampis
Want revenge
on this town,
and he's just...
He's trying
to protect it.
They do want revenge.
Or, at least, they did.
But that's why
we separated from them.
My mom wasn't after venge.
She just wanted her life back.
I haveo get out
of this town, jeremy.
You're leaving?
But I've been thinking.
You could come with me.
I could turn you.
I mean, you said
you wanted me to.
Here.
It's my blood.
If you die with it
in your system,
you'll come back.
Anna--
I know you,
What it's like for you--
Being alone,
always feeling empty inside,
No one to understand.
But when youe a vampire,
you don't have to feel that way.
You can shut it off.
I can show you how.
I wanted to. I did.
But I don't think
I ca
I'm sorry.
John?
Is--is that even posble?
Well, there's no proof,
but he dated isobel
when she was a teenager,
And he was the one who
brought her to your dad's
office for the delivery.
My who life,
I've never liked this man.
I...
I'm sorry.
I just--
I wanted to te you
before damon dropped
it on you
In some typically
inappropriate way.
No, I'm happy
that you told me. I just...
I really hope
that it's not true.
What am I supposed to do?
Do I just...
Confront him and say,
"are you mbiological father?"
I guess
when you're ready.
I'm never gonna be ready.
Stefan, I have enough problems
with the family that
I actually care about.
Jeremy hates me,
and why wouldn't he?
My journal gave him
every single reason to.
He's just hu.
He's confused.
He's never gonna
forgivme for vicki,
For taking away his memory,
for lying to him.
He's your brother.
He'll forgive you.
Just give him some time.
Bonnie: Say cheese.
Wait. Hide your cast.
It's not era-appropriate.
Seriously? Uhh.
Yes. [giggles]
ok. All right.
[shutter clicks]
I want one with bonnie now.
Here, I can take it.
I'll be on the float.
Uhh.
I said I was sorry.
You made out with his mother,
and then you beat him to a pulp.
You're gonna have to do
a little bit better than sorry.
Elena: Jeremy.
Heh. I was wondering
where you were.
You look great.
You guys did
a really great job
on the float.
Go away, elena.
Jeremy, come on, please.
I don't want it to be
like this between us.
Why don't you have damon
erase my memory again?
Then I can go back to
being your in-the-dark
little brother.
Jer, please.
Just don't.
You n't fix this
that easily.
Something like this
doesn't just get fixed.
[crowd cheering]
let's give a big hand
To the mystic falls
high school marching ban
[band playing]
Mrs. Lockwood:
And for a little local history,
Mr. Saltzman's students
have recreated
Virginia's
battle of willow creek.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
Our stunning
miss mystic falls court
And their handsome escorts.
[cheering intensifies]
This is caroline forbes,
miss mystic falls.
Mrs. Lockwood:
Aren't they beautiful?
What do you want?
Just watching
the parade.
Where are you going?
Away from you.
I want to say
something to you.
Just leave me alone.
Thank you.
The device
that emily spelled
could have killed me.
I don't take whayou did
lightly, so...
Thank you.
I did it for elena.
I know that.
But I'm still
very grateful.
And...
I owe you.
Enjoy the parade.
Mrs. Lockwood: Let's hear it
for the stic falls
high school football team.
All rit! Let's show them
our support, everybody.
This is the key.
Once inserted,
the device will be activated.
It will work only once
for an estimated time
of 5 minutes.
Mayor lockwood:
Yes. How does it work?
It's a high-pitched frequency
that humans can't he..
Any vampire
within a 5-block radius
will be incapacitated,
Exposing them.
At that time,
the sheriff's v5 depies
Will inject them with vervain
and bring themere,
Where we'll finish them off.
And you're certain
they're attacking tonight?
I had a source.
One of the vampires
from the tomb--
He confirmed the attack.
Man: Everybody listen up.
The plan stays the same.
We wait
till the fireworks start.
Ununtil then, blend in.
Stay a part
of the celebration.
They'll never see us coming.
They want revenge for what
our ancestors did in 1864,
Which makes us their targets.
This area here is the stage.
This is where
the founding famies
are gonna be.
Any questions?
We're taking
an enormous risk.
We're talking about
our families, john.
Anna.
What are you
doing here?
It's the only way
to draw them out
and kill them...
All of them.
I like you better
like this.
The period look, it...
Didn't suit you.
Is that an insult?
Actually, elena,
is a compliment
Of the highest order.
Look, I know
stefan is worried
About our friendship.
Did he mention
something to you, too?
No.Idid he mention
something to you?
No. Nothing worth repeating.
So, I think
you should stop with
the flirty little comments
And that eye thing
that you do.
What eye thing?
Heh.
Don't make me regret
being your friend.
Ok?
I don't believe
that we can't fix this.
I lied. I was wrong.
But you're my brother,
jer, and I love you.
And I have to fix it.
So, just tell me.
What can I do?
You can go to hell, elena.
[music playing]
Damon, mockingly:
I have so many emotions,
But I don't have any way
to express them.
Being a teenager is so hard.
You dick.
You do not
talk to me like that.
I'm not your sister.
And from now on,
don't talk to your sister
that way, either.
So, what, you're gonna
kill me just 'cause
I hurt ele's's feelings?
Cut her some slack.
She erased my memories.
No, I did.
She was protectingou.
It wasn't
her call to make.
[panting]
Let go of me
before I cau a scene.
You'll be unconscious
before you even
got a word out.
Let him go.
You all right?
Yeah.
What my brother
is trying to say
Ison't blame elena
for this.
Damon turned vicki.
I killed her.
She was a threat to you,
and she was a threat
to your sister.
I'm sorry that it happened.
I wish that it hadn't.
Shouldn't have
made me forget.
Good cop, bad cop--
I like it.
What are you doing? Hmm?
He was being a punk.
Elena's relationship
with her brother is
none of your business.
You stay out of it.
Oh, the's only one
Do-gooder hero role available.
Oh, my bad. I'm sorry.
Get over yourself.
We both know that
you're not doing this
for e right reasons.
See, there you go with
th little jealousy act again.
Uh, wh-what are
the right reasons, stefan?
Enlighten me. Please.
Well, see, damon,
It's only real when
it comes from your desire
To do the right thing
for nothing in return.
Right. Yeah.
And I know that that is
An entirely
foreign concept to you.
I completely understand
how you wouldn't get it.
You wa to use
our town as bait?
It's too dangerous.
It's insane.
Wee e gone over the plans
with your deputies.
They're all on board.
You've gone
behind me?
Yeah, because wenew that's
exactly how you'd react.
Our children are here.
Liz, we need to do this.
We have no choice.
This is the reason
for the secret council.
Our founding fathers
created the secret council
for just this rpose.
I'm the sheriff.
It's my call.
And I say no.
Richard, let me speak
to the sheriff alone.
John, you're not
thinking clearly.
I'm not gonna
change my mind abouthis.
Yorerellllroround?
Hehere's setetng
ou need d tonono
Thvampires from
ththe mb a arelalaingg
an attacack ninit.T.
How do you know this?
I went to them.
They think
I'm m th them, but I'm not.
They want
the founding families dead.
When is this
supposed to happen?
When the fireworks start.
John gilrt wants to use
that invention o othem.
Waitit
thenene can't bebeere.
It doesn't work.
It's been deactivated.
Well, then a lot
of people are nna die.
Where are they right now?
They're already here,
dan.
Remember, we don't know
which of them
ingest vervain.
It's not about the feed.
It's about the kill.
You know what to do.
Rick.
Yeah.
You keep those
nifty little
vamp weapons
In the car?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
Because this square
is crawling with
tomb vampires.
I think we might
need a stake or two.
Got it.
[chatterg
and laughing]
Uh, what are you doing?
Saving your life.
15 words or less--
Tomb vps are here.
Founding families
are the target.
Get her out of here. Now.
Wait. Wait.
Where are you going?
That's more than
15 words, stefan.
Wait.
Jeremy's out here somewhere.
Let's go find him.
Come on.
[music playing]
There was this time
freshman year
When bonnie and I were
in a fight.
And we swore that we would
never talk again.
Caroline,
give it a rest.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
I told you to goome.
I decided not to.
If I tell you
to do something,
you do it.
Get off me.
Mayor. Is everything ok?
Please, tyr, I need
you to go home. Now.
Take your friends
with you.
But why?
What's going on?
I can't explain.
All of you need
to get home. Now.
Please.
Yeah, ok.
[exhales] here.
[keys jingling]
take my car.
It's outack.
Come on. Caroline, matt,
go with him.
Anna, what are you doing here?
My uncle could s you--
I don't care about that.
Needed to find you.
For 150 years,
Mystic falls has been
the kind of town
That everybody
wants to call home--
Safe, osperous, welcoming.
And we have the founders
to thank for that.
And that's why I'd like
to dedicate this evening's
fireworks display
To their legacy.
[applause and cheering]
[static]
get in position.
Enjoy the show!
[fireworks whistling]
[crowd cheering]
Stay clo to me.
[cheering continues]
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
[door opens and closes]
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
Yes. As a matter
of fact, I do.
[clicking]
[high-pitched squealing]
[grunting]
Aah!
Stefan?
What's going on?
What's happening?
My head.
What?
Uhh! Aah!
Aah!
What's wrong?
Anna.
[sobbing] please make it stop.
[squealing continues]
what the hell is that?
What's the matter?
That noise.
Wait, what noise?
Oh.
Whoa.
Tyler. Tyler!
Aah!
Aah! Aah! Unh!
Dude! Hey!
[tires screeching]
caroline! The wheel!
Tyler!
Uhh!
Aah!
[squealing continues]
[grunting]
Stefan.
Ow.
I got this one.
There's one over there.
Take this. Go. Go. Go!
I don't know what happened.
He jt dropped.
He's not the only one.
Cops are grabbing everyone
whs gone down,
Injecting them
with vervain.
What?
They're rounding up
the vampires.
Please help him.
Aah! Uhh! My head!
[sobbing]
Hey, I got one.
What a you doing?
Hey! Leave her alone!
Hey!
[sobbing]
What are you doing?
Hey! Leave her alone!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Anna! Leave her one! Anna!
The device is done.
The only thing keeping them down
is the vervain.
We don't have much time.
Let's finish this.
Anna.
[liquid sloshing]
You can head up.
I'll take it from here.
[grunting]
Please.
Uhh.
[gasps]
Are you ok?
It's like needles
Were piercing my skull,
and then it just stopped.
I saw at least
5 vampires go down.
They were taking them to
your family's old building.
It's the gilbert device.
It has to be.
But how did he
get it to work?
Bonnie unspelled it.
Maybe she didn't.
She did.
We saw her do it.
No, no, no. He's right.
Think about it.
We asked bonnie
to deactivate a device
That could protect people
against vampires.
So we could
protect you.
And damon. Vampires.
Where is damon?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him
since this started.
Can you get my broer?
Take him home?
Of course.
Let's go.
[door opens]
Liz. Are you ok?
There's a key in--
what is going on?
There's a key in my belt.
I need you to get it.
Uhh. I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Something's happened
to richard.
They took him.
Who took him?
Your deputies.
I--I don't understand.
He's not a vampire.
Let's go.
[grunting and groaning]
Mayor.
Ishat you?
What are you doing here?!
I'm a vampire.
What's your excuse?
No, really.
The vervain
didn't affect you.
You're not a vampire.
What the hell are you?
Mayor lockwood.
[grunts]
[panting]
Hey, are you ok?
Your side took
the biggest hit.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
No, they need
To check you out.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
They're helping tyler.
Pulse is steadying.
All right.
[pants]
What the hell?
What? What's wrong?
His eyes.
[inhales and pants]
What happened?
Dude, don't scare me like that.
Woman: Hey, she needs
some help over here.
Caroline!
Guys! Unh!
Caroline, hey.
God, what happened?
Caroline, wake up.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can hear them.
The building's
on fire.
Elena: What?
Building's on fire.
[clattering]
Where's damon?
With the rest of them,
Where he should be.
It's over for damon.
You're crazy.
Why?
'cause I'm doing what
shou have been done
145 years ago?
This is
the right thing, elena.
Go ahead.
You won't make it out.
It'll save me the trouble
of killing you myself.
You know
the building well.
Is therenother
entrance in?
Utility door. There's one
around the side.
[grunts]
Take one more step,
and I'll alert those deputies
That they missed a vampire.
I'm asking you not to.
That doesn't mean
anything to me.
As my father, it should.
You know.
I wasn't sure.
But now I am.
Boie: Hey!
You can't go in there.
The fire
will take you out.
He's my brother, bonnie.
Ahh.
[ena panting]
stefan!
Elena! Y--
you can't go
in there.
Bonnie, what are you doi?
I'm sorry I lied to you.
[panting]
[chanting]
Bonnie, I've got to
get in there.
[continues chanting]
[bonnie chanting]
Damon.
Come on.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Come on. Come on.
[chanting]
[chants]
Bonnie...
Bonnie, what is it?
Are they gonna be ok?
[panting]
oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
[coughing]
[radio chatter]
The fire's out.
The story is that
the building's old wiring
is what caused it.
Did you see
where damon nt?
No, he just
kind of disappeared.
Figures. [chuckles]
Ohh.
I'm so glad you're ok.
[exhales]
I try so hard...
To hate him.
I guess it's just
pointless.
You care about him.
So do I.
But I love you, stefan.
I know that you're worried
about that.
I just...
You know,
I-I know my brother.
But I love you, stefan.
I know the trouble
he can cause.
I love you, stefan. You.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Ok?
[exhales] so jenna called.
Jeremy's home.
I'm just gonna run over
to the school
To pick up my dress,
my clothes
the rest of my stuff.
And en I'll check on him.
What are you doing here?
Anna's dead.
I figured that
once they took her away.
I know you cared
about her.
Yeah, I did.
I saw her killed.
I was watching
and all I could
think about was...
I wanted to help her.
But I couldn't.
Why are you telling me
all this?
I took away
your sfering
once before.
I can do it again.
But it's your choice.
Look...
I know you think
you took it away,
But it's still there.
Even if I can't
remember why,
I still feel empty.
Alone.
And making me forget
won't fix it.
It won't fix
what's really wrong.
What I did to vicki
Was wrong.
Sorry for my part.
Anna said that vampires
don't have to feel pain;
That they could turn it off
if they shut out their humanity.
That's very true.
Is it easier that way?
Is what easier?
[scoffs] life.
Life sucks
either way, jeremy.
At least
if you're a vampire,
You don't have
to feel bad abouit
if you don't want to.
Is that what you did?
I did it for...
I did it for
a very long time.
And life was
a lot easier.
[crickets chirping]
Hey, man.
I'm so sorry.
Look, I don't even know
what happened.
It's ok, man.
L right.
What's happening?
Is she all right?
Oh, there was some
internal bleeding.
We're taking her
into surry.
What else did they say?
Is she going to be ok?
They're going to do
everything they can.
Tyler, have you
talked to your mom?
I left her message
telling her I was here.
You need to call her.
What is it?
It's your dad.
[exhales]
[indistinct chatter]
oh, hey.
Hey.
You, uh,
You just missed
elena.
I was looking for you,
actually.
Oh.
Elena is my best frien
And because she loves you,
I couldn't let you
or damon die in that fire.
I'm very grateful,
bonnie.
I hope you know that.
I do. But I hope you know
that tngs have to change.
Damon has to change.
We both want
the same thing.
We both want to protect
the people we care about.
The difference is,
for you,
Damon is one of them.
You saw what I was able
to do tonight.
I know who I am now.
And if damon spills
so much as one drop
Of innocent blood,
I'll take him down.
Even if have
to take you with him.
Let's hope it doesn't
come to that.
Let's hope it doesn't.
Whatre you doing here?
A failed and feeble attempt
at doing the right thing.
Which was...
It's not important.
I'll take this from you.
Thank you.
You know,
I came in this town
Wanting to destroy it.
Tonight I...
Found myself wanting
to protect it.
How does that happen?
I'm not a hero, elena.
I don'do good.
It's not in me.
Maybe it is.
No.
No, it's reserved
for my brother
and--and you,
Andonnie,
Even though
she has every
reason to te me,
Still helped
stefan save me.
Why do you sou
so surprised?
Because she did it
for you.
Which means
that somewhere
along the way,
You decided that
I was worth saving.
And I wanted to...
Thank you for that.
You're welcome.
[music playing]
Hi.
It's late.
You should probably
come inside.
[elena sighs]
What are you doing?
I don't want
to talk about it.
[chuckles] you scared me.
Sorry.
Ohh.
You know, I first
met isobel when
I was a teenager.
I fell in love
with her instantly,
Although I'm pretty sure
She never loved me.
She was special.
And part of why I hate
the vampir so much
Is because
what she became.
How it ruined her.
And I never would have
sent her to damo
Had I known
she wanted to turn.
It's my fault.
I'm telling you this
Because I hoped
Maybe you'd
understand.
Thank you.
Can I help?
Sure.
[groaning]
[gasping]
katherine?
Hello, john.
Good-bye, john.
[groaning]
I looked everywhere.
Yeah, someone definitely
took my stuff.
I just gotta check
on jeremy before
I go to the hospital.
Can you meet me there?
Ok. I love you,
stefan.
Jeremy?
You up?
[john groaning]
♪ carry on, my wayward son ♪
♪ there'll be peace
when you are done ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net