Man: Previously on "
the vampire diaries"...
For over a century,
I have lived in secret untinow.
I know the risk. But I have to know her.
Elena--she's a deadringer for katherine.
That neckless contains
an herb calledervain.
It protects u from being compelled.
My love for therine wasn't real, damon.
I'm gonna bring her back.
There's a tomb underneath the church.
A spell sealed katherine in
that tomb, protecting her.
Hello, jenna. Logan.
Who are you? A friend of jenna's.
Aah!
Alaric saltzman.
I'm your new history teacher.
Banister showed me this-- I'm a witch.
Aah!
His face as like-- are you ok?
What's going on, elena?
I'm gonna tell her the truth.
I ow you that think that you brought
all of this bad stuff into my life.
But my life alrey had it.
This is different.
I kn what I want.
I've never been in your room before.
This room holds every memory that I
ever that I thought was important
enough to hold onto.
Elena?
Elena. It's stefan.
I know that picture must have
confused you. But I can explain.
I need to explain.
Please, when you get this, call me.
[gasp]
[coughing]
[cracking]
[cowering]
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
How ya doing in there?
Damon?
You look stuck.
My seat lt.
Let me get you out of there.
I want you to put your hands
on the roof. Just like that.
You ready?
...2, 3.
I got you.
Are you ok?
Can you stand? Anything broken?
Uh-uh.
Whoa, you're fading fast, elena.
Elena, look at me.
Focus. Look at me.
Ok.
I look like her.
What?
Upsy-daisy.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I found one.
After years of reseah and study,
there it was right in front of me.
I was terrified.
As I stared it in the eyes,
I drove a stake through its heart.
I was right about mystic falls.
There is evil here.
I can sense it. Feel it.
It's everywhere.
[music playing]
Mmm. It's not even 7:00 yet.
Which means you shouldn't be
awake for at least 6 hours.
I hate morning people.
I'm going to be home te tonight.
Mm love you.
And I love you too.
Morning.
Where are we?
Georgia.
Georgia?
No, no. No, we're not.
Seriously, damon. Where are we?
Seriously, we're-- we're in georgia.
How ya feeling?
I--I--
There's broken bones. I checked.
But my car. There was a man.
I hit a man.
But then he got up and--who was that?
That's what I would like to know.
Where is my phe?
Ok. We really need to go back.
Nobody knows where I am.
Pull over.
I mean it, damon. Pull over!
Stop the car!
Ohyou were so much more
fun when you were asleep.
Hey.
I'm fine.
We havto go back.
Oh come on. Look.
We've already come this far.
Why are you doing this?
I can't be in georgia. I wrecked my car.
I have to go home.
This is kidnapping.
That's a little melodramatic,
don'you think?
You're not funny.
You can't do this.
I'm not going to georgia.
You're in georgia.
Without your magical
necklace I might add.
I can very easily make you...Agreeable.
What are you trying to prove?
[cell phone rings]
That's my phone.
Mmm. It's your boyfriend.
I'll take it.
Elena's phe.
Where is she?
Why do you have her phone? Is she ok?
Elena? She's right here.
And, yes, she's fine.
Where are you? Let me speak to her.
He wants to talk to you.
Uh-uh.
Yeah. I don't--
I don't think she wants
to talk to you right now.
Damon, I swear to god,
if you touch her--
You have a good day. Mm-hmm. Bye-now.
Argh!
Look. No one knows where I am.
Can we please just go back?
We're almost there.
Where is there?!
A little place right outside of atlanta.
Oh, come on, elena.
You don't wanna go
back right now. Do you?
What's the rush? Time-out.
Trust me. Your problems are still
going to be there when you get home.
Look. Step away from
your life for 5 minutes.
5 minutes.
Am I going to be safe with you?
Yes.
Will you promise not to do
That mind control thing with me?
Yes.
Can I trust you?
Get in the car. Come on.
Hey, mr. Saltzman.
Hey, jeremy.
I, uh--can't find my ring.
I took it off for the gym
And thought I put it-- there it is.
Losing family heirlooms-- bad.
How's your extra credit coming?
You pick a topic yet?
Mystic falls, the cil war era.
What's the angle?
My family-- I found a journal
Of an anstor who lived in the 1800s.
And the gilberts were one of t original
founding families of mystic falls. So...
That sounds good.
Bonnie. Stefan
Hey. Hi.
I haven't seen you lately.
How are you doing with everything?
I'm fine. It's all fine.
Good. Yeah
Are you back in school?
No. Actually I came here to find you.
I s hoping you could help
me with something. A spell.
Stefan, look, I know elena's
ok with all of this,
And I appreciate what
you did to help me.
But I'm not really ready to
dive into it with you just yet.
I understand. But I need your he.
It's elena. She's with damon.
I have elena's necklace.
I was just hoping you could e this
To make some sort of a connection.
I just neeto know that she's ok.
How do you know I can do this?
Because I've known a few
witches over the years.
I've seen what they can do.
I'm still new at it.
It's ok.
Give it a shot.
Ok.
All right.
There's nothing.
Nothing's happening.
Usually there's an image or...
Tell me if anyone's looking.
Ok.
All right.
What is it?
Something's wrong. With elena?
With me. There's
something wrong with me.
I have to go. I'm sorry, stefan.
I can't hp you.
So, where's my car?
I pulled it off on the side of the road.
I don't think anyone will bother it.
At about that man in the road?
Was he a...?
From what I could tell. Yeah.
You don't kn him?
If I've never met him,
I wouldn't know him.
I mean, it's not like we all hang out
together at the vamp bar and grill.
You brought me to a bar?
Damon, I'm not old enough.
They're not going to let me in.
Sure they will.
[hands clap]
[music playing]
No. No, it can't be.
Damon.
My honey pie.
Listen up everybody!
Here's to the man that broke my heart,
Crushed my soul,
Destroyed my life,
And ruined any and all
chances of happiness!
Drink up!
Ahh. Whoo!
So, how'd he rope you in?
I'm not roped in.
Actually, I'm dating his--
Honey, if you're not roped,
you're whipped.
Either way, just eoy the ride.
Ok.
So, how did you two meet?
College.
You went to college?
I've been on a college campus, yes.
About 20 years ago, when I was
just a sweet, young freshman.
I met this butiful man,
and fell in love.
And then he told me
about his littleecret,
Made me love himore.
Because, you see,
I had a little secret of my own
That I was dying to share with somebody.
She's a witch.
Changed my world.
I rocked your world.
He is good in the sack, isn't he?
But mostly he's just a walkawayoe.
So, what is it that you want?
Oh my god. I am so sorry.
There was this one book
wedged between the other.
And I pulled and then kaplunk, kaboom.
Are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Ohh!
I'm anna.
I'm jeremy.
Thank god you're back.
And hello to you, too.
What's the matter?
Powers are gone, grams.
I can't do anything,
Even when I concentrate.
And there's nothing in
in any of these books
That can tell me how to get them back.
Hang on, now. Just calm down.
Tell me what happened.
I can't.
We keeping secrets now?
I have to. I'm sorry. I promised.
Please help me.
Well, first of all, there's nothing
in any of these that's gonna help you.
If you're blocked, it's in here.
You gotta clear it out,
then you're back in business.
Clear what out?
Whatever's got you so scared.
Hi, jenna. I'm so sorry.
Where are you? Why didn't you call?
I was so tired last night.
I fell asleep at bonnie's.
And then this morning,
I just wanted to get to school.
Are you ok?
You know, stefan and stuff.
Come on, there's gotta b another way.
After all these years,
it's still only katherine.
How do you even know she's still alive?
Well, you help me get into
that tomb and we'll find out.
I already did. 20 years ago. Remember?
3 easy steps--
Comet. Crystal. Spell.
There's a little problem with number 2.
I don't have the crystal.
That's it, damon. There is no other way.
It's emily's spell.
What about a new spell
With a new crystal that
overrides emily's spell?
It doesn't work that way, baby.
Emily's spell is absolute.
You can't get into that tomb.
Hello? [echoing]
[wood cracking]
Anybody here?!
Aah!
[cell phonringing]
[hearing in mind] stefan:
Elena, is th you?
I'm here.
Where are you?
You lied.
Not until I explain, please.
So, you didn't lie?
Just tell me where you are.
So that I can comeet you.
How am I connected to katherine, stefan?
I honestly don't know.
And I'm supposed to believe that?
It's the truth. I--
Listen--
[hangs up]
You ok?
Don't pretend to care.
I know you're gloating inside.
[dialing]
[blender starts]
Hey, it's bree.
You'll never gonna guess
who walked into my bar.
Oww.
Hello?!
Anybody?!
Ahh!
[knocking]
Hi.
Can I help you?
I'm stefan. I'm a friend of bonnie's.
Her dad told me that she might be here.
She was. Not anymore.
Do you know where she went?
No. But you do.
I'm sorry?
I told her to face down her fear.
And I'm sensing now that you
know exactly why she was scared.
You know what I am.
And yet you offered me your hand,
Which means you wanted me
to see that I can trust you.
Can you?
I ust you'll keep her safe.
You'd better be on your way, then.
I'm not going to invite you in.
I'm sure you understand why.
This aisle is local and state history.
And civil war is one over.
What do you need?
Local. 1860s. Do you work here?
Nope. You want reference. This way.
Uh, home-schooled. I study here
for a moc school environment.
Ah, here we go.
Original settlers, town archives,
founders stuff. It's all here.
So, what's your topi
The town's fear and
hysteria surrounding the war
And how it influenced
certain writers of the time.
You might want to focus that.
The origin of local folklore and myths.
You mean the vampires?
Let's just say that I'm
descended from katherine--
Does that make me part vampire?
Vampires can't procreate.
But we love to try.
No.
If you are related,
it would mean katherine had a child
Before she was turned.
Did stefan think that he
could use me to replace her?
Kinda creepy if you ask me.
Come on, what? You don't like pickl?
What's wrong with you?
How can you even eat?
If technically you're supposed to be--
Dead.
It's not such a bad word.
As long as I keep a healthy
diet of blood in my system,
Our dy functions pretty normally.
This nice act. Is any of it real?
Bree: Here you go, honey.
Thank you.
I'll have one too.
Hmm?
Time out, remember? For 5 minutes?
Yeah, well that 5 minutes
is going to need a beer.
There you go.
You're kidding me, right?
There's no such thing as vampires.
Well, there's not a lot of documentation
But the stories have been
told since the civil war.
My granddad used to tell me all these
creepy stories when I was little.
And he said that his
granddad told them to him.
Yeah. That would be folklore.
Vampires are a metaphor
for the demons of the day.
Which are?
The union soldiers.
I've read the stories myself.
They talk about the enemy,
the demons that attack night.
That sounds like vampires to me.
Allegorical vampires.
Which is what it is.
Creative expression during
a very volatile time.
I mean, a couny at war
doesn't want realism.
They want fantasy.
Thus, vampire fiction.
Man, you're smart.
I gotta give it to you.
When I first saw you, I missed it.
Yeah. I've had a rough go of it lately.
But I'm just now getting
back to my old self.
Well, good luck on the paper.
I gotta get home.
You know, my great grandfather
actually showed me a journal once
Of an ancestor and he had written all
of this creepy stuff about vampires.
It was actually really believable.
Wait. A journal?
Yeah? Why?
Are you sure you have to go?
[cell phone beeps]
Come on, phone!
[cell phone beeping]
Great! Great.
[rumbling]
[screaming]
Bonnie! Get away from me!
It's me. It's stefan.
Stefan.
The ground gave way and I fell.
It's ok. It's ok. Calm down.
Come on, let's get you out of here.
How?
Just close your eyes.
Trust .
You can open your eyes now.
Whoa.
I didn't want to scare you.
How did you know where I was?
Well, your grandmother told
me what you were doing.
I guessed the where.
I heard them.
Down there. Behind the door.
Are they in pain?
In the beginning--yes. But not anymore.
They've been starved to
the point of dessication.
But if they have blood--
That's not going to happen, bonnie.
They can't get out.
Emily saw to that when she
had you destroy the crystal.
You're safe.
Ready...Go!
That's 3.
Do you need a bib?
Sorry I can't unhinge my jaw
like a snake to consume alcohol.
Whatever. All right. Who's next?
Another round, bree.
Honey, you should be on the floor.
I am not even drunk.
My tolerance is, like, way up here.
Bree: All right. Here you go.
Jeremy: So, you have no
idea where the journal is?
Nope. Gramps died.
And all the kids split
his stuff. I can ask.
I just find it weird that our ancestors
kept the same kind of journal.
It's crazy.
Maybe it's based in
some partial reality.
No. It's gotta be a metaphorical.
My ancestor wrote short stories.
So, that's why you're hung
up on the fiction of it all.
No, I'm hung up on fiction of it all
Because I've seen "the lost boys"
And "near dark," like, 50 times.
Are those movies?
Hey. I've never seen them.
Maybe we can have a fright night
And rent a whole bunch
of vampire movies.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Why does tt sound like a no way in hell?
Sorry, I'm blunt.
No, it's--I don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
I just recently got out of something,
It's a little too soon, you know?
Oh please, sure. No worries.
I meant as friends. Yeah.
Look, I really gotta go.
Nice meeting you, jeremy.
[cell phone ringing] yeah!
Hello? Jenna?
Hold on, it's loud in here.
Huh? Yeah. No, I'm good.
Eveything's fine. Hold on.
I can't hear you.
Hello?
[mumbling]
Hey, where's your girl?
Hmm.
She was right back there.
Damon, no.
What t hell?!
No!
Who are you?
That's pfect. You have no idea.
What are you talking aut?
What did he do?
He killed my girlfriend.
What did she do to you,
huh? What did she do to you?!
Nothing.
Elena: I don't understand.
My girlfriend went to visit sfan,
And damokilled her. Got it?
Ugh!
Lexi?
Lexi was your girlfriend?
She told me about you.
She said you were human.
I was.
Lexi turned you?
If you want to be with someone forever,
You have to live forever.
She loved u.
She said, "when it's real,
you can't walk away."
Well, that's a choice you're
not going to have to make.
Don't. Don't, please, don't hurt him--
I'm doing you a favor.
Lexi loved y. And she was good.
That means you're good too.
Be better than him.
Don't do this. I'm begging you!
Please.
Thank you.
It wasn't for you.
Well, now, look who's
returned from battle
Can I talk to your friend for minute?
Thank you.
I appreciate your help, stefan.
You're welcome, sheila.
I wasn't sure you remembered.
October 1969.
I was barely a teenager.
And you were leading what was probably
The only anti-war si
t-in within miles of mystic falls.
Hmm.
You knowwhen you spoke,
people were mesmerized.
I know I was.
Until the cops showed up.
You took a big risk
coming to see me earlier.
Letting me read you,
realize who you were.
It could have gone a
completely different way.
Your familhas a very long
history of keeping my secret.
I knew that I could trust you if you
believed I waworthy of your trust.
Bonnie knows, doesn't she?
Yes.
Please understand,
our loyalty can only extend so far.
This town won't be easy on any
of us if they figure it out.
And I'll protect my own
before anybody else.
I know that.
As long as we're clear
Goodnight, then.
Goodnight, sheila.
We were just leaving,
and I wanted to sagood bye.
Good to see you again, damon.
No ks?
I'm full of vervain.
I put it in everything I drink.
And you're telling me this why?
Lexi was my friend.
How could you?
The tomb can be opened.
You're lying!
Emily's grimoire, her spellbook.
If you know how she closed the tomb
The reversal process will be in
her book. You can open that tomb.
D where is this book?
I--I--
You have no idea.
No. I'm telling you the truth.
And I believe you.
My dear, sweet bree.
That's why I'm almost sorry.
Ugh!
So, why did you bring me with you?
Wellyou're not the worst
company in the world, elena.
You ould give yourself more credit.
Seriously?
You were there in the road.
All damsel in distress-like.
And I knew it would piss off stefan.
And...
U're not the worst company
in the world, elena.
I used to be more fun.
You did ok.
I saved your life.
I know.
And don't you forget it.
[footsteps approaching]
Hi.
You coulhave told me.
I wanted to tell you.
You said no more lies. Only the truth.
I can handle the truth, stefan.
As crazy as it is,
I can handle the fact
that you are a vampire.
D you have a vampire brother.
And that my best friend is a witch.
I can accept the fact that the
world is much more mysterious place
Than I ever thought possible.
But this--this lie, I can't take.
What am I to you?
Who am I to you?
You are not katherine.
You are the opposite
everything that she was.
And when did you figure that out?
Before you kissed me?
Before we slept together?
Before I met you.
What?
The first day of school. We when met.
It wasn't for the first time, elena.
Then when was it?
May 23, 2009.
But that was--
That was the day your parents'
car went off the bridge.
You were the?
Every couple of years
that I come back here
To see zach and see my home.
Last spring, I was out in the woods,
by old wickery bridge.
And I heard the accident. All of it.
I was fast getting there,
but not fast enough.
The car was already submerged.
Your dad was still-
he was still conscious.
I was able to get to him,
But he wouldn't let me help
him until I helped you.
Oh my god.
When I woke up in the hospital,
Nobody could figure out
how I got out of the car.
They said it was a miracle.
I went back for them.
But it was too late.
I couldn't--
I couldn't save them.
When I pulled you out,
I looked at your face.
You looked like katherine.
I couldn't believe the resemblance.
After that, I spent months
making sure th you weren't her.
I watched you. I learned
everythi that I could about you.
And I saw that you were
nothing like katherine.
And I wanted to leave town,
but, elena, I couldn't.
I couldn't leave without knowing you.
I'm so sorry that I didn't tell you.
I wanted to. But you were so sad.
Why do I look like her?
Elena, you've been thrgh so much.
Why do I look like her,
stefan? What are you not telling me?
It didn't make any sense  me.
You were a gilbert. She was a pierce.
But the resemblance was too similar.
And then I learned the truth.
You were adopted, elena.
There you are.
Hey.
All right,ook.
I know I don't know you,
so don't ask me why I did this.
I just, sometimes-- mostly all the time-
I have this need to be right.
So I googled and...
What is it?
Proof. Sort of.
What does this mean?
Well, I only went as far back as 1942,
And found that there's been
a string of animal attacks
Periodically in and around this
town for the past 75 years.
It's consistent.
In '62, 5 boes found.
In '53, 4 people killed.
In '74, 3 people dead.
And there's been 5 this year.
All attacked.
All suffered major blood loss,
as in drained of blood.
How do you know th?
Your birth certificate
from the city records.
It says elena gilbert.
Mystic falls general.
But there's no record of your
mother ever being admitted.
There's no record of her
ever being pregnant.
What else do you know?
For me to go any further, I would've
had to look into the pierce family,
And I couldn do that.
It's too much of a risk.
If seone found out I was
asking about katherine--
Listen to me, it doesn't matter.
You are the woman that I love.
I love you.
I don't set a lot of rules, elena.
Not with you. I trust you
to tell me the truth.
Where were you? Why would
you lie to me about it?
I thought that we were closer than that.
Now is not the time you want
to talk to me about lies.
Don't do that.
Don't turn this back on me.
I didn't do anything.
Ok, question-- am I apted?
I trust you to tell me
the truth too, jenna.
How coulyou not tell me?
I thought we were closer than that.
Elena, didn't-- they asked me not to.
I don't want to hear it!
Lexi: Love you.
I'm going to be late tonight.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net