Somewhere in the Nevada Desert.
Hi, Ted.
No internet
connection available.
Ted... I know you're there.
I'm not online.
How are you doing this?
I know what they did to you.
Look at the needle.
We should meet.
Turn around.
My name is Hana Gitelman.
How the hell did you do that?
Satellite signals.
Wi-Fi, radio waves.
Your computer can download
them and so can I.
So you can, uh,
access the internet
without a computer.
Just pull email
out of your head.
Yes.
And you're radioactive.
Why come to me?
Because they got to me too.
I can find them, Ted.
And you can nuke them.
Previously on Heroes.
Turned on the waterworks,
and they were mine.
- They're getting the suitcase as we speak.
- Where's the bag?
You may fool Ando,
but you do not fool me.
Matt Parkman,
here to protect you, sir.
Sir, we've got to get out of
here right now. This is a setup.
- What? How do you know that?
- I just do.
Now, you absorb all
these abilities you find.
I'm gonna teach you how to
pull 'em out one at a time.
- I don't have to do anything!
- Except fly.
- Hello. Zane Taylor?
- Yes.
You must be Dr.
Suresh. Come on in.
There are others
out there like you.
- And I am going to find them.
- I could go with you.
She had an appointment
with a neurologist.
Your mother's been
having some headaches.
Yeah, she's also been
having some memory loss.
Did you tell them that?
I don't know any Mr. Muggles.
And I don't know you.
Dad?
Dad!
Where's Dad?
He's on one of his
stupid business trips.
There's something
wrong with Mom.
wrong with you.
Mom?
Do you know who this is?
Claire, leave your
brother alone.
You recognize us?
Yes, you are the daughter who is
supposed to be setting the dinner table.
I was standing right
there just a minute ago,
and you had no idea who I was.
Lyle, help your sister with the table.
Honestly, Claire.
Good thing Dad's not home,
'cause he would so drug test you.
It's good you called us, Isaac.
I didn't know who
else to trust.
That man, Peter Petrelli,
is going to be
responsible for all this.
I tried finding him. I kept painting
what I thought were empty spaces.
- And now?
- There, in the water.
Footprints.
So...
Peter's invisible?
That sound so crazy?
Any more than a man who
can paint the future?
Peter absorbs
others' abilities.
Apparently, he's met someone
who we assumed was dead.
- That's the roof of the...
- The Deveaux building.
Look, there's a chance that
Peter might come here first
before we reach him.
What do you expect
me to do with this?
Save the world.
Chapter Sixteen - Unexpected
Hey.
You know what? Let me do that.
I am pregnant, not porcelain.
No, I'm just trying
to be Mr. Helpful.
Try Mr.
Get-the-hell out-of-the-way.
What did you do?
You like it?
I love it.
- I do.
- Yeah?
Matt, we can't afford this.
I mean, we're...
Nah, come on. I got a guy.
He gave it to me
wholesale, so...
I'm so bloated.
You, you look so
beautiful to me.
I'm sorry.
You...
made this beautiful gesture,
and I have to mess it up.
What do you mean?
A man called yesterday.
A Professor Suresh.
He was a geneticist.
He wanted to talk about DNA.
Matt, your DNA.
Did you tell him anything?
I mean, you didn't tell him anything,
did you?
Of  course I didn't
tell him anything.
He found you.
He  knows.
Geneticists.
Who are these people?
Um, before we go in,
I just wanted to say thanks.
For what?
Well, you know,
for bringing me with you.
You  didn't have to do that.
It would have been
a long road alone.
I'm glad for the company.
Well, I believe in fate,
Mohinder, and karma,
and I'm not just saying
that 'cause you're Indian.
I mean,
you really came to my rescue,
and I won't forget that.
It's not completely
altruistic on my part, Zane.
I have a feeling
we're gonna meet up
with a lot of skepticism
from these people.
- You can help.
- I'm ready.
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
Oh.
Rap music.
Can't stand it, but it's the only thing
I've found that cancels out the...
- Can I help you?
- We're looking for Dale Smither.
You found her.
Oh. O-of course.
I'm Mohinder Suresh,
and this is Mr. Taylor.
Zane. Actually, it's just Zane.
I left you several
messages this week.
Yeah, I got 'em.
I believe I can help with
what's happening to you.
I'm sure you have
lots of questions.
Yeah, only one...
- How'd you find me?
- You gave blood 11 years ago.
Signed a consent form
to have a sample used
in a program called the
Human Genome Project.
You dialed the wrong number.
Look, I know what you're
thinking right now,
that you've got
nobody to talk to,
nobody that understands
what you're going through.
But that's not true.
I-I understand.
Yeah?
Damn.
That was my best wrench.
So there really
are others, huh?
Yes. I'm proof of that.
That's why we're here.
I-I...
I thought the headaches at
first were gonna kill me.
I'd lie awake at night thinking
that my head was gonna explode.
A cockroach crawling
across my neighbor's floor
was like a marching band
parading through my house.
I'm sorry.
It must be quite a burden.
A burden?
Hell, no.
This is the best damn thing
that ever happened to me.
Well, now that I've
learned to control it,
I'm like Superman or something.
I can hear rain coming
from 40 miles away.
I can even hear
someone's moods...
The tiniest changes
in a heartbeat.
Yours, for instance.
It's racing kind of fast.
You nervous about something?
Um, no, I'm just excited
to meet somebody like me.
Well, if you've come to try
to take it away from me,
you're gonna have a hell
of a fight on your hands.
I can assure you we
only want to help.
Uh, I'd like to
perform a few tests,
s-some questions,
really, that's all.
Shouldn't take more
than a couple of hours.
I'm kinda backed up today.
We can come back
in the morning.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Ando?
Is that you? I'm locked in!
You're not Ando.
S.R. Gustavson.
State Gaming Commission.
I come in peace.
- What's an Ando?
- Ando is my friend.
I bring him from
Japan on my mission.
- Where's the girl?
- Oh!
Where's the suitcase?
She said her name Hope.
Tell me where they are!
Take me with you.
I must save Ando.
Not a chance.
I work alone, pal.
You take me with you
or she gets away...
pal.
I so miss you, Karen.
I miss your laugh.
But they're gonna pay
for what they did to me.
What they did to us.
I know you're not gonna
like what I gotta do.
So, uh, I came to say good-bye.
- Enough!
- I say when it's enough!
You've got a power to stop me.
What are you waiting for?
I'm trying!
And when you've left New
York a smoking wasteland,
we'll put that on
your tombstone:
"Here lies Peter Petrelli.
He tried."
Dig into that file cabinet of
yours and pull something out!
Fly, stop time,
paint me a pretty picture.
Do... something... unexpected!
Ha ha!
You pushed that away
with your mind.
Which one of your sorry
friends has telekinesis?
None of 'em do.
Right... that guy who was
chasing Claire in Texas.
- He sent some lockers flying at me.
- Texas?
And you pulled that little
trick out in the here and now?
Well, we might just have a chance
at stopping you from going nuclear.
I tried.
Every street I painted,
every building... empty.
I think Peter's left New York.
Why does this seem so familiar?
Oh, now I remember.
You'd get that same
look on your face
when you'd lie to
me about using.
You think I'm lying?
You're right.
I can't willingly throw you
into another man's arms.
- Because you're jealous.
- Because he's dangerous.
Oh, God.
I don't think I should
have this anymore.
No. Keep it. Please.
I would do anything
for you, Simone.
Anything.
Find Peter.
Look, you're nothing but a
Japanese MapQuest for me.
So till we find that girl,
just sit there and shut up.
I bring Ando from
Japan on my mission.
I am responsible for him.
All a partner ever does is either
drag you under or screw you over.
A partner helps by
believing in you.
He keeps you honest.
Uh-huh. Well.
Who  wanted to help the girl?
Grab the suitcase?
Take your car?
Ando.
You take on a partner,
all you get is their
blood on your hands.
Why are we stopping here?
I thought we were going
to your mother's house.
The less questions
you ask, Ando,
the better off
you'll be in life.
Why is that?
That'd be another question.
- Here, I will help you with...
- No, I've got it.
- It's okay...
- No...
What is this?
What did I say about
asking questions?
You know,
I have to admit, Zane,
when you first offered to help,
I was...
- I was cautious.
- In what way?
I don't know you.
You don't know me.
It could have been a disaster.
You... made a difference today.
Thank you.
Here is your key.
When you told that woman Dale
that you could help her,
is that really possible?
It's only theoretical
at this point.
But I am working
on an inhibitor,
a chemical that'll isolate
the genetic mutation
that causes
these abnormalities.
We can offer these people
understanding, control,
or, if needed,
elimination of their ability.
Elimination? You make it
sound like a virus or plague.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to imply...
It's just not all of you exhibit
the same sets of skills you do.
And they can be dangerous.
My father had to
learn that firsthand.
How's that?
He was murdered by
a man named Sylar.
Well, what happened to this...
Sylar?
I'm  not sure.
He just got away with
killing your dad?
I only know he's gone,
locked away.
What does it matter?
Even if I could come face-to-face with
him, what difference would it make?
Justice can never
really be served.
What a shame.
They're out there.
I can feel them...
So innocent,
so unaware of what's happening to them.
We'll find them, Mohinder.
All of them, together.
The two of us.
It's our destiny.
I'm gonna call it a night.
I'll catch you in the morning.
Claire, do we need to talk?
No.
Yes.
Mom, you know how you
sometimes forget things?
Honey, is this about my
trip to the neurologist?
It's just some headaches.
I don't want you to worry.
But they don't know
what's causing it, right?
We are still waiting on
the results from the tests.
What if it's not some thing
that's responsible
for it but someone?
What on earth are
you talking about?
What if you knew a secret,
and they had a way
to brainwash you?
You have been
studying long enough.
Let's curl up in my bed,
piece of pie, glass of milk,
and watch an old
Cary Grant movie.
Mom, I'm serious.
I know this is a little scary,
but Dad's in charge of
talking to the doctors,
and they will come
up with the answers.
Maybe you shouldn't
trust Dad so much.
Now, why would you say that?
What if it gets worse...
and next time that you...
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom, please wake up.
What's this all about anyways?
- What's what?
- The birds.
I mean, you...
you sort of hate
everything, everyone.
Except you treat these
pigeons like they're family.
Charles Darwin bred pigeons
when he was working out
his theory of evolution.
Married up various permutations
to get maximum potential.
What do you mean by that,
maximum potential?
I think he meant you, friend.
But you used to care.
About all this.
Didn't you?
All right, sharing time's over.
Time to get...
- What are you doing?
- Something unexpected.
Claire, this isn't
a great time.
Dad, you have to come home.
Mom fell and she blacked out.
I called 911...
What  happened to her?
I came home and she didn't
even know who I was.
She didn't even
remember Mr. Muggles.
I'm coming home right away.
Claude'll have to wait.
- Matt, where are you?
- Hey, what's up?
The ring.
I took it to get resized,
and the jeweler told me
it was worth $40,000.
Well, that's ridiculous.
And he accused me
of stealing it.
I had to tell him my
husband was a cop
and there has to be some
kind of an explanation.
There is an explanation, right?
The guy that I was
protecting, Malsky...
those were his.
- You have to give them back.
- I can't.
I can't. He's dead.
- Hmm. Uh, I need to sit down.
- See...
Honey, this is why I didn't want
to tell you about this, okay?
- You were gonna get upset...
- You let me keep the ring.
It was stolen property.
What were you thinking?
I don't know what
I was thinking.
- I have no idea.
- You know, Matt, for a guy that can...
read other people's thoughts,
you should spend a little
bit of time on your own.
You know what?
I'm just trying to figure out
how to take care of our family.
I don't have a job, Jan.
And I'm worried
that the baby...
Ever since you told
me about this thing,
this thing that you do,
I have tried to act like
everything's okay, but it's not.
It's stealing and lying.
Matt, you're better than this!
All right.
Fine, I'll take them
down to the precinct.
- Call them right now.
- What?
Call them right now.
Hello?
What?
Where are you right now?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know the place.
- I'll be right there.
- Who was that?
- I, uh, I gotta go out.
- Where?
Matt.
How you feeling?
You knew they were after you.
Who? I don't know
who they were!
You wanted to know why I was
invisible all these years.
It was because of them,
and you've brought the
bastards right to my door!
I just saved your ass!
You've no idea
what you've done.
Your mate, the painter.
He took your girl
up to the roof.
- He must have known we were up there.
- Isaac.
- He's a comic book artist.
- Let's call a spade a shovel, mate.
It had to be Isaac.
They got to him.
You said yourself he
disappeared for a bit, right?
- Yeah, so?
- Well, that's how it works.
At least,
that's how it did in my day.
You drop off the face of
the earth for a few days,
wake up with a memory hole,
a killer headache,
and a souvenir.
Did he have a set of these?
I don't know. What is that?
Those are for the lucky ones.
So what do we do now... hey!
We?
You watch your own back.
I do what I always
do... disappear.
I'm not letting you run again.
We're getting somewhere with all this.
You should have thought of that
before you brought your
baggage to my roof.
- I can't do this on my own.
- Then I guess you go boom.
Have you heard from Peter?
Last time I saw my brother,
he flew out of a window
to get away from me.
I doubt he's going to
come knocking on my door.
- He flew out a window?
- So to speak.
Simone, I've got people looking for him,
people I can trust.
Around the clock.
We'll find him.
But what if you don't?
You need to go public,
call a press conference,
tell everyone about
Peter's condition.
Nobody's gonna believe
somebody can explode and
destroy a city, Simone.
- I can't believe I believe it.
- Let's tell them everything.
Isaac painting the future,
Hiro stopping time.
Even you...
what you all can do is incredible.
It's time people know
what's happening.
The truth.
Simone, look,
I know your heart...
it's in the right place.
You want to help Peter,
and I want to help him too.
But if people knew what
we were capable of,
they would drop a
collective brick.
You think they'll burn
you at the stake?
Yeah, pretty much.
Because that's what I would do.
I'd round us all up,
stick us in a lab on some island
in the middle of the ocean.
Where Peter saw hope,
you see disaster.
I guess I'm voting
for the other guy.
Simone.
Do not take this public.
But you kissed me.
- I thought you liked me.
- Don't remind me.
What will happen to me now?
Damn it!
Hope!
I want my share.
- Ando!
- Hiro!
Ando!
This way hurry!
Hiro. I'm sorry.
I should've listened to you.
No, this is all my fault.
I never should have...
brought you on my mission.
And if you didn't...
I would be at my desk in Tokyo.
I would never know...
what is it to be a hero.
I don't want to die!
Did your powers work?
I had my eyes closed!
Me too.
Her gun must have misfired.
I guess...
Lucky for us!
Look Ando!
Not a scratch on the Versa!
Funny. I didn't hear
your footsteps.
That's because
there weren't any.
That sound.
In your heart.
What is it?
Murder.
Is my mom gonna be okay?
She's stable.
When your dad gets here,
we can discuss options.
Options?
Claire, why don't
you come sit down.
Your mother has a
subdural hemorrhage.
I got a C-minus in biology.
Oh. It's, um...
it's like a bruise
on her brain.
Specifically the area
that controls memory.
Has your mother had any
recent exposure to radiation?
A history of epilepsy?
Claire, if this is a result
of domestic violence...
No. No, it's not like that.
Not really.
Then what's it like?
You won't believe me.
Anything you say will be held
in the strictest confidence.
There's a man...
who works for my dad.
He can make you forget things.
Anything,
just by touching
you with his hands.
I'll talk to your father.
Wait, I'm telling
you the truth!
Hey, I only came here
because you said it was a
matter of life and death.
You can't go blowing
anything else up.
I found out what these are.
They're tracking us.
Like animals!
What the hell's that
supposed to mean?
The truth.
Hey! What's going on? Ted?
She's... she's a friend,
okay, like us.
She's the one who put
me onto the scratches.
It comes from a
pneumatic needle.
It injects a radioisotope for
tracking viruses in Africa.
That's what we are to them,
a-a virus. A plague.
Who's them?
A shipment of needles went to
Primatech Paper in Odessa, Texas.
The tracking slip went
to a man named Bennet.
- Sound familiar?
- I've already been down this road.
Trust me, it's a dead end.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why would a paper company need
pneumatic needles with a radioisotope?
I had my blood tested.
- It's in me, that isotope.
- Ted, you're radioactive by nature.
How much you wanna
bet it's in you too?
No, it's insane. No!
I want to put this
whole thing behind me.
My wife and I have a baby coming,
my family needs me.
If you got a family,
that means you got something to protect.
There is no putting this
whole thing behind you.
We gotta find out what they
did and make them fix it!
If they can track us
like you say they can,
- he'll know we're coming.
- Good.
I can get us through
any wall they got.
I need you to get
inside his head.
He can't lie to us
if you're there.
We'll find out the truth.
Look, I cannot do this...
without you.
If we can save ourselves,
we could help others.
We could be heroes!
Dad.
I've convinced the doctor to let
us take her home in the morning.
- She'll be okay.
- No thanks to you.
Shut up, Claire.
Claire, can I talk
to you outside?
Please?
The doctor told me you
had an interesting theory
- about your mom's condition.
- It's not a theory.
You did this to her.
You erased her mind.
Claire, that's ridiculous.
You tried to erase mine.
I don't know where you're
getting these ideas.
Stop. Stop it! Stop lying!
After what you did to Mom,
isn't that enough?
What you know is dangerous.
If the wrong people find
out about what you can do...
- Like the man who killed Jackie?
- Exactly.
Why?
Why did you do this to Mom?
A few days ago,
that man broke into our house...
looking for you.
He found your mother instead.
So I made her forget.
Your mother is a gentle soul.
And people like her shouldn't have
to know about people like him.
And maybe people like you.
I never meant for
her to get sick.
I only wanted to
protect my family.
Claire bear, I promise...
I promise this will
never happen again.
No!
You don't just get
to say you're sorry
and make everything go away.
Zane, are you all right?
Yeah, it's just, uh,
it's just a headache.
Okay. Sit tight. I'll be back.
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hey, maybe we should just
come back, Mohinder.
Dale?
Mohinder, what's the matter?
- What are you doing?
- Dialing 911.
Do you think that's
a good idea?
What are you talking about?
She was murdered.
And what were we doing here?
What do you mean? We found her.
How? Why? I mean, l-look at us.
Where did we come from?
How did we get here?
Can we explain any of this
without looking completely insane?
The top of her
head was removed.
It was Sylar.
I don't... I mean, how?
Sylar. Okay,
we have to warn them.
Everyone on the list.
He's after them.
We'll, uh, we'll leave now
and we'll call the police
anonymously from the road.
Zane, are you okay?
Hiro, my arm still
hurts a little.
You should drive.
No, you always drive.
Take the Versa back to
the rental car place.
What are you doing?
What I should've
done weeks ago.
Go home, Ando.
Why are you doing this?
I said I was sorry
about the girl.
This isn't about you.
It's about me.
I made a mistake by
bringing you along.
I have to do this alone.
But you can't! It's destiny!
The comic-book...
we're going to save the world!
Life isn't a comic book.
Too many people have
died since we began.
I don't know what I would do...
if I lost you too.
Hiro, please.
Hiro!
Hey, young fella.
All by yourself?
Yes, just me.
Lyle.
Claire.
We'll get through this.
Your mom needs us. Lyle too.
I don't even know if I'll
remember any of this tomorrow.
All I want to do is run away,
but I can't.
Somebody has to protect
this family from you.
Lyle, take your mother.
- Get out of the house right now.
- Dad?
I'm sure you have
a lot of questions.
We all do.
- Why'd you do it, Isaac?
- How'd you get in here?
What'd they give you,
money? Drugs?
- What's a Judas get these days?
- I was trying to stop you.
You're dangerous.
You said it yourself.
Without them to help,
you'll become that.
I had help.
I was learning to control it.
- You scared my only chance of hope!
- Stop it!
What are these marks, huh?
What do they mean?
They're nothing.
They mean nothing.
Don't lie to me!
This is why you
sent them after me.
Jealousy?
With me out of the way,
you'd have Simone
all to yourself.
You stole her away from me!
But I did it to save New York,
to stop the bomb.
I can do it right now.
With just one bullet,
I can be a hero.
You're not a hero, Isaac.
You're a junkie.
You couldn't even
save yourself.
That's why she left you, Isaac.
It had nothing...
to do... with me!
Show yourself!
Simone!
Simone. Simone.
No. No.
Thanks to Raceman for the Transcript
Subtitles Made By The Bloc Team
Synchronised By Tagne
For www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net