Previously on Heroes.
Five strangers
accross the globe
began to discover they have
extraordinary abilities.
From the cheerleader who
realized she's invincible.
I have busted every
bone in my body.
And I don't have
a scratch on me!
To the office worker who
can bend space and time.
These strangers are discovering
they're meant for
something more.
Do you ever get the
feeling like you were meant
to do something extraordinary?
And as a son seeks the truth by
finishing his father's work...
I spoke to him 2 days ago.
He was this close to
finding the 1st of them.
He's forced to run from a
man surrounded in mystery.
He left everything
behind but his computer.
A man who's more conencted
than anyone imagine.
- Hi, daddy.
- Hey, baby.
And now Heroes continues.
Chapter Two
Don't Look Back.
We all imagine ourselves
the agents of our destiny,
capable of determining
our own fate.
But have we truly any
choice in when we rise?
Or when we fall?
Or does a force larger than
ourselves bid us our direction?
Is it evolution that
takes us by the hand?
Does science point our way?
Or is it God who intervenes,
keeping us safe?
- Whoa, whoa, easy, buddy.
- Where am I?
You're in a hospital.
What happened?
- You don't remember?
- No.
You jumped, Pete.
- Jumped?
- Yeah.
Off the roof of a
15-story building.
You tried to kill yourself.
You were a little wound up yesterday.
But I thought you
were just being you.
What are you talking about?
I didn't...
I didn't try to kill myself.
You were in the alley below.
I jumped, and...
then you...
- You flew.
- I what?
You flew up and you caught me.
You jumped... Peter.
25 feet to a fire escape.
I climbed up and carried you down.
That's what happened.
The rest is just crazy talk.
You understand?
Dad... you mind if I talk
to you about something?
- You pregnant?
- What? No.
- You doing drugs?
- Dad!
Actually... I already
know what it's about.
You do?
It's about wanting to
know who you really are.
Your mother told me that you've been
asking about your birth parents.
Well, I think it's
time that I knew.
Well, I have a few
questions first.
Not the least of
which is why now?
I'm just wondering, that's all.
You know, what they're like,
what they can do.
- What they can do?
- Yeah, like hobbies and...
skills.
You know, I don't...
mean this to be condescending.
Even though you're gonna
say I'm being condescending.
But I really do believe that
this is an adult decision.
You're right.
That is condescending.
Claire, there are
gonna be issues.
You're going to have issues.
They're going to have issues.
It's very complex, emotionally.
- Yeah, well, so am I.
- Well, exactly.
Look, here's my advice,
if you'll indulge me. Just...
keep things light and fun as long
as you can. Like cheerleading.
Being a cheerleader is hard work.
Hard, treacherous work.
- Of course it is, sweetheart.
- I don't wanna be late.
Hey...
I just don't want you to be in
such a hurry to grow up, okay?
Trust me.
I actually know a few things.
Who are you?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Sorry, sorry! Easy, easy.
Your super let us in.
We're doing the whole building today.
I just got done with the lady
with the dog and the cough.
Almost done here.
Uh, listen, it looks like some
cockroaches might have infested
your, uh,
floorboards.
Who are you?!
What did you do to my father?
Let's take a little breather,
huh, professor?
I suppose the cockroaches
are the least of my problems.
Yeah, no argument there.
Did you kill my father?
I think we're done here,
don't you?
So I'll tell you what.
Have a really great day.
Hey, look,
I'm just the exterminator.
This guy came in and
pulled a gun on me.
- He is not an exterminator.
- He's paranoid.
I was just in there spraying
bugs in his apartment.
He came in and freaked out.
If you're the exterminator,
why do you have a gun holster?
- Thanks for coming to my rescue.
- You're welcome.
Mohinder  Suresh.
The professor's son.
Yatai!
Hello, New York!
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I love New York!
Hello!
Whassup?
Britney Spears.
Go, Yankees!
Hey! Pal! This isn't a library.
No pay, no read.
Hey,  get back here!
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
- Simone--
- Shh, you had a hard night.
I saw it.
There was a... bright light.
Like an explosion.
It wiped out the whole city.
Like Hiroshima--
Shh, shh, shh, it's okay.
It was all a dream.
- No... I don't think so.
Yes.
I shot up last night. I had to.
I painted what I saw.
Is it there? Do you see it?
Yes, I see it!
But you need to rest.
- We have to warn them.
- Uh! Warn who?
F.B.I., Homeland Security.
We need to tell someone.
Isaac, you can't paint the future.
No one will believe you.
- I'd hoped you would.
- None of it is real.
What is real is,
you got a drug problem.
You overdosed on heroin last night.
You're lucky to be alive.
You know,
I'm watching my father die.
And I can't watch you die too.
So you need to make a choice.
Me or this.
It's not about
having big hands.
Most guy's hands are too
rough to pick out the details.
Mine are sensitive.
Feel how soft they are.
Wow.
But you've got dainty hands.
My mom says my hands
are very dainty.
Maybe I should try out
for the football team.
Claire, may I borrow your
ears just for a minute?
- Why?
- Hey, Zach!
Is it true you got an erection
in the boys' locker room?
- It's really urgent--
- Not now. Not now.
Claire, Jackie.
The sheriff and some firemen would
like to have a word with you two.
Okay.
Hi, this is Niki.
Leave me a message.
Mom...are you there?
When are you coming to get me?
I hate it here.
You said you'd be back soon.
Just come pick me up, okay?
Honey, I'm so sorry.
I'm on my way.
Baby, I'm only five
minutes away, okay?
You know I love you.
Come on.
Yeah.
That's the way I like it.
Go ahead. Come on.
What's the problem, baby?
Things  just started
getting good here.
I said what's the problem?
Screw you.
Hello?
Mom... where have you been?
I called you, like, four hours ago.
- What? Four hours?
- Yeah.
I'll be right there, baby.
What is the matter with you,
making him wait like that?
I'm sorry.
Hon, two seconds.
Okay. What the hell
is going on, Niki?
Something terrible
has happened.
What? What is it?
Those guys that you said that Linderman
would send to get his money back...
- Yeah?
- Well, he did.
And now they're dead.
On the floor of my garage.
What? How?
That's just it. I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
I mean I don't know.
I just--
I woke up, and they were dead and...
I think that I might...
Sometimes I look
in the mirror...
and I'm not sure it's
me that I'm seeing.
Maybe it was DL, you know?
He's trying to protect you because
he still loves you and Micah.
DL wouldn't risk coming back.
The cops are after him.
And once Linderman
finds out they're dead,
it's not gonna matter who killed them.
He's gonna come after me.
Then you need to listen to me.
Niki, you have to call the police.
No, I gotta cover my tracks.
And then I gotta run.
I gotta go.
Why would anybody wanna
tap Papa Saresh's phone?
Papa Saresh?
Yeah, he told me to call him that after
I butchered his name a couple times.
I don't know why someone
would want to tap his phone.
Back in Madras,
I found a man in his apartment
stealing his research,
and now this.
Why don't you just ask your dad?
He must have some idea who it is.
My father died four days ago.
What?
I'm sorry, I...
You didn't know?
He was murdered in his cab.
Oh, my God. How awful.
You were close?
Yeah... I mean,
I hate cooking for one.
So I used to make extra and
bring it over, and we would...
eat together, and he'd tell me
about his theories and the map.
We were friends.
Well... then you were
closer to him than I was.
I'm happy to hear he
had someone to talk to.
I'll get you some water.
I had no idea anything
was wrong. I...
I knocked on the door a couple of times.
I just...
I thought he was out,
and we were missing each other.
I had this book I
wanted to show him.
What book?
Darwin's Origin of Species.
Thank you.
It's a true first edition.
I work at this
antique book store,
and I found a copy,
and I just...
thought he'd get a kick
out of reading it.
Well, he most definitely would
have gotten a kick out of it.
That's very thoughtful.
You know,
he told me he was being watched.
I thought that he
was just eccentric.
I like that you didn't
use the word "paranoid."
Do you think that
they're watching you now?
They could have killed me,
if that's what they wanted.
For the time being, it seems I'm
more important to them alive.
You said that he talked to you
about his theories and the map.
I need you to tell me
everything he said to you.
Everything you
remember. Everything.
Girls! This isn't a...
criminal investigation.
Nobody here is in any kind of trouble.
Quite the contrary.
There just happens to
be a very grateful man
lying in the hospital who'd
like to thank one of you for...
saving his life yesterday.
I've never seen anyone so
reluctant to be called a hero.
You're sure it was one
of our cheerleaders?
The uniform said
Union Wells High.
I'd  have to say it was...
her on the end.
That's Claire Bennett.
Claire...
where'd you go yesterday
after cheerleading practice?
I, uh...
It wasn't her. It was me.
I was taking a shortcut
home from school, and...
I saw the wreckage of the train...
wreck. And...
I just had to help.
Why didn't you say something?
I guess I didn't want all the attention,
you know?
That's not why I did it.
Well, on behalf of the
Odessa Fire Department,
I'd like to congratulate you
as an honorary firefighter.
- How is he?
- Who?
The man Jackie pulled
out of the train.
He's got some pretty bad burns.
Smoke damage to his lungs, but...
he's alive.
Happy to be so.
Thanks to Jackie.
Claire!
I'm glad I finally got you alone.
Look, we have to talk.
Did you hear they asked Jackie
to be the Grand Marshall
of the Pioneer Day Parade?
They're gonna put her on
the top of the fire truck.
They should put her
under the fire truck.
It's about the videotape.
- What?
- The videotape!
The  tape where you're, like,
killing yourself like 20 times.
Oh, yeah, that.
Can we just keep it under wraps?
That's what I'm
trying to tell you.
It was in my backpack,
and now it's not.
- What?
- It's gone.
What do you mean, it's gone?
Oh, my God! Claire!
I'm so sorry. Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm okay. I'm all right.
Yeah. You just
caught me off guard.
I thought I heard
something snap.
Nope. I'm okay!
I'm fine! I'm okay.
Yeah, not a scratch on me.
Guess you're not so
dainty after all.
I'm dainty enough.
We have got to find that tape.
Whoo!
What if I don't want
to go on vacation?
You don't have a choice.
You have to.
Why are we doing this, Mom?
Why won't you just tell
me what's going on?
I wish that I could, baby.
But you are just gonna
have to trust me, okay?
Now go in and pack
up your stuff.
I have to take care of
something in the garage.
Mom... What happened
to our house?
Mikey, you're just gonna
have to trust me, okay?
Now go in and grab
some stuff. Go.
In the trunk. Follow the map.
Help me understand what you
were doing on that roof.
I can't. Not yet. But I will.
You just have to trust me.
There's something you need to
know about your father's death.
He committed suicide.
What?
I found him on the
floor of the bathroom.
- You said he had a heart attack.
- I lied.
For his reputation,
his heart was fine.
But he'd had two
others before that.
Well, I lied about those too.
Suicide attempts, both of them.
He finally got what he wanted.
When he was 23, he was diagnosed
with major depressive disorder.
He couldn't help it.
It was just who he was.
Why didn't I know about
any of this before?
Your father and I decided
not to tell you since the
disorder can have a genetic link,
and you were always so sensitive.
We didn't want you
to worry about it.
But you're telling me now.
It can start with
delusions of grandeur.
Thinking you're invincible
or indestructible.
They are irrational thoughts
that then turn suicidal.
It's time you took a
hard look at your life.
And if there are changes to be made,
I want to be here to help you.
Because there's something
else I never told you.
Come here.
You were always my favorite.
I cannot lose you.
Mr. Isaac Mendez?
Hello?
Mr. Isaac?
Mr.  Isaac?
Freeze! Drop your weapon.
Get your damn hands up.
Serial killer strikes
in the middle of L.A.,
abducts a little
girl and here I am.
100 feet away.
Might as well be in Siberia.
That's all right.
They don't pay us enough
to be where the action is.
What are you gonna do, anyway?
What do you mean?
I just wanna help.
You wanna help?
Help me get more tape.
What do you think--
C.I.A. or F.B.I.?
Nah, she's dressed
too nice for F.B.I.
I saw the test scores
got posted this morning.
Don't worry about it, man.
Not everybody's a test taker.
Please don't hurt me.
You know, we don't have any
idea what happened in here.
- I've got a theory.
- You always do.
This is Barstow all over again.
- It's Sylar.
- There isn't a Sylar.
Last words of a dying victim.
It didn't mean anything.
And look at her. Must have taken
three guys to lift her up that high.
- What about the daughter?
- No sign.
We checked the house and surrounding,
issued an Amber Alert.
You've seen what
happened to the father.
Frozen solid, skull sawed off.
We need to find out how.
The little girl's the priority.
You are not supposed
to be in here.
It's okay.
It's okay. You're safe now.
Look, I'm a cop.
I'm one of the good guys, okay?
He hurt my mom and dad.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm not gonna let
anybody hurt you.
No, no, no.
Come on, take my hand.
It's okay, come on. It's okay.
Come on.
For years, he'd been working
on a mathematical theorem
using human genomes and
DNA migration patterns.
He thought he could find a
way to identify these people,
the ones who were special.
I never believed it was possible.
We fought about it constantly.
It's the reason we grew apart.
You've reached Chandra Saresh.
Please leave a message.
He's got messages.
Chandra, this is Emi.
You forgot to turn in your
trip sheet for last week.
Where is your head, man?
- Oh, my God, Mohinder.
- Yes?
No... the other Mohinder.
The lizard.
He's gotta be around
here somewhere.
Hi, I'm Nathan Petrelli.
It would be an honor to represent
New York's 14th district.
When the time comes,
vote Petrelli.
Hello, Chandra.
Why won't you talk to me?
You can't leave me like this.
Hello, Mr. Sylar.
I asked you not to call here anymore.
The hunger, it's--
I can't control it.
I don't want to.
You made me this way.
I made you a murderer?
You helped me to
discover my potential.
You wanted to see what I
could do as much as I did.
And now you want it to stop.
It's over. Goodbye.
I found a tape of a conversation my
father had with a man named Sylar.
A man he believed
was Patient Zero.
Come here, you.
Mohinder, this is Mohinder.
You wanna give him a kiss?
What is it?
It's a portable hard drive.
My God, he did it.
He actually came up with
a way to find them.
You wondered why someone
would want to kill my father.
The reason for his death.
It's this!
I'm going to finish
what he started.
Hey, Parkman.
How the hell did you know that
little girl was in there?
I don't know.
I don't know, I just--
I heard her whispering, and, um...
House full of cops, but you're outside,
and you just heard her whisper?
I can't explain it. It was...
I thought everybody could hear her.
You guys couldn't hear her?
You got someplace better to be?
It's my wife. I'm, uh...
I'm meeting her at a...
a therapy session.
Couples counseling.
We're having some
problems at home.
This guy's
worthless. Worthless...
Cut him loose. He got lucky.
Not yet, Parkman.
Your captain says you've taken the
exam to advance to detective 3 times?
Right.
You really think you're
detective material?
Yes, ma'am, I do.
So how does it make you feel?
Flunking out so many times.
I don't know. Embarrassed, I guess.
A little angry.
- A little angry?
- Yeah.
Angry enough to do
something about it?
Maybe set yourself up
to look like a hero?
Wait, what,
you think I killed these people?
I didn't kill these people.
Sylar did.
How did you know that name?
Six people assigned to this
case know the name of Sylar.
How the hell did you know that?
I heard it.
From you.
Like you heard
the girl whisper.
Yeah.
Then hear this one.
You're under arrest.
What? Ow!
- Claire Bear!
- Hi, Dad.
Hey. How was school?
Very school-like. How was work?
Very work-like.
Listen, I, um...
I made a couple of calls today.
I spoke to a very nice woman
at the adoption agency.
And she said they were going
to try to get in touch...
with your birth parents.
And, uh...
and request a meeting.
I thought that was
an adult decision.
You seemed pretty adult
this morning when you told
me you wanted to do it.
Thanks.
She said it was a
lengthy process.
And it could take weeks.
I'm hoping... years.
That way, you'll be my little
girl for a while longer.
I'm not done protecting
you from the world.
You're my dad.
You'll never not be my dad.
I promise I'll...
be your little girl
for as long as I can.
But you can't
protect me forever.
I know.
And it breaks my heart.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, sweetheart.
Go get ready for dinner.
This is Claire Bennett.
And that was
attempt number six.
It really does break my heart.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Did you know about
Dad's depression?
Yeah.
Why didn't you ever tell me?
Because everyone's entitled
to their secrets, Peter.
I was so sure when it happened.
Now it turns out I'm just...
going crazy.
Look, hey...
We've been through this before.
We've played this game, okay?
Let's just... let's just go.
Tell me what happened, Nathan.
When I jumped.
Tell me you flew.
I wanna hear you
say that you flew.
Tell me, or I'll jump again.
Hey, good luck on
your campaign...
when I'm splattered all
over the ground below.
All right.
You want the truth?
Yeah.
We both flew. Pete...
I caught you, and I lost control.
You're too heavy.
We both started falling to the ground.
And just before we--
Just before we hit,
you flew. You.
Are you lying to me?
You are. You're trying to tell
me what you think I wanna hear.
You're lying to me again!
Did you see that?
Did you see that? I flew?
Yeah, I know.
You're one sick son of a bitch,
you know that?
Very sorry.
I not speak much English.
What I wanna know is what did
you do with the man's brain?
You flush it down the toilet,
you eat it, what?
We got a live one here.
No English, no passport,
no American money, no I.D.
Except for this here.
"An honorary member of the
Merry Marvel Marching Society."
Let's start by asking him
how he got to New York.
He says he teleported
himself here.
Teleported? What
the hell is that?
Like Star Trek.
He says he can bend the
space-time continuum.
Funny, I've seen
all the Star Treks.
I don't remember
you from the show.
How long ago did he do this?
- Yesterday.
If you let me make a pone call
my English speaking friend
will clear everything up.
Hiro?
New York! Teleport--
Your friend says he
was with you yesterday.
- Yesterday?
- That's not correct?
I have not seen Hiro
Nakamura in five weeks.
We look for him everywhere.
His buddy hasn't seen
him for five weeks.
Your friend says
he hasn't seen you
in five weeks.
- October 2?
- October 2? No, pal.
Today.
November 8th.
November? No... October.
For all his bluster,
it is the sad province of Man that
he cannot choose his triumph.
He can only choose how he will stand
when the call of destiny comes.
Hoping that he'll have
the courage to answer.
www.tvsubtitles.net