Previously on Heroes...
My dad lied to me
about my entire life.
My biological parents.
My ability.
You can't just hide
things like that.
A 21-year-old woman was
killed in the explosion.
Also killed in the fire was
her 18-month-old daughter.
Hi, I'm looking for someone
related to Meredith Gordon.
- This is her.
- Mom?
Where are you taking us?
Tell your boss I'm on
very important mission.
I work for someone...
who has true power.
And wants you to stop.
Father?
It can take years to integrate
a multiple personality,
but if you let me,
I can help you.
What I am, you can't fix.
Who are you?
How can you see me?
I don't know,
I can just do what you can do.
I'm the Invisible Man.
I'm Claude Rains.
Now get away from me.
I found you.
I need you to help me.
This entire city is in danger.
You seem pretty sure about that
pending apocalypse of yours.
How many people have
you taught before me?
If he crashes,
you bring him back.
Again and again.
He's dead.
Well, that's less than ideal.
I don't see how petty theft
is part of my training.
There's a lot you don't see.
You've no idea how to use
these gifts of yours properly.
- Yeah, and you do?
- No, I...
Right now,
your abilities only show up as a reflex.
Autonomic, like swallowing.
That's a dog's trick.
Making it a conscious choice,
using it,
that's what makes
you more than poodle.
Is insulting me really gonna
help me learn how to do that?
Listen, you're the one who's
a bomb set to blow up me
and everyone in this city unless
I can get you housebroken.
That's right,
now he's listening.
Now, you absorb all these
abilities you find, yeah?
You're invisible with me,
you've flown,
you've read some minds.
Yeah, put me in a
coma for two weeks.
Your body doesn't know
what to do with them all.
It's gotten jumbled,
like file cards
knocking around a shoebox.
Except with you,
the cards are dowsed in plutonium,
piling up to a critical mass.
Now, I'm gonna teach you how to
pull 'em out, one at a time.
You think that's possible?
I hope so.
Next time you shut down,
it might not be just a coma.
Might be the day you melt down.
- So then, let's get to today's lesson.
- All right,
let's start by seeing if
you can hold on to one
of your powers without your
benefactors hanging around.
You think I can do that alone?
We're about to find out.
Remember to breathe.
Hey!
Chapter Fourteen - Distractions
God, it sounds like a
bomb is about to go off.
I know it's hard.
Just focus on the mirror
and try to relax.
I can't relax.
- You're trying to bring her out.
- Jessica...
I told you.
She is dangerous.
- She could hurt you.
- Tell me.
Those cuffs could keep an
elephant in that chair.
And just 'cause I'm a shrink,
don't think I don't know
how to use that Taser.
I thought that the goal
was to get rid of her.
The goal here
is to bring your two halves
to a healthy middle.
To have a unified
and whole you.
Not two aspects at war.
How do we do this?
Like I said,
you focus on the reflection.
And breathe.
Come on.
Feel free to let
your mind wander.
We used to have a
piano in our home.
You played?
Chopsticks, barely.
- My sister...
- Jessica.
She played beautifully.
I used to...
play with her sheet music.
I didn't... know what it was.
It was just... dots and lines.
I would...
get out my crayons
and connect the dots.
Jessica used to say...
that I could turn
Mozart into a monkey.
- I sure did.
- Jessica.
You  should have listened
to the little mouse.
How's Claire?
That was for the haircut.
You shouldn't have
built such a good cage.
You go anywhere near her...
No!
Noooo!
You didn't just used
your key this time.
I shouldn't have them.
Not anymore.
You started painting since
you got back from rehab.
Can I see 'em?
That's  not done yet!
Oh, God.
That's the roof of my
father's building.
We had a lot of good
memories up there.
Is that how you remember
our relationship?
With all of New York destroyed?
What are you
looking for, Simone?
It's Peter. He's still missing.
I'm running out of
places to look.
You finally believe I
can paint the future,
and you want to use it to
find your new boyfriend.
I don't wanna be asking
you this either.
- Can you?
- I have been.
Except it's not working.
Every time I try to paint
where Peter is, I get nothing.
You've been trying
to find him... why?
I know what he can do.
He's the one that's gonna
turn New York into this.
I'm not gonna let him.
- How do you know so much about him?
- Because I painted it.
I care about you, Simone,
more than I knew
how to say when...
when it would have
made a difference.
But right now,
I don't care if you hate me.
I just want you safe.
Stay away from Peter.
Just...
tell me you'll look for him.
I'll try.
Yeah.
Simone...
Keep the key.
The manatee is on the
brink of extinction.
There's one at the
aquarium in Lubbock,
and the marine biologist said
we could stop by any time.
You're asking my
permission to skip school?
No, if I wanted to skip school,
I'd check into home room and then
sneak out Ms. Roberts' window.
But you've always stressed honesty,
so I'm being honest.
The manatee's a very
noble creature.
Is your car in working
order, Zachary?
- Just had the oil changed.
- Any tickets?
Just parking.
- You'll be home for dinner.
- Yes.
That's not a question.
I'm making fajitas.
Zach, you're
welcome to join us.
Let's go. Come on.
We'll wait 15 minutes,
and then head out.
-  Do you have the directions to Kermit?
- Uh, yeah.
Look, what if your
mom wants proof?
About the aquarium.
- Where did you get these?
- Motel 6 lobby and my color printer.
No one can know we're
going to see my real mom.
We have to be perfect.
Your father looks angry.
My father always looks angry.
But your sister looks hot.
For this you leave your job,
take an unauthorized vacation.
Gorge yourself on
hamburgers and waffles.
Waffles are very good.
You would like them.
No, Hiro. I would not.
No more distractions.
You will come home.
And you will get back to work.
Father, I...
I am on an important mission.
You are only on a plane home.
You will return to
Yamagato Industries.
THAT is what is important.
My job was meaningless.
I worked in a cubicle!
I only put you at the bottom so
you would reach for the top.
Perhaps I was too strict.
When you return I will make you
an Executive Vice President.
On your way to taking
my place as CEO.
You are my only son, Hiro.
This is your destiny.
Father.
I believe I have...
a different destiny.
And what is that?
It's... complicated.
I have to bring that painting
to a man in Las Vegas...
so I can steal Takezo
Kensei's sword...
then use my power to stop a
bomb from blowing up New York!
Kensei?
From those stories I read you?
If only I had the sword I
could show you what I can do.
Do you want to see what
I think of your destiny?
We're going home.
Get a doctor!
Oh... wait. What happened?
No! No! No!
I tried to tell her.
- Take me back to my cell!
- Love to!
Thanks for almost
getting me arrested.
A little more focus, you'd have
had some cash and fresh lipstick.
I never said it'd be easy.
In fact,
I think I said repeatedly it'd be crap.
You been doing
this for 15 years.
Cut me a little slack on trying
to do it for five minutes.
You'll learn.
We just gotta find
what's holding you back.
The cops have my
name and address.
I'm pretty sure Nathan's
gonna kill me first anyway.
You worry a lot about your people,
don't you?
Your friends, your mother,
your brother.
No wonder your
head's all clogged.
You're still sunk under.
- Under what?
- Your attachments.
All these people who
feed you biscuits,
pat your head, and tell you
you're not fit for the outdoors.
You still see yourself through
their eyes, is that it?
- No, I don't.
- Right, well,
I'll bet you 20 bucks your dad
didn't make much of you either.
Ha! God, you're easy.
We've gotta get these
people out of your head.
Do you understand?
These people are my family.
I can't just cut 'em out.
Peter can't use his powers
without someone holding his hands.
How can you not punch that
face every time you see it?
- He's not like that.
- He is, trust me.
- You don't know him.
- I don't need to.
I spend a lot of time moving around
people's homes, their bedrooms.
You get to know people if you see
them when they think they're alone.
You see them for
what they truly are:
selfish, deceitful, and gassy.
So what is that,
your big truth about the world?
Sooner you learn it,
sooner we get that collar off your neck.
People suck, friend.
Every last one of them.
Never forget that.
Not all of them.
Oh, right. There's a girl.
She's not like
the rest of them.
Everyone's  like the rest.
That's why they're the rest.
Fine, let's go and see
what your girl's up to.
Then maybe we can
clear your head.
Wait, you wanna... spy on her?
Look, you can follow
her all you want.
I'm telling you,
she's not like that.
Well, then,
no harm in taking a look.
This is bad.
What will we do?
Did you put on cologne?
Please, Father,
let me speak with him.
Oh, Kimiko.
You have brought shame to our family,
little brother.
That was not my intention.
Father doesn't need me.
You're the one he trusts.
He thinks I'm weird.
Father is too proud
to tell you...
there is trouble at Yamagato.
And now the
stockholders are saying
if Father can't
manage is own son...
how can he manage his business?
You are his only son.
His heir. You must come home.
How can I?
I have a mission.
You are so busy pretending
to save the world.
What about saving your family?
Maybe you should think about it.
Your powers are gone.
You have no way to get your sword.
Your family needs you.
B ut...
I was a hero.
Listen to Kimiko.
She's the smart one.
Yes, she is!
This is it.
Number 36.
Nice pinwheel collection.
You know,
I always imagined my
parents would live in a...
penthouse in New York City.
Not some trailer
park in Kermit.
So she lives in a trailer.
Maybe she likes the open road.
Just not what I imagined.
Stop imagining.
She's right there.
What am I supposed to say?
"Hi, I'm your daughter,
and I can regrow my kidney"?
I mean, what if she's got
burns and scars from the fire?
She's supposed to
be dead, right?
So are you, remember?
You already got that in common.
Hey... where are you going?
I'm getting rid of
your exit strategy.
You'll be fine.
I'll be back in
time for fajitas.
Claire?
Hi, little Fluffy.
Claire home from school yet?
No?
We'll just wait.
Now, what's your name?
Mr. Muggles?
Where are you, baby?
Mama's home!
Of course.
Let's go say hi.
I-I'm sorry.
Who are you?
I just came from the
paper factory, ma'am.
I'm just makin' a delivery
for your husband.
And I saw...
this little guy...
in the street.
Now, somebody must have
left the back door open.
Oh, I hope you don't mind.
I took the liberty.
Well, aren't you sweet?
And he was just out
there in the yard?
Oh... just chewin'
on a sprinkler head.
Mm! Who left those doors open,
Mr. Muggles?
Claire or Lyle?
You tell me,
so I can tan their ass.
Well, thanks for
invitin' me in.
I always wanted to, uh,
see where Mr. Bennett lived.
It is so funny how all of y'all
call him Mr. Bennett over there.
I've always just
known him as...
Stop that, you. No more shoes.
He just discovered shoelaces.
Can't get enough.
That's funny, I never really imagined
him as much of a dog person.
I  guess he just looms a little
larger when he's drillin' you.
He mostly talks about Claire.
I was hopin' to
meet her, actually.
I've heard so much about her.
Well, she has promised
to be home for dinner.
Which means a half
an hour late.
My son is at a Tai Kwon
Do sleepover tonight.
That means an extra plate.
Why don't you stay for dinner?
Least I can offer my new hero.
Are you sure?
It's not too much trouble?
I will call my husband and
tell him to expect you.
- What did you say your name was again, Mister...
- Sylar.
Oh, I don't think you'll reach
him at the office, though.
Last I saw,
he was just swamped.
I'm staring. I'm sorry.
I mean, you have to understand.
I never thought
this would happen.
You sitting inches
away from me.
You're so beautiful.
Thank you.
You a good student?
Um, I'm okay.
- Lousy at math.
- No help from me there.
Well, I'll bet you're
all kinds of popular.
I was homecoming queen.
Kind of.
Damn, I missed so much.
If I'd known you were
out there, but...
You must think something awful.
I mean, I was so sure that
nothing could have
survived that fire.
It was a miracle
that I did, and...
God, when I saw that roof, I...
Don't question the
miracle, right?
Here.
It's horchata.
I learned a secret recipe in Mexico.
It's sweet.
- You lived in Mexico?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, I moved around a lot.
After I lost you, I sort of
started running.
I never really stopped.
And I only came back to
Kermit a couple months ago.
I spent some time
in Cuernavaca.
And La Paz.
You've never been.
Well...
Sorry.
It's my mom.
Hi!
Yeah, we're at the
aquarium right now.
They just let Zach
feed him turtle grass.
We're practically on our way.
We'll be home in,
like, an hour.
No, I won't let him speed.
Okay. Bye.
She doesn't know you're here.
She doesn't really understand
what's going on with me right now.
Neither of my parents do.
Well, I'll pretend I understand
why you're sneaking around.
All girls deserve
their secrets, right?
Seems like I have a
lot of them these days.
I have to show you something.
You may understand it,
you may not, but...
- I need you to see.
- See what?
I think I know how I
survived that fire.
- Claire, don't!
- It's okay.
Please say something.
Some family.
I told Claire to get a move on.
She said she'd be back soon.
A cheerleader, huh?
- Co-captain by junior year.
- Wow.
Although not so
much these days.
They dissolved the
team 'cause of some...
horrible event at the school.
Oh, I heard about that.
That must have been
hard on poor Claire.
You are awfully interested
in my daughter.
Well, ever since I
seen what she can do,
I guess you could
say I'm a... fan.
She's really quite gifted.
Oh, you've been to a game?
Yeah, I guess I have.
I just couldn't get over
those irresistible...
talents of hers.
I should...
I should check with my husband again.
Excuse me.
I'd rather you didn't
so I can surprise him.
- H-h-how did you do that?
- I'm special.
Just like Claire. Well,
different. But...
you catch the meaning.
It's a shame I'll
have to kill her.
Or maybe I'll kill you first.
I really haven't decided yet.
Hi.
Find him. He dies!
I don't understand
what happened.
Why was he...
he moved the phone
- without even touching it.
- Shh.
You're safe now.
I'm right here.
I'll find him.
He kept asking about Claire.
Claire is fine. She's safe too.
And she'll stay that way.
I promise.
- Who is that?
- This is my friend.
He's gonna make
everything okay.
He'll help you forget again.
Again?
What do you mean again?
It's okay. Hold my hand.
It'll all be over soon.
You could stay a little longer.
Have some dinner.
I can't cook worth crap, but...
Well, I was supposed to
be home a while ago.
I got about six
messages from my dad
telling me to come
home right away, so...
He sounded pretty pissed.
This isn't good-bye.
You know that.
I was hoping you could
tell me about my father.
Now, that's...
complicated.
Why don't you let me work
on that for next time?
Some family.
Here...
A little something from Mexico.
Oh, no, I can't.
You can, and you're gonna.
It'll look ten times better on
you than it ever did on me.
Okay.
Isaac.
We haven't been up here
together in a long time.
There's something
about this roof.
You and I spent a
lot of time up here.
I mean,
it's connected with what's happening.
- It's important somehow.
- Well, it's certainly mysterious.
You know, I never figured out
how those pigeons got up here.
My father always said,
"If they found their way,
we ought to let 'em be."
I know we had a lot
together, Isaac.
For a long time.
You saw it.
The painting of us.
It's the future
I still hope for.
This city took me in.
Everything important that ever
happened to me happened here.
Good...
bad...
you.
And now it's all gonna be
destroyed because I can't stop it.
You don't know that.
It keeps coming back,
worse every time.
You saw what this looks
like after the bomb.
The world will never
recover from that.
That's not true.
You can't lose hope.
- What hope is there?
- There's you.
What you can do.
Why else would you be
allowed to see the future
unless it was to do
something about it?
You can't just see
the future, Isaac.
You make it.
You'll find a way.
You really believe that?
I believe in you.
I have given it much thought,
big sister.
Please tell Father I will return as
the new Executive Vice President.
This is good news.
Oh yes.
It is time to restructure.
And consolidate
management in Tokyo.
You can't
consolidate management...
I'm Executive Vice President,
I can do everything!
That would be a disaster.
Oh? You think you
have a better idea?
We should expand by making
new acquisitions in aviation.
Improve R&D in
biotech, recapitalize...
What do you know
of these things?
I run three divisions
at Yamagato.
If anyone knows how to run this company,
it's me!
Kimiko?
What's gotten into you?
My apologies.
I did not mean to.
Yes, she did.
Kimiko is smart and dedicated.
You don't need me.
You have your
successor right here!
- Get dressed!
- Dressed for what?
You're going home.
- That's not possible.
- Oh, it's more than possible.
The charges against you have
been dropped, Ms. Sanders.
What?
The D.A.
threw out the entire case.
That can't happen.
I killed people.
The state of Nevada isn't
so sure about that anymore.
It seems a rather terrible
gentleman on death row
confessed to all the
crimes you're accused of.
DNA evidence backed
up everything.
Wonderful system, isn't it?
As far as they're concerned,
justice has been served.
And as far as
Linderman is concerned?
Oh, don't worry about
tomorrow's problems today.
No.
I need to be in here.
I need help.
You only need to get dressed,
Ms. Sanders.
You're going home.
And that's the one you love.
Off to dinner with the guy
she left to be with you.
Sort of fickle,
don't you think?
Why would you show me that?
I didn't show you anything.
She did.
We just followed her.
Not even very long.
- I'm sorry, Peter.
- No, you're not.
You enjoyed that.
You got this rosy film over your eyes,
like a kid.
It's no wonder you live
like an adolescent.
Posters on the wall,
hair in your face.
You've got to see
the world as it is.
The only way you'll
learn how to save it.
And what, be like you?
A hermit?
No one knows you're alive
except for some pigeons.
You have to get rid of your
distractions. The people I love are
not distractions!
Then why can't you fly? You've done it.
Your body remembers how.
The only thing standing
in your way is you.
What am I supposed to do?
Cut 'em out of my life?
- How cold do you expect me to be?
- Did you forget you're a bomb?
You've got to remember
what this is about.
Or, do you have to ask for your
brother's permission for that as well?
Anything else that I have to do?
You wanna make a list?
You're a sad cartoon of a broken
heart bleeding all over the place.
I'm just trying to get
your mind straight.
Look, I have followed you around and
listened to your half-assed wisdom.
You don't have
any answers! Okay?
You don't know anything.
- You are afraid of the world.
- You have to listen to me.
And I am tired of you
telling me what I have to do!
- I don't have to do anything!
- Except fly.
Son of a bitch.
Not quite what I was expecting,
but hope for the flowers yet.
You threw me.
Off of a 30-story building!
If I didn't regenerate,
I'd be dead!
Well, you could have flown.
Listen, if you hadn't
have worked this one out,
you'd have been
hopeless anyway.
And I'd have to defuse
the biggest bomb ever.
But you did it, didn't you?
You cleared your mind.
You called out your power.
You know,
before I hit the ground...
when I knew what was about to happen,
I had this flash...
in my head,
of this girl that I met in Texas.
This cheerleader.
She could heal herself.
Oh, gosh, she's this sweet kid.
Sad little smile,
and she just...
You were wrong.
I don't have to cut her out.
I have to remember her!
How... how she made me feel!
That's how I...
Oh, God.
It's happening.
I'm losing it!
Well, it's a start.
Peter?
Yes?
I think I found a
way to stop him.
- I found him.
- Sylar?
- I thought you had Sylar.
- I will again.
Soon.
You mean Petrelli. Where is he?
I think he's been
here this whole time.
And I've been painting him.
Except no one can see him.
Like he's a ghost, or...
invisible.
What does that mean?
It means an old friend isn't quite
as dead as we thought he was.
You have made the
right choice, Father.
Let us hope so.
This does not mean I approve
of what you are doing.
That's okay. You don't have to.
Life evolves, Father.
And the son you wanted to be like
you will follow his own path.
Now I have to go
save the world!
Should never have read
him those stories.
You are insane, little brother.
You are welcome.
She's really
starting to like me.
Mom? I know it's
not our game night,
but can we play a
game of Scrabble
- since you just got home?
- Absolutely.
I owe you, like, a dozen.
- Just give me a minute, okay?
- Okay!
No!
What are you so
mad about, Niki?
You're the one who
wanted to be locked up.
No... no.
I'm home!
In the kitchen.
You are in big trouble,
young lady.
The school called.
Did you think you could ditch,
and I wouldn't find out?
Mom, we talked about
it this morning.
Zach and I went
to the aquarium.
Claire, I think I would remember a
conversation about you skippin' school.
- You okay?
- Fine, I...
banged my head on something.
Bit of a headache.
Why don't you let me finish,
uh, setting the table,
and you can go lie
down for a little bit.
Don't think this gets
you off the hook.
Hello?
You might not remember me.
We haven't spoken in
a long time, but...
Our daughter just found me.
Did you hear what I just said?
She's alive.
We need to talk, Nathan.
Thanks to Raceman for the Transcript
Subtitles Made By The Bloc Team
Synchronised By Tagne
For www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net