1
00:00:39,990 --> 00:00:42,080
Tonight's the night.

2
00:00:44,580 --> 00:00:47,960
And it's going to happen
again and again -

3
00:00:48,670 --> 00:00:50,670
has to happen.

4
00:00:55,470 --> 00:00:57,470
Nice night.

5
00:00:59,510 --> 00:01:01,060
Miami is a great town.

6
00:01:01,180 --> 00:01:02,720
I love the Cuban food.

7
00:01:02,850 --> 00:01:06,100
Pork sandwiches - my favorite.

8
00:01:13,030 --> 00:01:16,070
But I'm hungry
for something different now.

9
00:01:45,890 --> 00:01:47,890
There he is.

10
00:01:48,020 --> 00:01:50,100
Mike Donovan.

11
00:01:51,570 --> 00:01:53,230
He's the one.

12
00:02:15,260 --> 00:02:17,800
You're mine now,
so do exactly as I say.

13
00:02:19,640 --> 00:02:22,970
- What do you want?
- I want you to be quiet.

14
00:02:23,100 --> 00:02:24,180
Now drive.

15
00:02:52,130 --> 00:02:53,710
Turn here.

16
00:03:23,780 --> 00:03:25,120
You have to listen.

17
00:03:27,200 --> 00:03:29,000
And do what I say.

18
00:03:40,010 --> 00:03:41,510
Look.

19
00:03:41,630 --> 00:03:42,550
No.

20
00:03:42,680 --> 00:03:44,890
Uh, yes.

21
00:03:46,350 --> 00:03:47,260
No, no.

22
00:03:47,390 --> 00:03:50,310
It's horrible, isn't it? Isn't it?

23
00:03:50,430 --> 00:03:52,180
Please.

24
00:03:53,230 --> 00:03:57,020
Open your eyes
and look at what you did!

25
00:03:58,360 --> 00:04:00,690
Look or I'll cut your eyelids
right off your face.

26
00:04:06,830 --> 00:04:10,160
It took me a long time
to get these little boys clean.

27
00:04:11,580 --> 00:04:14,420
One was in the ground so long
he was falling apart.

28
00:04:14,540 --> 00:04:16,920
I pulled him out in bits and pieces.

29
00:04:17,040 --> 00:04:19,460
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is...

30
00:04:19,590 --> 00:04:21,590
Stop! That never helped anybody.

31
00:04:25,390 --> 00:04:27,550
Please, you can have anything.

32
00:04:27,680 --> 00:04:30,390
That's good. Beg.
Did these little boys beg?

33
00:04:36,810 --> 00:04:39,770
I couldn't help myself.
I couldn't. I just...

34
00:04:39,900 --> 00:04:41,900
Please, you have to understand.

35
00:04:45,070 --> 00:04:48,620
Trust me, I definitely understand.

36
00:04:48,740 --> 00:04:50,990
See, I can't help myself, either.

37
00:04:53,160 --> 00:04:56,040
Children - I could never do that,
not like you.

38
00:04:56,170 --> 00:04:59,460
Never, ever kids.

39
00:05:00,590 --> 00:05:01,840
Why?

40
00:05:03,720 --> 00:05:05,090
I have standards.

41
00:05:29,950 --> 00:05:33,450
Soon you'll be packed

42
00:05:33,580 --> 00:05:38,460
into a few neatly wrapped Hefties

43
00:05:40,290 --> 00:05:45,340
in my own small corner of the world.

44
00:05:47,130 --> 00:05:51,350
It'll be a neater, happier place.

45
00:05:55,480 --> 00:05:57,770
A better place.

46
00:06:20,500 --> 00:06:23,290
My name is Dexter, Dexter Morgan.

47
00:06:23,420 --> 00:06:25,340
I don't know what made me the way I am,

48
00:06:25,460 --> 00:06:28,760
but whatever it was
left a hollow place inside.

49
00:06:28,880 --> 00:06:32,050
People fake a lot
of human interactions,

50
00:06:32,180 --> 00:06:35,430
but I feel like I fake them all
and I fake them very well.

51
00:06:37,770 --> 00:06:40,560
Ahoy, there!
Any big marlin out there today?

52
00:06:40,690 --> 00:06:43,900
And that's my burden, I guess.

53
00:06:44,020 --> 00:06:45,650
I don't blame my foster parents.

54
00:06:45,780 --> 00:06:49,240
Harry and Doris Morgan
did a wonderful job raising me.

55
00:06:50,700 --> 00:06:52,870
But they're both dead now.

56
00:06:52,990 --> 00:06:55,120
I didn't kill them.

57
00:06:55,240 --> 00:06:56,450
Honest.

58
00:06:58,160 --> 00:07:00,710
You're different, aren't you, Dexter?

59
00:07:00,830 --> 00:07:05,670
- What do you mean, Pop?
- The Billups said Buddy disappeared.

60
00:07:08,220 --> 00:07:09,510
I found the grave, son.

61
00:07:09,630 --> 00:07:11,720
That dog was a noisy little creep, Dad.

62
00:07:11,840 --> 00:07:14,430
He was barking all night
and Mom's very sick.

63
00:07:14,550 --> 00:07:18,310
That lousy dog was yapping at every leaf that
blew down the sidewalk.

64
00:07:18,890 --> 00:07:23,060
There were a lot of bones in there, Dexter,
and not just Buddy's.

65
00:08:23,370 --> 00:08:25,290
Blood -

66
00:08:25,420 --> 00:08:27,790
sometimes it sets my teeth on edge.

67
00:08:30,960 --> 00:08:33,800
Other times,
it helps me control the chaos.

68
00:08:35,800 --> 00:08:39,600
The code of Harry,
my foster father, is satisfied.

69
00:08:40,270 --> 00:08:41,600
And so am I.

70
00:08:42,640 --> 00:08:44,560
Harry was a great cop here in Miami.

71
00:08:44,690 --> 00:08:48,400
He taught me how to think like one,
how to cover my tracks.

72
00:08:49,480 --> 00:08:51,150
I'm a very neat monster.

73
00:08:54,820 --> 00:08:57,030
Dexter, are you there?

74
00:08:58,070 --> 00:09:00,530
OK, Dex, please,
as soon as you get in,

75
00:09:00,660 --> 00:09:03,870
I'm at a crime scene
by the shithole, the Seven Seas Motel,

76
00:09:04,000 --> 00:09:06,540
and I need you here, OK?

77
00:09:06,670 --> 00:09:08,210
Dex? Please.

78
00:09:08,340 --> 00:09:10,840
Pretty fucking please
with cheese on top.

79
00:09:10,960 --> 00:09:14,010
That's my foul-mouthed
foster sister, Debra.

80
00:09:14,340 --> 00:09:16,760
She has a big heart
but won't let anyone see it.

81
00:09:16,890 --> 00:09:19,600
She's the only person
in the world who loves me.

82
00:09:19,720 --> 00:09:21,470
I think that's nice.

83
00:09:21,600 --> 00:09:23,350
I don't have feelings

84
00:09:23,480 --> 00:09:27,310
but if I could have feelings at all,
I'd have them for Deb.

85
00:09:31,190 --> 00:09:32,820
There's something strange

86
00:09:32,940 --> 00:09:36,490
about looking at a homicide scene
in the daylight of Miami.

87
00:09:36,610 --> 00:09:39,070
It makes grotesque killings look staged,

88
00:09:39,200 --> 00:09:42,160
like you're in a daring section
of Disney World.

89
00:09:43,160 --> 00:09:44,080
Dahmer Land.

90
00:09:44,200 --> 00:09:45,290
You better be a cop.

91
00:09:45,410 --> 00:09:47,210
No. Forensics.

92
00:09:53,380 --> 00:09:54,550
Dex!

93
00:09:55,840 --> 00:09:57,930
Hey, what's up?

94
00:10:01,760 --> 00:10:05,060
Jeez, Deb. Where the hell
do you keep your gun?

95
00:10:05,180 --> 00:10:06,770
They found another hooker in the pool.

96
00:10:06,890 --> 00:10:09,270
- Another?
- Chopped up in bits and pieces.

97
00:10:09,400 --> 00:10:12,560
- The third one in five months.
- Third? You mean there's a...

98
00:10:12,690 --> 00:10:14,400
A serial killer, that's right.

99
00:10:14,530 --> 00:10:18,450
The other two were in Broward,
chopped up just like this one.

100
00:10:18,570 --> 00:10:21,620
- Any suspects?
- Wish I knew.

101
00:10:21,740 --> 00:10:25,620
I'm on Vice so LaGuerta told me
to stay out of sight.

102
00:10:25,750 --> 00:10:27,710
God forbid she listens to you.

103
00:10:27,830 --> 00:10:30,000
Tell me about it.

104
00:10:30,130 --> 00:10:32,630
How does someone so dumb
get so much power?

105
00:10:33,210 --> 00:10:36,590
She knows how to play the game.
You could take a lesson.

106
00:10:37,090 --> 00:10:38,630
In what, ass-kissing?

107
00:10:38,760 --> 00:10:40,260
Politics.

108
00:10:44,600 --> 00:10:47,930
I just want to catch this guy
before he kills another one of my girls.

109
00:10:48,060 --> 00:10:49,690
Don't get so emotionally invested.

110
00:10:49,810 --> 00:10:51,980
- You always say that.
- So did Dad.

111
00:10:52,770 --> 00:10:55,820
Yeah, but he also said,
"Go after what you want."

112
00:10:55,940 --> 00:10:58,820
I want out of Vice and into Homicide.

113
00:10:58,950 --> 00:11:01,070
What can I do to help?

114
00:11:02,660 --> 00:11:05,700
You get these hunches
with these types of murders.

115
00:11:06,950 --> 00:11:08,410
Only sometimes.

116
00:11:08,540 --> 00:11:10,410
Well, see if you get one this time.

117
00:11:10,540 --> 00:11:14,340
And can I bounce some ideas off you?
I get smarter when I talk to you.

118
00:11:14,460 --> 00:11:16,630
You just need
a little more confidence.

119
00:11:22,800 --> 00:11:24,890
All right, I'll take a look.

120
00:11:25,010 --> 00:11:27,600
Avoid LaGuerta
and talk to Captain Matthews.

121
00:11:27,720 --> 00:11:29,930
He and Dad were tight.
He may put you on the case.

122
00:11:30,060 --> 00:11:32,190
You're making me smarter already, see?

123
00:11:33,480 --> 00:11:37,780
And keep the sex suit on when you talk
to the captain. It'll help your cause.

124
00:11:49,830 --> 00:11:51,870
That's a nice haircut, Masuka.

125
00:11:52,000 --> 00:11:54,330
I saw your sister.
Damn, looking hot.

126
00:11:54,460 --> 00:11:56,670
Yeah, she should.
It's hot as hell out here.

127
00:11:57,550 --> 00:12:01,130
- So, why are you here?
- It's a crime scene.

128
00:12:01,260 --> 00:12:03,880
- Yeah, but you do blood spatter.
- So?

129
00:12:04,010 --> 00:12:06,100
So... There's no blood here.

130
00:12:07,810 --> 00:12:11,350
- What was that?
- Yeah. There's no blood in or on

131
00:12:11,480 --> 00:12:12,560
or near the body at all.

132
00:12:12,690 --> 00:12:14,900
It's the weirdest thing you ever saw.

133
00:12:15,020 --> 00:12:17,020
Hey, Angel, let's show him.

134
00:12:17,150 --> 00:12:18,400
No blood.

135
00:12:18,530 --> 00:12:21,490
No sticky, hot, messy, awful blood.

136
00:12:21,610 --> 00:12:23,070
No blood at all.

137
00:12:25,490 --> 00:12:28,410
Why hadn't I thought of that?
No blood.

138
00:12:29,870 --> 00:12:32,080
What a beautiful idea.

139
00:12:32,210 --> 00:12:34,000
How does the killer get rid of the blood?

140
00:12:34,120 --> 00:12:35,580
It's hard to say.

141
00:12:35,710 --> 00:12:37,380
The body's in good shape.

142
00:12:37,500 --> 00:12:39,460
She had a nice ass too.

143
00:12:40,510 --> 00:12:43,170
Head is over there,
if you want to take a look.

144
00:12:43,300 --> 00:12:44,760
This is unique.

145
00:12:44,880 --> 00:12:48,010
No shit. And no prints, either.

146
00:12:48,430 --> 00:12:53,060
I've never seen such clean,
dry, neat-looking dead flesh.

147
00:12:53,180 --> 00:12:54,180
Wonderful.

148
00:12:55,060 --> 00:12:57,860
- It's very clean.
- Yeah, but he didn't finish.

149
00:12:59,650 --> 00:13:01,280
It looks pretty completo to me, Angel.

150
00:13:01,400 --> 00:13:02,440
No, no. Look.

151
00:13:02,570 --> 00:13:07,870
He cut the leg in four pieces,
almost like using a ruler.

152
00:13:07,990 --> 00:13:10,910
But this leg is in three pieces.

153
00:13:12,750 --> 00:13:15,620
Now, look, he started to make
a fourth cut but stopped.

154
00:13:15,750 --> 00:13:17,580
It's possible that he got interrupted.

155
00:13:17,710 --> 00:13:20,960
LaGuerta's looking for a witness,
working on the motel porter.

156
00:13:21,090 --> 00:13:22,420
God help him.

157
00:13:25,260 --> 00:13:26,430
No blood.

158
00:13:26,550 --> 00:13:28,970
I can't think.
I have to get out of here.

159
00:13:32,270 --> 00:13:34,520
- Where are you going?
- Hey, no blood...

160
00:13:47,700 --> 00:13:49,200
I wish she'd stop that.

161
00:13:49,320 --> 00:13:52,950
It's one of those mating rituals
which I really don't understand.

162
00:13:59,500 --> 00:14:01,500
But that bloodless body...

163
00:14:02,880 --> 00:14:05,920
This guy may have exceeded
my own abilities.

164
00:14:11,050 --> 00:14:12,100
Morning, Dex.

165
00:14:12,220 --> 00:14:13,560
Morning.

166
00:14:16,390 --> 00:14:17,640
Hey, Dex.

167
00:14:17,770 --> 00:14:19,480
Hey, Sue. Dan.

168
00:14:19,600 --> 00:14:21,560
How are the families?

169
00:14:22,610 --> 00:14:25,190
Good. You?

170
00:14:25,320 --> 00:14:28,700
- See you at the next bloodbath?
- Never miss a party.

171
00:14:28,820 --> 00:14:30,490
Thanks.

172
00:14:33,450 --> 00:14:36,790
Salt of the earth, these people,
and they work hard.

173
00:14:36,910 --> 00:14:39,040
But with the solve rate
for murders at about 20%,

174
00:14:39,170 --> 00:14:41,330
Miami is a great place for me,

175
00:14:41,460 --> 00:14:44,130
a great place for me to hone my craft.

176
00:14:47,550 --> 00:14:50,880
- I like your other outfit better.
- You're a sick bastard.

177
00:14:51,090 --> 00:14:53,850
Guess what. Sex suit worked.
Captain put me on the case.

178
00:14:53,970 --> 00:14:56,770
LaGuerta wasn't happy
but she needs to get laid.

179
00:14:57,600 --> 00:14:59,270
I guess. So congrats.

180
00:15:00,650 --> 00:15:02,900
- So you got any ideas yet?
- Nope.

181
00:15:03,020 --> 00:15:05,230
Well, start working
on your mental autopsy

182
00:15:05,360 --> 00:15:07,730
cos I could use your theories.

183
00:15:07,860 --> 00:15:10,530
And thanks for the fucking doughnut.
I got to go.

184
00:15:13,320 --> 00:15:14,320
Doughnut?

185
00:15:18,790 --> 00:15:20,710
You keeping your fingernails clean?

186
00:15:20,830 --> 00:15:23,130
Never leave home
without my rubber gloves.

187
00:15:23,250 --> 00:15:24,380
Good boy.

188
00:15:27,510 --> 00:15:28,840
So, anything new?

189
00:15:37,810 --> 00:15:40,100
One of these days
you're gonna tell me.

190
00:15:40,230 --> 00:15:43,270
I already told you. Blood spatter
doesn't take up all my time.

191
00:15:43,400 --> 00:15:45,270
I like doing it. Maybe I can help out.

192
00:15:45,400 --> 00:15:46,900
It fills my nights.

193
00:15:47,030 --> 00:15:49,610
You have
a morbid sense of fun.

194
00:15:49,740 --> 00:15:51,030
That's probably true.

195
00:15:51,820 --> 00:15:53,410
You should find a pretty girl.

196
00:15:53,530 --> 00:15:55,530
I found you.

197
00:15:56,740 --> 00:15:58,240
Charming like your father.

198
00:15:58,370 --> 00:16:01,040
Just don't get me fired.

199
00:16:01,160 --> 00:16:04,040
Then who would
I bring doughnuts to?

200
00:16:16,760 --> 00:16:18,390
Just like me -

201
00:16:18,510 --> 00:16:20,180
empty inside.

202
00:16:32,610 --> 00:16:36,370
- Where the hell you been?
- Crime scene.

203
00:16:37,280 --> 00:16:41,240
What about the hotel cokehead murders,
this dealer and the girl?

204
00:16:43,040 --> 00:16:46,500
This Hallmark-looking couple didn't die
by the hands of a professional.

205
00:16:46,630 --> 00:16:50,840
This is child's play.
Messy work.

206
00:16:50,960 --> 00:16:53,550
That blood on the walls
looks like a finger painting.

207
00:16:54,470 --> 00:16:56,680
You give me the fuckin' creeps,
you know that, Dexter?

208
00:16:56,800 --> 00:16:59,850
Yeah, I know. Sorry about that.

209
00:17:00,890 --> 00:17:02,430
Fuck you.

210
00:17:02,560 --> 00:17:04,100
OK.

211
00:17:04,230 --> 00:17:05,520
Is there something I can do?

212
00:17:05,650 --> 00:17:08,230
Give me your fucking analysis
on the blood spatter.

213
00:17:08,360 --> 00:17:11,440
You think I'm here to invite you
to my nephew's Bris?

214
00:17:11,570 --> 00:17:12,860
I didn't know you were Jewish.

215
00:17:12,990 --> 00:17:15,860
Shut the fuck up
and write your report already.

216
00:17:15,990 --> 00:17:17,200
Don't even know why I need you.

217
00:17:17,320 --> 00:17:19,490
Grab a crayon, psycho,
and scribble this down.

218
00:17:19,620 --> 00:17:23,540
Rival dealer came in, two scumbags slashed to
hell, dealer stole the drugs.

219
00:17:23,660 --> 00:17:25,370
Wham, bam, done.

220
00:17:25,500 --> 00:17:26,920
I don't give a shit what you say.

221
00:17:27,040 --> 00:17:29,580
That's what happened
and that's who I'm looking for.

222
00:17:30,840 --> 00:17:34,210
We are looking for
a motherfucking thief dealer. You got it?

223
00:17:34,760 --> 00:17:36,260
OK. Sure.

224
00:17:38,010 --> 00:17:41,390
I guess, but I should get over there.

225
00:17:41,510 --> 00:17:44,140
Then get over there already,
you fucking weirdo.

226
00:17:44,270 --> 00:17:46,940
- I need it quick.
- I'm on it, Sergeant.

227
00:17:52,110 --> 00:17:54,480
The only real question I have is why,

228
00:17:54,610 --> 00:17:56,190
in a building full of cops,

229
00:17:56,320 --> 00:17:59,320
all supposedly with a keen insight
into the human soul,

230
00:18:00,070 --> 00:18:04,870
is Doakes the only one
who gets the creeps from me?

231
00:18:05,830 --> 00:18:08,040
So this killer used a sword?

232
00:18:10,380 --> 00:18:14,130
No, probably a very sharp knife.

233
00:18:14,260 --> 00:18:16,630
Look at the blood spatter.
It tells a story.

234
00:18:16,760 --> 00:18:19,550
You see this big pond of blood
right there?

235
00:18:19,680 --> 00:18:21,850
That's from the initial stab.

236
00:18:21,970 --> 00:18:24,810
The male victim was standing right here,

237
00:18:24,930 --> 00:18:27,730
and the killer plunged his knife
into the shoulder,

238
00:18:27,850 --> 00:18:30,020
severing the carotid artery, and...

239
00:18:31,190 --> 00:18:33,570
Notice the long, thick, heavy drips?

240
00:18:33,690 --> 00:18:34,650
Yeah, nice.

241
00:18:34,780 --> 00:18:38,240
Now, over here, you have nice,
clean sprays of blood.

242
00:18:38,360 --> 00:18:41,410
That only happens when you're holding
something light and moving quick -

243
00:18:41,530 --> 00:18:43,370
nice, sharp slices through the body.

244
00:18:43,490 --> 00:18:45,740
No splashes, no drips.

245
00:18:45,870 --> 00:18:48,370
Clean and easy.

246
00:18:49,080 --> 00:18:52,420
This guy knew how to use a blade.

247
00:18:54,380 --> 00:18:56,880
So we're looking for a sushi chef.

248
00:18:57,840 --> 00:18:59,300
Yeah, sushi chef is possible.

249
00:18:59,430 --> 00:19:03,350
Wouldn't be my first choice,
but, hey, you never know.

250
00:19:04,510 --> 00:19:07,180
- Now what?
- Now I eat.

251
00:19:07,680 --> 00:19:10,560
The problem with eating and driving,
which I love to do,

252
00:19:10,690 --> 00:19:13,650
is not being able to employ
the 10:00-2:00 hand position on the wheel.

253
00:19:13,770 --> 00:19:16,360
It's a matter of public safety.

254
00:19:17,530 --> 00:19:20,360
But there's always a sacrifice.

255
00:19:26,990 --> 00:19:30,790
This guy, Jamie Jaworski.

256
00:19:30,920 --> 00:19:34,170
Six months ago, I think he fell
in love with a pretty brunette,

257
00:19:34,290 --> 00:19:36,460
Mrs. Jane Saunders -

258
00:19:37,130 --> 00:19:40,050
a sweet mother of two married
to a successful banker -

259
00:19:40,170 --> 00:19:41,760
all living a pleasant life

260
00:19:41,880 --> 00:19:43,760
until she, unfortunately, disappeared,

261
00:19:43,890 --> 00:19:46,390
leaving the kids
emotionally devastated forever.

262
00:19:51,560 --> 00:19:53,520
The cops arrested my favorite valet

263
00:19:53,650 --> 00:19:57,150
but his lawyer got him off
on a faulty search warrant.

264
00:20:00,860 --> 00:20:03,700
It's a good thing
I don't bother with them.

265
00:20:55,540 --> 00:20:58,880
Animals don't like me, especially dogs.

266
00:20:59,880 --> 00:21:04,670
I don't think they approve of what
I sometimes do to their masters.

267
00:21:04,800 --> 00:21:10,140
That dog recognizes me
as easily as I can recognize Jaworski

268
00:21:10,260 --> 00:21:12,720
or any other killer.

269
00:21:36,120 --> 00:21:38,420
Interesting taste in literature.

270
00:21:39,460 --> 00:21:42,800
His needs are evolving,
turning violent.

271
00:21:44,300 --> 00:21:45,760
He's on the fast track.

272
00:21:46,590 --> 00:21:49,260
Have you ever wanted
to kill anything else?

273
00:21:49,390 --> 00:21:52,810
You know, something bigger than a dog?

274
00:21:54,890 --> 00:21:56,140
Yes.

275
00:21:56,980 --> 00:21:59,230
Like a person?

276
00:21:59,360 --> 00:22:02,110
Yeah, but no one in particular.

277
00:22:04,280 --> 00:22:06,490
Why didn't you?

278
00:22:08,950 --> 00:22:11,280
I thought you and Mom wouldn't like it.

279
00:22:21,040 --> 00:22:22,960
Come here.

280
00:22:31,220 --> 00:22:34,140
Friday night - date night in Miami.

281
00:22:35,180 --> 00:22:39,060
Every night is date night in Miami
and everyone's having sex.

282
00:22:40,270 --> 00:22:43,400
But for me sex never enters into it.

283
00:22:43,520 --> 00:22:45,980
I don't understand sex.

284
00:22:46,110 --> 00:22:50,070
I have nothing against women
and an appropriate sensibility about men,

285
00:22:50,200 --> 00:22:53,740
but when it comes
to the actual act of sex,

286
00:22:53,870 --> 00:22:57,120
it's always just seemed so...

287
00:22:58,000 --> 00:22:59,830
undignified.

288
00:23:01,210 --> 00:23:03,000
But I have to play the game.

289
00:23:03,130 --> 00:23:05,170
And after years
of trying to look normal,

290
00:23:05,300 --> 00:23:07,300
I think I met the right woman for me.

291
00:23:08,340 --> 00:23:12,550
Deb saved her life
on a domestic-dispute call, introduced us,

292
00:23:12,680 --> 00:23:14,470
and we've been dating for six months.

293
00:23:15,720 --> 00:23:19,390
She's perfect because Rita is,
in her own way,

294
00:23:19,520 --> 00:23:21,900
as damaged as me.

295
00:23:22,020 --> 00:23:25,570
I'm running late. I'll just be a sec.
I have to change.

296
00:23:25,690 --> 00:23:26,780
Okey-doke.

297
00:23:33,200 --> 00:23:34,660
Hi, Dexter.

298
00:23:35,830 --> 00:23:38,410
May I say that you look lovely
this evening?

299
00:23:38,540 --> 00:23:39,660
OK.

300
00:23:40,870 --> 00:23:42,870
Master Cody,
handsome as ever.

301
00:23:43,000 --> 00:23:44,330
High five.

302
00:23:51,550 --> 00:23:53,890
Do the Space Shuttle.

303
00:23:56,890 --> 00:23:58,850
Vanilla...

304
00:23:58,970 --> 00:24:01,520
chocolate, and strawberry.

305
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:03,390
No coffee?

306
00:24:03,520 --> 00:24:05,400
Which one do you think melts faster?

307
00:24:06,900 --> 00:24:07,900
Ready?

308
00:24:09,530 --> 00:24:11,690
Rita's ex-hubby, the crack addict,

309
00:24:11,820 --> 00:24:15,200
repeatedly raped her,
knocked her around.

310
00:24:15,870 --> 00:24:20,080
Ever since then, she's been
completely uninterested in sex.

311
00:24:21,160 --> 00:24:22,910
That works for me.

312
00:24:23,920 --> 00:24:25,290
Will you be back?

313
00:24:25,420 --> 00:24:26,790
Of course I'll be back.

314
00:24:26,920 --> 00:24:28,630
I meant Dexter.

315
00:24:28,750 --> 00:24:30,130
You'll be asleep.

316
00:24:30,260 --> 00:24:31,460
No, I won't.

317
00:24:31,590 --> 00:24:34,880
Then I'll stop in and we'll all play cards.
Texas hold 'em?

318
00:24:36,800 --> 00:24:38,760
Give Mommy a kiss.

319
00:24:40,220 --> 00:24:41,470
Ready?

320
00:24:41,600 --> 00:24:43,180
Yeah.

321
00:24:55,610 --> 00:24:58,370
Needless to say,
I have some unusual habits.

322
00:24:58,490 --> 00:25:00,370
Yet all these socially acceptable people

323
00:25:00,490 --> 00:25:05,040
can't wait to pick up hammers
and publicly smash their food to bits.

324
00:25:06,460 --> 00:25:09,340
Normal people are so hostile...

325
00:25:10,550 --> 00:25:12,380
but not her.

326
00:25:33,650 --> 00:25:35,150
Where are we going?

327
00:25:37,070 --> 00:25:38,620
They might need me.

328
00:25:43,000 --> 00:25:45,540
Just stay right there.
I'll be right back.

329
00:26:07,940 --> 00:26:10,440
Son of a whore.

330
00:26:10,560 --> 00:26:11,900
Who?

331
00:26:12,020 --> 00:26:14,480
Talking about this hijo de puta,
this asshole killer,

332
00:26:14,610 --> 00:26:17,570
this maricÃ³n savage who makes us
work on a Friday night.

333
00:26:17,700 --> 00:26:21,070
Only Mondays through Thursdays,
that's what I always say.

334
00:26:21,200 --> 00:26:23,410
Of course. Be reasonable.

335
00:26:23,540 --> 00:26:25,790
Who wants to work
on a Friday night?

336
00:26:25,910 --> 00:26:27,410
I have my needs.

337
00:26:30,210 --> 00:26:32,000
So, what are you doing here?

338
00:26:32,750 --> 00:26:34,710
I was in the neighborhood.
I'm on a date.

339
00:26:34,840 --> 00:26:36,420
A date? Nice.

340
00:26:37,720 --> 00:26:40,010
- Same guy, same pattern.
- Bone dry.

341
00:26:40,140 --> 00:26:41,470
No blood again.

342
00:26:44,060 --> 00:26:46,430
There's some small differences in the cuts.

343
00:26:46,930 --> 00:26:50,560
Over here -
rough, almost emotion.

344
00:26:50,690 --> 00:26:53,310
Then over here, not so much.

345
00:26:53,440 --> 00:26:55,690
And then over here - clean.

346
00:26:57,530 --> 00:26:59,740
Yeah, nice. But look at this.

347
00:27:01,070 --> 00:27:02,870
All bone.

348
00:27:02,990 --> 00:27:06,160
The killer flayed the skin,
the flesh, completely off.

349
00:27:07,080 --> 00:27:11,540
- Now, why would he do that?
- He's experimenting.

350
00:27:11,670 --> 00:27:16,090
- Is he experimenting with the head, too?
- What do you mean?

351
00:27:16,210 --> 00:27:19,090
La bestia left her tits
and took her fucking head.

352
00:27:19,220 --> 00:27:22,890
I don't find anyone around here.
God only knows what he's doing with it.

353
00:27:23,010 --> 00:27:24,680
He's certainly raising the bar.

354
00:27:24,810 --> 00:27:26,350
Damn.

355
00:27:26,470 --> 00:27:29,100
This guy is good.

356
00:27:30,390 --> 00:27:32,850
Will they catch him soon?

357
00:27:32,980 --> 00:27:35,610
I doubt it.

358
00:27:36,610 --> 00:27:41,610
- The killer is an artist.
- What do you mean?

359
00:27:44,120 --> 00:27:49,580
His technique is incredible.

360
00:27:55,290 --> 00:27:59,510
I'm sorry. I don't think I want to.

361
00:27:59,630 --> 00:28:03,260
I mean, I'm not ready.

362
00:28:04,550 --> 00:28:06,050
Damn it, Dexter.

363
00:28:08,520 --> 00:28:10,730
What have I done now?

364
00:28:12,480 --> 00:28:16,730
And why can't I get that neat stack
of body parts out of my head?

365
00:28:16,860 --> 00:28:19,320
No blood.

366
00:28:20,440 --> 00:28:23,110
Why did I touch her that way?

367
00:28:24,660 --> 00:28:26,660
I need to get back to my work.

368
00:28:29,500 --> 00:28:33,120
Jaworski's website -
Scream, Bitch, Scream -

369
00:28:33,250 --> 00:28:35,330
the mother of all rape sites.

370
00:28:51,520 --> 00:28:54,190
That's it. He's definitely the one.

371
00:28:56,940 --> 00:29:01,530
It's just a matter of time before he becomes a
drop of blood in my glass slide collection.

372
00:29:03,860 --> 00:29:07,990
But I have to wait. I have to be careful

373
00:29:08,120 --> 00:29:10,870
and follow the code of Harry.

374
00:29:21,210 --> 00:29:22,710
Hey, Dad.

375
00:29:26,640 --> 00:29:29,430
- I can explain.
- You and I had an understanding.

376
00:29:29,560 --> 00:29:33,560
Whenever you get an urge, you tell me,
and we deal with it together.

377
00:29:33,680 --> 00:29:35,390
- I do tell you, Dad.
- The hell you do!

378
00:29:35,520 --> 00:29:37,310
There's blood on this knife.

379
00:29:37,440 --> 00:29:39,940
Animals. I find animals, that's all.

380
00:29:40,070 --> 00:29:41,650
Are you sure?

381
00:29:41,780 --> 00:29:44,360
- Are you telling me the truth?
- Yes.

382
00:29:45,030 --> 00:29:46,700
I thought we had this under control.

383
00:29:55,710 --> 00:29:58,420
You still don't remember
anything from before,

384
00:29:58,540 --> 00:30:00,000
you know, before we took you in?

385
00:30:00,130 --> 00:30:01,590
No.

386
00:30:03,960 --> 00:30:06,010
Is that why I have these urges?

387
00:30:09,430 --> 00:30:11,800
What happened
changed something inside you.

388
00:30:13,020 --> 00:30:15,020
It got into you too early.

389
00:30:16,890 --> 00:30:19,310
Your urge to kill is only gonna get stronger.

390
00:30:20,310 --> 00:30:23,480
You're saying I'll be like this forever.

391
00:30:23,610 --> 00:30:26,070
You're a good kid, Dex.

392
00:30:26,200 --> 00:30:31,160
You are. Otherwise, it would have been
a lot worse than animals.

393
00:30:34,040 --> 00:30:37,210
OK? We can't stop this.

394
00:30:38,790 --> 00:30:39,790
But maybe...

395
00:30:42,170 --> 00:30:45,170
we can do something to channel it.

396
00:30:49,550 --> 00:30:50,590
Use it for good.

397
00:30:51,800 --> 00:30:53,350
How could it ever be good?

398
00:30:53,470 --> 00:30:56,810
Son, there are people out there
who do really bad things.

399
00:30:57,680 --> 00:30:59,890
Terrible people.

400
00:31:00,650 --> 00:31:03,440
And the police can't catch them all.

401
00:31:06,740 --> 00:31:09,450
Do you understand what I'm saying?

402
00:31:10,490 --> 00:31:13,870
You're saying they deserve it.

403
00:31:13,990 --> 00:31:15,660
That's right.

404
00:31:17,660 --> 00:31:20,460
But, of course, you have
to learn how to spot them,

405
00:31:21,500 --> 00:31:23,000
how to cover your tracks.

406
00:31:25,710 --> 00:31:27,420
But I can teach you.

407
00:31:29,840 --> 00:31:31,300
Dad...

408
00:31:31,430 --> 00:31:32,970
It's OK, Dex.

409
00:31:33,100 --> 00:31:34,890
You can't help
what happened to you,

410
00:31:35,560 --> 00:31:38,390
but you can make the best of it.

411
00:31:38,520 --> 00:31:40,480
Remember this forever.

412
00:31:41,440 --> 00:31:43,520
You are my son.

413
00:31:43,650 --> 00:31:46,440
You are not alone and you are loved.

414
00:31:49,990 --> 00:31:51,030
OK.

415
00:31:52,240 --> 00:31:54,820
Preparation is vital.

416
00:31:54,950 --> 00:31:56,700
No detail can be overlooked.

417
00:32:02,420 --> 00:32:05,330
And the ritual is intoxicating.

418
00:32:13,800 --> 00:32:16,100
Duct tape,

419
00:32:16,220 --> 00:32:17,890
rubber sheets.

420
00:32:19,730 --> 00:32:21,730
Necessary tools of the trade.

421
00:32:27,440 --> 00:32:29,280
You can't bullshit me, Dex.

422
00:32:29,400 --> 00:32:31,990
Help me out. LaGuerta still
has me interviewing hookers.

423
00:32:32,110 --> 00:32:34,280
It's a waste of time.

424
00:32:35,700 --> 00:32:38,280
Deb, if he was interrupted...

425
00:32:38,410 --> 00:32:39,990
Think.

426
00:32:41,540 --> 00:32:43,080
Jesus Christ, right.

427
00:32:43,210 --> 00:32:45,960
Then how do you have
time to wrap all the pieces?

428
00:32:46,080 --> 00:32:49,170
She's dumber than the boat people.
Throw her a fucking raft.

429
00:32:49,300 --> 00:32:52,050
But now we have a fourth body,
and the cuts were different.

430
00:32:52,170 --> 00:32:53,800
And that's telling us a story.

431
00:32:53,930 --> 00:32:56,090
The ritual is changing.

432
00:32:57,390 --> 00:33:00,100
He's looking for inspiration
and not finding it.

433
00:33:00,220 --> 00:33:02,020
So he keeps doing it until he gets it right.

434
00:33:02,140 --> 00:33:03,730
I could be wrong.

435
00:33:05,900 --> 00:33:08,270
So how the hell was your date
with Rita last night?

436
00:33:08,400 --> 00:33:11,530
Great. You should try it sometime.
You need a life.

437
00:33:11,650 --> 00:33:13,650
Well, find me a guy I can trust.

438
00:33:13,780 --> 00:33:17,530
I need a transfer to Homicide, bro,
then we'll see about a life.

439
00:33:17,660 --> 00:33:19,700
It certainly would sound better

440
00:33:19,830 --> 00:33:22,540
for the kids to say,
"Mommy's on Homicide."

441
00:33:22,660 --> 00:33:24,080
Don't make me hit you.

442
00:33:24,210 --> 00:33:25,540
Come on.

443
00:33:26,630 --> 00:33:30,250
Then we could talk about
more little Morgans, nephews and nieces.

444
00:33:30,380 --> 00:33:32,840
You sound like Mom.

445
00:33:32,960 --> 00:33:36,930
Just tell me what you know
about cell crystallization.

446
00:33:37,050 --> 00:33:38,590
What do you mean?

447
00:33:38,720 --> 00:33:42,180
I heard the coroner say it last night.
He was talking about that dead...

448
00:33:42,310 --> 00:33:43,680
The headless chick.

449
00:33:43,810 --> 00:33:45,640
You got that look in your eye.

450
00:33:46,440 --> 00:33:47,440
I was there before you,

451
00:33:47,560 --> 00:33:51,940
And I noticed this body looked
different than the other ones.

452
00:33:52,070 --> 00:33:53,730
The pieces were cold.

453
00:33:54,400 --> 00:33:59,410
They were meat-packing cold.
Is that what cell crystallization means?

454
00:33:59,530 --> 00:34:02,950
My God, why didn't I think of that?
It's beautiful.

455
00:34:03,080 --> 00:34:04,870
Dex?

456
00:34:05,000 --> 00:34:06,410
What are you thinking?

457
00:34:06,540 --> 00:34:10,580
Sorry. That makes sense.

458
00:34:10,710 --> 00:34:12,170
Cold.

459
00:34:14,340 --> 00:34:19,550
- It slows the flow of blood.
- Why the hell is that important?

460
00:34:19,680 --> 00:34:22,050
It's just a feeling.

461
00:34:22,180 --> 00:34:24,430
Well, it's not good enough.

462
00:34:24,560 --> 00:34:28,020
I got to show LaGuerta and her boys.
They're making fun of me.

463
00:34:28,690 --> 00:34:31,560
They're saying the only way
I can close a case is on my back.

464
00:34:32,690 --> 00:34:36,490
I got to get out of Vice.
Dex, please, you got to...

465
00:34:36,610 --> 00:34:38,360
Refrigerated truck.

466
00:34:40,570 --> 00:34:43,660
What the fuck are you talking about?

467
00:34:43,790 --> 00:34:45,620
A refrigerated truck.

468
00:34:47,160 --> 00:34:53,590
He wants a cold environment
to slow the flow of blood,

469
00:34:53,710 --> 00:34:58,550
clean and mobile so he can dump
the garbage afterwards.

470
00:34:59,220 --> 00:35:01,760
So I'm looking for
a refrigerated truck now?

471
00:35:01,890 --> 00:35:04,220
Probably a stolen one.

472
00:35:05,930 --> 00:35:08,020
You think there are a lot
of stolen trucks out there?

473
00:35:08,140 --> 00:35:11,480
Are you nuts? In Miami?

474
00:35:13,570 --> 00:35:16,150
Choir. Kids.

475
00:35:17,030 --> 00:35:19,900
Can't you do something?
Just find my husband.

476
00:35:20,030 --> 00:35:23,660
Ma'am, the detectives
are looking into everything.

477
00:35:24,530 --> 00:35:27,160
I'm pretty sure I covered all my tracks.

478
00:35:27,290 --> 00:35:29,160
What do you care about that woman?

479
00:35:30,580 --> 00:35:31,960
I don't. I was just...

480
00:35:32,080 --> 00:35:35,290
You like when women cry?
You like that?

481
00:35:35,420 --> 00:35:38,800
- What's your thing, psycho?
- I was just heading to the briefing room.

482
00:35:38,920 --> 00:35:40,630
You got no call to be in there, so flee.

483
00:35:40,760 --> 00:35:43,680
Lieutenant, this fucking guy
doesn't belong.

484
00:35:43,800 --> 00:35:47,640
I'm still waiting for his spatter report
on the cokehead murders. Go do that.

485
00:35:47,770 --> 00:35:49,980
It's OK.
I don't want to upset anybody.

486
00:35:51,100 --> 00:35:55,360
He can stay. I'd like your input,
We'll discuss your case after the meeting.

487
00:35:57,190 --> 00:35:59,610
How about we get started?

488
00:36:12,620 --> 00:36:14,170
You ready?

489
00:36:14,290 --> 00:36:16,380
I'm gonna shame this bitch.

490
00:36:16,500 --> 00:36:19,510
Just state your case clean and easy.
You'll be the hero.

491
00:36:19,630 --> 00:36:22,010
OK, settle down.

492
00:36:23,130 --> 00:36:25,510
Now, has anyone tracked down
that witness?

493
00:36:28,010 --> 00:36:31,640
Oh, come on, people.
Someone needs to find something here.

494
00:36:33,310 --> 00:36:34,940
Lieutenant LaGuerta?

495
00:36:35,060 --> 00:36:37,860
Officer Morgan. I didn't recognize you
with your clothes on.

496
00:36:40,360 --> 00:36:44,070
I have an idea,
something in a different direction.

497
00:36:44,990 --> 00:36:47,030
An idea?

498
00:36:48,410 --> 00:36:50,240
Well, please, share it with us.

499
00:36:55,000 --> 00:36:56,830
Cell crystallization.

500
00:36:56,960 --> 00:36:58,210
Excuse me?

501
00:36:58,340 --> 00:37:00,590
A little more confidence, please.

502
00:37:03,010 --> 00:37:05,220
On the last victim,
I'd like to check and see

503
00:37:05,340 --> 00:37:10,850
if any refrigerated trucks
have been stolen in the last week or so.

504
00:37:12,180 --> 00:37:14,640
Refrigerated trucks
like ice-cream trucks?

505
00:37:19,190 --> 00:37:21,730
No, not ice-cream trucks.

506
00:37:21,860 --> 00:37:25,740
A refrigerated vehicle that could cause
that kind of tissue damage.

507
00:37:25,860 --> 00:37:29,280
A refrigerated truck that's mobile

508
00:37:29,410 --> 00:37:31,990
so he'll be harder to catch.

509
00:37:32,120 --> 00:37:37,210
A refrigerated truck
that might give us a lead.

510
00:37:39,750 --> 00:37:43,670
That's very interesting, very creative,
but let's keep looking for the witness.

511
00:37:43,800 --> 00:37:45,550
We know that he or she is out there.

512
00:37:45,680 --> 00:37:49,390
The interrupted cut proves
that there was an eyewitness.

513
00:37:49,510 --> 00:37:51,930
Now, somebody out there saw something,

514
00:37:52,060 --> 00:37:54,600
so let's concentrate
on finding that person, OK?

515
00:37:54,730 --> 00:37:57,310
- But...
- Just keep talking to all your hookers.

516
00:37:59,860 --> 00:38:01,520
That's all for today.

517
00:38:08,740 --> 00:38:11,080
What the fuck was I supposed to say?

518
00:38:11,200 --> 00:38:14,370
I'm only in here because the Captain said they
had to let me in.

519
00:38:14,500 --> 00:38:16,790
But he didn't say
they had to listen to you.

520
00:38:16,920 --> 00:38:18,330
Well, right again.

521
00:38:18,460 --> 00:38:21,130
So say adiÃ³s to my career.
I'm gonna die a meter maid.

522
00:38:21,250 --> 00:38:24,460
Stop it. Deb, there's another way.
Find the truck.

523
00:38:29,430 --> 00:38:32,510
Excuse me, Dexter...
My office, please.

524
00:38:41,270 --> 00:38:43,270
What the hell?

525
00:38:46,320 --> 00:38:47,860
What the fuck?

526
00:38:49,950 --> 00:38:51,820
Are you boning her?

527
00:38:52,870 --> 00:38:55,120
- No.
- Oh, my God!

528
00:38:55,250 --> 00:38:56,410
Deb, wait.

529
00:38:56,540 --> 00:38:58,410
Shut up.

530
00:39:01,790 --> 00:39:03,460
It had nothing to do with drugs.

531
00:39:03,590 --> 00:39:05,500
Lieutenant, this is a waste of our damn time.

532
00:39:05,630 --> 00:39:07,130
I think Sergeant Doakes is right.

533
00:39:07,260 --> 00:39:09,550
I read all the other forensic analysis.

534
00:39:09,680 --> 00:39:14,010
The cokehead murders had nothing to do with
cocaine. It was a crime of passion.

535
00:39:14,140 --> 00:39:16,520
The murderer came to kill
the woman, not the dealer.

536
00:39:16,640 --> 00:39:18,430
He did him quick
and got him out of the way.

537
00:39:18,560 --> 00:39:21,190
But he sure as hell took his time
slicing up that lady.

538
00:39:21,310 --> 00:39:25,570
You don't do that unless you have a close,
personal relationship with someone.

539
00:39:25,690 --> 00:39:28,530
Probably an ex-boyfriend.

540
00:39:28,650 --> 00:39:30,530
That's who I'd look for.

541
00:39:33,370 --> 00:39:34,370
OK.

542
00:39:35,410 --> 00:39:38,950
It's a bit of a push, but, Sergeant,
you should check it out.

543
00:39:47,670 --> 00:39:49,670
I'm watching you, motherfucker.

544
00:40:03,650 --> 00:40:06,230
Jaworski's been
coming here for weeks -

545
00:40:06,360 --> 00:40:08,650
likes to steal all the copper plumbing.

546
00:40:08,780 --> 00:40:10,780
There's good money in that.

547
00:40:11,820 --> 00:40:15,070
No security guards - that's good.

548
00:41:21,140 --> 00:41:22,810
- Talk.
- What do you mean?

549
00:41:22,930 --> 00:41:25,350
- I think you know what I mean.
- No.

550
00:41:25,480 --> 00:41:27,980
Oh, God!

551
00:41:28,110 --> 00:41:30,070
Talk to me about Jane Saunders.

552
00:41:31,940 --> 00:41:34,440
OK. I did her.

553
00:41:34,570 --> 00:41:37,530
- How?
- In a movie, snuff film.

554
00:41:38,240 --> 00:41:39,830
But I'm not sorry.

555
00:41:39,950 --> 00:41:41,410
Of course not.

556
00:41:43,040 --> 00:41:45,040
Now I'm not sorry, either.

557
00:42:07,400 --> 00:42:08,310
Hello?

558
00:42:08,440 --> 00:42:12,980
Hey. I'm sorry.

559
00:42:13,110 --> 00:42:16,610
I mean, I'm sorry
about the other night, but...

560
00:42:18,110 --> 00:42:21,870
Look, Dex,
I really, really need to see you.

561
00:42:21,990 --> 00:42:26,960
So can you come by later,

562
00:42:27,080 --> 00:42:29,290
you know, just for a little while?

563
00:42:29,420 --> 00:42:31,840
I mean, I'm really -

564
00:42:33,170 --> 00:42:36,130
All right.
What are you doing now?

565
00:42:36,670 --> 00:42:40,720
I'm just finishing up a little project,
but I'll come by later.

566
00:42:40,850 --> 00:42:42,180
OK, bye.

567
00:42:57,860 --> 00:43:00,410
All in all, it was a good night.

568
00:43:00,530 --> 00:43:04,200
One less amateur filmmaker
polluting the internet.

569
00:43:36,150 --> 00:43:37,860
No way.

570
00:45:13,500 --> 00:45:15,500
Give us a minute.

571
00:45:16,710 --> 00:45:18,540
Hanging in there?

572
00:45:18,670 --> 00:45:20,250
This will teach me to tailgate.

573
00:45:22,170 --> 00:45:24,670
- Let's go over this again.
- I'm all yours.

574
00:45:24,800 --> 00:45:25,880
So...

575
00:45:26,010 --> 00:45:27,930
All the ice trucks in Miami -

576
00:45:28,050 --> 00:45:30,060
bit of a coincidence, don't you think?

577
00:45:30,180 --> 00:45:31,470
Sure, during business hours.

578
00:45:31,600 --> 00:45:34,270
But this time of night,
a truck like that sticks out.

579
00:45:34,390 --> 00:45:38,650
- And you followed it.
- That's right.

580
00:45:38,770 --> 00:45:40,320
You never saw the driver?

581
00:45:40,440 --> 00:45:42,440
Just high beams and a flying head.

582
00:45:44,150 --> 00:45:47,740
So then he must have already had
the head with him in the front seat.

583
00:45:47,870 --> 00:45:51,030
That's weird.
Why would he keep it there?

584
00:45:51,160 --> 00:45:53,910
I don't know, so he could use
a carpool lane?

585
00:45:57,540 --> 00:45:59,080
It just seems odd.

586
00:45:59,210 --> 00:46:04,300
Your sister has this ice-truck theory,
and then here you are to back it up.

587
00:46:04,420 --> 00:46:06,970
She's good.
You should give her a chance.

588
00:46:08,140 --> 00:46:10,180
You know, you should call me Maria.

589
00:46:11,060 --> 00:46:14,180
But I'll tell you who's good - you are.

590
00:46:14,310 --> 00:46:17,390
Doakes picked up the killer
in the cokehead murders.

591
00:46:17,520 --> 00:46:19,810
You were right.
It was her boyfriend.

592
00:46:19,940 --> 00:46:22,610
Of course,
Doakes still hates you.

593
00:46:22,730 --> 00:46:23,730
Of course.

594
00:46:27,700 --> 00:46:29,780
Tell me, Dexter,

595
00:46:29,910 --> 00:46:31,910
how did you get to be so smart?

596
00:46:35,870 --> 00:46:37,500
Lots of sleep.

597
00:46:41,460 --> 00:46:43,420
Is it OK if I fill out that report tomorrow?

598
00:46:45,380 --> 00:46:47,590
Sure thing. You're tired.

599
00:46:50,260 --> 00:46:51,800
Good night, Lieutenant.

600
00:46:51,930 --> 00:46:53,810
I'll catch you later.

601
00:47:11,240 --> 00:47:12,820
It's been a while.

602
00:47:13,530 --> 00:47:14,990
I'm sorry.

603
00:47:15,120 --> 00:47:18,750
I was worried.
I didn't know what to do.

604
00:47:18,870 --> 00:47:20,290
I called in sick.

605
00:47:21,290 --> 00:47:22,960
I mean...

606
00:47:25,420 --> 00:47:26,630
Are you OK?

607
00:47:26,760 --> 00:47:28,550
I'm fine. I was just...

608
00:47:29,050 --> 00:47:32,970
I'm sorry.
There was another... You know.

609
00:47:41,020 --> 00:47:44,730
Well, the kids slept over next door.

610
00:47:46,030 --> 00:47:47,280
OK.

611
00:47:49,200 --> 00:47:51,610
Would you like to come in?

612
00:47:52,070 --> 00:47:53,780
OK.

613
00:48:08,510 --> 00:48:11,010
I don't want to lose you, Dex.

614
00:48:13,140 --> 00:48:14,840
OK, sure.

615
00:48:17,680 --> 00:48:18,680
And...

616
00:48:20,230 --> 00:48:22,640
Well, I want you.

617
00:48:24,020 --> 00:48:25,190
I mean...

618
00:48:35,200 --> 00:48:36,450
OK.

619
00:48:37,490 --> 00:48:38,490
Thanks.

620
00:48:40,120 --> 00:48:41,620
You're welcome.

621
00:49:03,520 --> 00:49:05,440
Do you mind?

622
00:49:05,560 --> 00:49:07,360
Um, no.

623
00:49:22,040 --> 00:49:26,500
- It could be the kids.
- Better get it, then.

624
00:49:30,760 --> 00:49:31,760
Hello?

625
00:49:33,550 --> 00:49:35,340
Cody.

626
00:49:35,470 --> 00:49:37,470
Cody, stop crying, sweetie.

627
00:49:40,430 --> 00:49:42,680
All right. I'll come get you.

628
00:49:46,770 --> 00:49:49,650
Cody just threw up
all over Colleen's couch.

629
00:49:51,780 --> 00:49:53,440
I gotta go get him.

630
00:49:58,990 --> 00:50:00,280
Tell me we're OK.

631
00:50:02,330 --> 00:50:03,450
Better than.

632
00:50:04,870 --> 00:50:05,790
OK.

633
00:50:05,920 --> 00:50:07,420
Go be a good mom.

634
00:50:27,310 --> 00:50:29,560
OK, that was close.

635
00:50:32,320 --> 00:50:34,530
I'll admit, making out with Rita was...

636
00:50:35,530 --> 00:50:37,320
interesting.

637
00:50:38,160 --> 00:50:41,660
But if I don't keep a lid on this,
it could be the end of us.

638
00:51:04,600 --> 00:51:06,810
I suppose I should be upset,

639
00:51:06,930 --> 00:51:08,690
even feel violated,

640
00:51:08,810 --> 00:51:10,270
but I'm not.

641
00:51:12,570 --> 00:51:13,860
No.

642
00:51:13,980 --> 00:51:15,650
In fact I think this is a friendly message,

643
00:51:15,780 --> 00:51:19,400
kind of like, "Hey, wanna play?"

644
00:51:20,450 --> 00:51:22,450
And, yes, I wanna play.

645
00:51:23,915 --> 00:51:26,747
I really, really do.

