Previously on Heroes...
Camera's ready for whatever.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
When we embrace
what lies within
our potential has no limit.
As far as you know,
that was attempt number one.
The future is filled
with promise.
- The present, rife with expectation.
- Whoosh!
But when we deny
our instinct...
and struggle against
our deepest urges...
- Are you on the list?
- Uncertainty begins.
My dad obviously doesn't
work in a paper factory.
I don't know what he does.
Where is he? Where's Sylar?
- I have no idea what you're talking about.
- Oh!
Where does this path lead?
I have no idea how you're pulling
this off but I swear to God,
I'm not gonna stop until I figure
it out. You understand me?
When will the changes end?
- Is this transformation a gift?
- I just wanna see my son!
- Or a curse?
- You don't anything about power.
And for those who fear
what lies ahead...
- I can't control it.
- Let me help you, Peter.
The most important
question of all...
Can we ever really
change what we are?
Aahh!
Hey!
What are...
What are you doing? Hey!
You...
- You can see me?
- You...
Nobody can see me!
I'm invisisible!
Who are you?
How can you see me?
I don't know,
I can just do what you can do.
Fantastic.
- One of those.
- One of those?
What do you mean,
you know someone else like me?
Hey wait, where are you going?
You need to explain this.
Look... I saw you.
I saw you in my dream.
Who are you?
Me? I'm no one.
I'm the Invisible Man.
I'm Claude Rains.
Now get away from me.
Forget you ever saw me.
Yeah, but you know.
What's happening to me?
What is this? What...
Listen, I found you.
I need you to help me.
- Why'd I want to do that?
- Because we're in danger.
This entire city is in danger.
It was in my dream.
People die. We die.
I don't know when,
but it happens.
Then you'd better leave town.
Hey, where are you going?
You can't hide from me.
I'm the Invisible Man.
I could walk around the
corner and disappear forever.
Yeah, but... but I can see you.
I'm gonna follow you.
Smarter men than you have
tried and have paid for it.
Stay away from me.
And don't follow me.
Chapter 13 - The Fix
Um...
Red elephant with blue stripes?
Pin stripe or plaid?
Honey, I can't see your thoughts.
I can only hear 'em.
Huh.
Oh, I have a good one.
Wait, the ratty curtains
in our old apartment?
Ugh! How do you do that?
I'm not sure what's happening.
His vitals are
extremely irregular.
After all we've done to him,
I'm not surprised.
Keep him stabilized.
There is another option.
Our instructions are to keep him alive.
Do whatever it takes.
If he crashes,
you bring him back.
Again and again.
When he dies it'll be on my terms,
not on his.
Clear?
But I'm only two minutes over.
- That'll be 48.50.
- For one-day parking?
Hey, you want your
car back or not?
Darn.
My power is lost
until I get the sword.
I focused the samurai
Kensei's power.
It will do the same for me.
But Hiro, if you have no power,
how can we steal the sword?
I will find a way.
That sword is my destiny.
A samurai's weapon must
be used with honor.
And respect.
This sword has many
lessons to teach.
Swords  are for killing.
That's why they're sharp.
Maybe I use the sword
to kill bomb-man.
Is it my destiny
to kill this man?
- Hiro, wait!
- What is it?
That man, waiting by our car...
He doesn't look very friendly.
He has a gun.
Do something!
I have no power!
Help, there's a man chasing us!
Uh-oh.
Dr.  Suresh?
- Do you remember me?
- Nathan Petrelli.
You yelled at my car.
Yes, we met under
unfortunate circumstances.
I believe I came off
as a deranged lunatic.
You mind if I come in?
I'm looking for my
brother, Doctor.
- That makes two of us.
- I'm sorry?
I've been leaving messages
for him for two days now.
Guess I'm at the
wrong place then.
I need to find him.
- The last time I heard, he was in Texas.
- He made it home barely.
Barely alive,
and now he's run off again.
Afraid that he's
gonna somehow...
hurt people.
Doctor, I, uh...
possibly you could explain to me.
What the hell's
happening to him?
Before his death,
my father compiled a list.
36 individuals who carry a genetic
marker which he discovered.
A marker which he theorized gave
these people certain abilities.
- And my brother's one of them?
- As are you.
- I didn't come here to talk about me.
- Fair enough.
Peter's specific DNA
allows for a blend.
Like colors in a mosaic.
Resequencing itself to mimic the
abilities of those around him.
- Like a chameleon?
- More like a sponge.
It's precisely why I've
been studying him.
Could his condition become dangerous
to himself or to other people?
If he absorbs too much,
or comes into contact
with an unstable ability,
then most definitely yes.
Can you fix it?
Alter his genes somehow?
Theoretically, it is possible to
develop a specific site inhibitor.
- But look, I will know more when we find him.
- We?
Doctor, the last
thing my brother needs
is somebody feeding
into his paranoia.
But thank you.
Mr. Petrelli.
Of all the people on that list
your brother may be
the most important.
If I can find him, study him,
then I can do more
than help him.
I can help all of you.
Now, give me a minute,
and I'll get my coat.
- I told you not to follow me.
- I need help.
You live up here?
You're not a fast learner,
eh, mate?
I took care of a man
who owned this building.
-  His name was Charles Deveaux.
- Never heard of him.
You don't think that's strange?
I worked here.
The place where you live
and keep your birds.
I don't keep anything.
I let 'em out once a day,
they come back.
Sounds like free will to me.
I need to learn how
to control this.
- Like you do.
- What are you talking about?
It can't be controlled.
There has to be some way.
If... if I don't,
New York explodes.
Okay? I explode.
An exploding man,
where'd you get that idea?
My dreams.
This place.
I found you for a reason.
I think you're the one that has
to teach me how to stop this.
There's no such thing.
No teaching.
No Sunday school
for the special.
What I can do, you can't learn.
You wake up in the morning,
it's there.
If you've got thin soup,
then that's your supper.
Sorry, mate,
that's the way it is.
I'm trying not to die.
There's got to be
something you can do.
I can kill you
myself right now.
Solve your exploding
problem here.
Maybe that's why you dreamt me.
Don't bother looking for me.
You won't find me here again.
So what exactly am
I looking for here?
Anything my dad doesn't
want us to find.
You said you're good
with computers.
I make movies on my laptop.
No, you're good at
finding those holes
in the internet password
protected nanny blocker stuff.
Shouldn't you be watching the
doorway if your dad walks in?
He's at work.
It's just you, me,
and Mr. Muggles.
There's nothing.
- There's not even any porn.
- Gross.
I'm serious,
this thing is totally clean.
No.
My dad lied to me
about my entire life.
My biological parents.
My ability.
You can't just hide
things like that.
There's gotta be
something on there.
If your dad's the guy
you're describing,
I don't think he's gonna keep his
secrets on the family computer.
- Shut it down.
- Okay, okay.
I thought you were at work.
Forgot my cell.
Zachary.
What a nice surprise
to see you here.
Yeah, it's biology class.
We're lab partners now.
Yeah we were just doing some
research on the internet.
- We have a presentation on...
- The manatee.
Also known as the sea cow.
Do you mind if I talk to Claire
in private for a moment?
You can wait in my room.
It's upstairs.
Second door on the right.
- So. You and Zach?
- Ms. Gomez stuck us together.
Must be some social
experiment or something.
- Worst day ever.
- Claire.
- What?
- You two used to be friends.
You might find you
actually get along.
Nice save.
Thanks.
So what now?
I need to talk to someone
who has some answers.
He said if I needed him,
I should hang these outside my window.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Okay, wait.
You're saying that the guy
with the glasses actually...
- abducted you?
- Yes.
- And he... he did this to you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, and I gotta figure
out how he did this.
And I'm gonna take him and
everybody with him down.
That Haitian guy, all of 'em.
Matt,  I... I'm sorry.
I've gotta say,
this is all a little nuts.
I mean,
first the whole psychic thing.
And now...
Come on, you're telling me
you're about to run off
and chase some guy who works
in a paper factory in Texas.
They did this to me, Janice.
I need to find them.
I have to figure out
what this is all about.
- Maybe you could call the F.B.I.
- No, I can't.
I can't go to the F.B.I.
They think I'm crazy.
I... I gotta get ready.
I got a review
hearing this morning.
I'm about to get my ass handed
to me by three captains.
Yes, I will call
the plumber today.
Are you always
gonna be in my head?
Well, I can't
control this thing.
You can't or you won't?
The painting is valuable.
Maybe they're
trying to steal it.
But if we don't deliver
it to Linderman...
we will never get the sword.
How long do we stay under here?
Until they are gone.
Who are these people?
And why is everyone
always chasing us?
Because I'm special.
Well I'm not special.
And I'm tired of
getting chased.
I'm going to have oil
all over my back...
because  of you!
You can surrender.
But I will never surrender.
A hero never gives up.
Did you feel something?
This way!
Hiro! Hiro!
Who are you?
Hiro!
Hey! Hello!
Let me go!
I am very special.
I offer myself in trade.
Release un-special Ando,
and I go with you. Okay?
Good deal, yes. Oh!
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, you no like the deal?
You came back for me.
This is how we roll.
Who are you?
Why did you take that off me?
I'm Dr. Witherson.
I'm a psychiatrist.
And I've been assigned
to your case.
No, you shouldn't be in here.
It's not safe.
If it makes you feel
more comfortable,
we can put the restraints
back on while we talk.
You don't understand.
The drugs keep her weak.
That jacket can't stop her.
- Give me a shot.
- You mean Jessica?
- How do you know her name?
- I read your file.
I know all about your past.
Your marriage.
Your website. Your sister.
Her accident?
Her name was Jessica too,
isn't that right?
Give me another shot.
You know, I haven't made
an official diagnosis yet.
But it seems like
we're dealing with
a classic case of multiple
personality disorder.
You're wasting your time.
- Just go.
- You know...
It's okay. It's okay.
It makes sense, facing the kind
of sentence that you're facing,
that you want to give up.
You think your life is over,
but it's not.
You can still make something
of yourself in here.
People do it all the time.
But you gotta want help.
And yeah,
it can take years to integrate
a multiple personality,
but if you let me,
I can help you.
What I am, you can't fix.
Just give me another
shot and go away.
No.
Aww, man.
I'm trying to pay this rent.
You know,
it would really help if you...
Yeah.
No, it's...
It's cool, it's cool.
I...  know you
would if you could.
Thanks anyway.
So have you seen my
lunchbox or not?
I don't know.
- It's wherever you left it.
- I left it in the car.
- Then that's where it is.
- Okay, so where's the car?
Car's in the shop, Micah.
- So you lost my lunchbox?
- I didn't lose anything.
- It's in the car.
- Fine, you make bad lunch anyways.
Micah!
Micah.
It's not my fault you can't
keep track of your own stuff.
Mom always put my lunch in my
backpack every single morning.
- Well, I'm not your mom.
- Yeah, that's for sure.
Micah, this isn't easy.
Well, it wasn't easy
for mom either.
But she always found a way
of making some money, Dad.
I'm late for school.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous this is?
You said if I had an emergency,
to hang the chimes outside my window.
- Is your father becoming suspicious?
- No.
And it's kind of a problem.
Every word out of
my mouth is a lie.
I have to laugh, and smile,
and look him in the eye.
My own father,
it's breaking my heart.
Would you prefer I
took your memory?
I need to know that one
thing in my life is real.
Do you know who my
real parents are?
Of your father, I know nothing.
And my mother?
Only that she died in an explosion
here in Texas 14 years ago.
My mother died?
Are you sure?
Your father told
me many years ago.
He had no reason to lie.
This is the last conversation
we have about this.
Now you need to go back home,
and forget about
your real parents.
The groomer missed one of Mr.
Muggles' nails.
I'm gonna run him back by
the shop before they close.
Don't want you scratching
up my wood floors.
No, we don't.
Where's Claire?
She's at the library getting
books for some biology report.
I cannot believe how many
projects they lay on these kids.
I don't know how she holds
everything in that head of hers.
No, I don't.
You're still worried about her,
aren't you?
She's had a rough
couple of weeks.
Well, besides a
little memory loss...
- I'd say she's doing just peachy.
- Do you really?
It's Lyle you need
to worry about.
That boy is getting so
absent-minded lately.
Yes, he is. We'll be back.
- Yes.
- I did everything I could.
He's dead.
Well, that's less than ideal.
What do you want me
to do with the body?
Get it ready for shipping.
I'll be in later.
There was a fire in an apartment
house 14 years ago in Kermit, Texas.
Kermit, why does that
sound so familiar?
'Cause of the frog?
Check it out.
A 21-year-old woman was killed in
the explosion. Meredith Gordon.
Oh, my God.
Also killed in the fire was
her 18-month-old daughter.
Claire, I think that's you.
But I didn't die.
Somebody thought you did.
What am I supposed
to do with all this?
You may still have a
real family out there.
Maybe you got an aunt or a rich,
eccentric uncle.
Great, an uncle.
Who knows, one of them might even
know who your real father is.
Well...
Surprised you left out
the flying saucers.
Officer Parkman,
is this really the statement
you want entered into
your public record?
That a paper salesman
from Odessa, Texas
is currently harboring a
super-powered serial killer,
and that you raided his
warehouse on a hunch?
Sir, all I've ever wanted to
do was protect and serve.
- To help my fellow man.
- I'll ask you again.
Do you want your future
as a police officer
to be decided by what
you've written here?
Just say "Yes," so I can
flush you down the toilet.
At this time, I'd like to recant
my previous written statement.
I made the whole thing up.
- Why did you do that?
- I failed to make detective three times, sir.
And, uh...
Quite frankly I was sick
of directing traffic,
handing out speeding tickets,
and I...
I wanted to look like a hero.
I am sorry for any shame that I
may have brought this department.
Great, a liar, not a nutcase.
Officer Parkman,
pending review of your case
by a civilian ombudsman
and union representative,
we're enforcing a six-month
suspension of your active duties.
We're gonna need your
gun and your badge.
Janice.
Matt, will you come upstairs?
- Oh, Matt!
- What?
Now are you gonna
fix the pipes?
Get me a wrench.
Where are you taking us?
Why isn't he talking to us?
Maybe...
he is not the Big Boss.
Tell your boss I'm on
very important mission.
I know all about your so-called mission
to save the world, Mr. Nakamura.
You think you have a power,
and that you can use it
to make a difference.
You are...
WRONG.
Who are you?
I work for someone...
who has true power.
A man who knows
what you're up to.
And wants you...
to stop.
Two first class tickets.
- Non-stop to Tokyo.
- First class?
Ando, do not be tempted.
Those tickets are a test...
of our devotion to our mission.
You cannot bribe a hero.
My heart is true.
My spirit unbreakable.
When I meet your Big Boss,
I will tell him the same thing!
Oh-- they won't like that.
Not one bit.
You aren't answering
your cell phone.
We've been looking
everywhere for you.
- What's he doing here?
- Making up for past mistakes.
I'd like to help you.
- You're leaving town?
- Yeah.
Yeah, think I'd get away
for a little while.
What, be a danger
to somebody else?
There's gotta be
another way, Peter.
- Let me help you.
- You can't.
- But maybe I can.
- How?
We can find that
answer together.
If you allow me to test you,
- with more research...
- Shh...
You can cure me?
You're gonna fix all of this?
It'll take study and time...
Time... I don't have time
to be your guinea pig.
- I have a plane to catch.
- I'm not letting you run away, Peter.
So what,
you gonna call the cops on me, Nathan?
You gonna tell them your
brother's going nuclear?
I could have my mentally ill
brother detained for his own safety.
I know you want to help me.
You're my big brother.
And you fix everything.
But you can't...
- You can't fix this one this time.
- I can.
Look, let's just sit down,
and we can figure this out.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
Peter!
- Where'd he go?
- Who?
You're supposed to
watch the door.
My God, did he just...?
Get down to the airport, and make
sure he doesn't get away this time.
Yes, sir.
Thanks. Help yourself.
- This your place?
- Yeah.
Guy with family connections like
yours could do a lot better.
Left the family business.
I'm a nurse now.
Nurse who's an empath,
very cute.
"Empath," what's that mean?
Means you're a pain
in my ass, mate.
Yeah, but you followed me.
Yeah, well,
I'm not very much of a people person,
but I'm certain I'm not
gonna let you kill 'em all.
You seem pretty sure about that
pending apocalypse of yours.
Yeah, not unless you
help me control it.
You don't know what you're asking,
what you have to go through.
You might want to
reconsider dying.
- Hell of a lot easier.
- I can handle it.
Yeah, that'shat they all say.
"They"?
How many... how many people
have you taught before me?
Come on, mate,
I'll steal us a cab.
You coming or not?
Uh, so they suspended
me for six months.
Oh, Matt.
I actually thought this ability
was gonna be a good thing.
And now I'm unemployed, and
about to lose my marriage.
You haven't lost that.
- Not yet anyway.
- Thanks, that's encouraging.
Look, we...
We just have to
trust each other.
I can do that.
Now...
So I'm gonna give
you one more freebie.
What am I thinking?
We're having a baby?
We're having a baby!
Nik, what have
they done to you?
- If they catch you...
- They won't.
Come closer.
What is it?
Your shirt.
It smells like home.
How's Micah?
- Is he okay?
- He's fine.
It's just...
I can't do this, Nik.
Not alone.
I thought I could.
I thought I could handle everything,
but I...
D.L., you can't do this to me.
I gotta find a way to
get you outta here.
This is crazy.
I can walk in here any
time I want, right?
I should be able
to get you out.
I am gonna be in here
for a long time.
The rest of my life maybe.
- You need to get used to that.
- Your son needs you.
Damn it, D.L.,
that is not fair.
I am counting on you.
You know that I need
to stay in here.
I need you, Nik.
We need you.
He's having such a
hard time without you.
You need to talk to him.
You need to be honest.
He needs boundaries
and a strong hand.
It's not too late.
You need to go.
Go.
There's only 12 people in Kermit
with the last name "Gordon."
So far, only three.
None of them have ever
heard of Meredith.
- Claire?
- Hold on.
- I'll call you back.
- Claire?
Sorry, I was just, uh,
talking to Zach
about our report.
Well, Molly in accounting is
married to a marine biologist,
and he said that...
You're already on top of it.
Did you know that all three varieties of
manatee are vulnerable to extinction?
No, I didn't.
Is everything all right?
We haven't talked in a while.
Actually, there is something.
Yeah?
The bears.
My stuffed bears.
I think it's time
for them to migrate.
I'm almost 16, Dad,
bears and talks can't last forever.
Whether you're 16,
or 32, or 64...
- When I'm 64, you'll...
- I will be there for you.
Always.
Don't you think it's time I learn
how to deal with my own problems?
Well, dinner's in an hour.
And, uh, do me a favor. No...
No extinction talk
at the table.
You know how sensitive
your mother is.
You have a change of heart?
My son.
My family needs me. So...
I want you to understand that
there are no guarantees.
I don't care.
I need to get rid of Jessica.
So you know what might help?
If I could talk to her.
All right?
- Isn't there another way?
- No.
I'm afraid in cases like these,
it is imperative that
I have interaction
with all aspects of the
patient's personality.
- Honey, let me talk to her.
- No!
You can't.
So let me put it to you this way.
Either I speak with Jessica,
or you may not see your little
boy for a very, very long time.
But...
Wait.
Micah, where have you been?
I was worried to death.
I was just out walking around.
Sit down.
Micah, we gotta
figure this out.
'Cause the truth is your
mom's not coming home,
and I'm having a
really hard time here.
I can't get a job.
I can barely pay the rent.
I've never felt much
like a man in my life.
My papa never taught me,
but I want to be
a good dad to you.
I'm gonna need your help.
We gotta pull together
and make this work.
- 'Cause it's just you and me.
- I'm sorry, Dad.
I can try harder.
Maybe this will help.
Where'd you get...
Where'd you get this from?
You know how you and
Mom have a secret?
Well, I have a secret too.
Where are we?
Your secret headquarters?
You let us go now?
That's up to the boss.
Hiro, please.
I don't want to meet the Boss.
I want to go home.
Tell them what
they want to hear.
Do not be afraid, my friend.
I shall never betray you.
No matter what.
Father?
GULP!
Hello?
Hi, I'm looking for someone
related to Meredith Gordon.
She died in an
explosion 14 years ago.
I've been calling everyone in Kermit
with the last name of "Gordon."
- Any chance that you're related to her?
- Who is this?
My name's Claire Bennet,
I'm calling from Odessa.
What... What is this about?
And how do you know the
name "Meredith Gordon"?
I think she was my mom.
Is this some kind of joke?
No, ma'am.
Well, Meredith only
had one daughter, and
she died in the fire.
That's kind of what
I'm trying to say is...
I didn't die.
I think I'm her and I'm looking for any
information I can find about my mom.
Well, then you made the right call.
This is her.
Mom?
Yeah.
How is Claire?
Thanks to Raceman for the Transcript
Subtitles Made By The Bloc Team
www.tvsubtitles.net