Last december,
Heroes gave us a look into the future.
But that was just
the beginning.
There were strangers whow
discovered extraordinary abilities.
I think I can fly.
Unti they realized
they were not alone.
We're all connected.
With the discovery
of one thing.
The list.
The invicible cheerleader
on a mission to find
her birth parents.
I think I'm old enough for you
to tell me who my
real parents are.
The mother with an alterego
makes a sacrifice to
protect her child.
- Can I help you, ma'am?
- Yeah, you can arrest me.
Your mom is not coming home.
And tonight the search
for new heroes begins.
How can you see me?
This entire city is in danger.
It's me.
Heroes, the next
chapter begins now.
You get your mind
read yet, Niki?
Up to me, I'd leave you in
the box here a few more weeks.
Even animals like you
get a lawyer visit.
You just move real slow-like,
you hear me?
Nice and easy.
Show me your hands!
Come on, get 'em up! Go on.
Let's go.
Union Wells High School
opens its doors today
for the first time since
16-year-old Jackie Wilcox
was brutally murdered
during a homecoming game
two weeks ago.
Teachers and students
wrestle with how to remember
the slain cheerleader,
while still trying to move on.
This is Angela Braumstead,
Channel 5 News.
Look at all those reporters.
You don't have to
worry about the press.
They're not allowed
on school grounds.
I'm more worried
about the other kids.
They're gonna want to ask
me questions about it.
Well... You don't have
to tell them anything.
Well, good,
'cause I don't really remember much.
I know that's supposed to be
post-traumatic stress or whatever,
but nothing? Nothing at all?
Memory's a funny thing. I think
it's a blessing that
you don't remember.
- Where'd you find me?
- What do you mean?
The night Jackie got killed.
You said you found
me by the stadium?
You were scared to death.
You were traumatized.
You just wanted to go home.
I don't remember.
Thanks.
I guess I better go.
Not so dangerous anymore,
are we, Mr. Sylar?
We've gone over
every strand of code,
trying to find the code on switches
that identify his aptitudes.
Other than telekinesis,
we're drawing a blank.
Has he responded to
the glycimerine?
Given him enough to
kill an elephant.
Nothing. We're no closer.
If we keep up at this rate,
he'll be dead by tomorrow.
After what he did to Eden,
he'd deserve it.
Unfortunately, they
haven't authorized that.
He stays alive.
You're just gonna
have to dig deeper.
You better be right
about this, Parkman.
Go, go, go!
Come on, come on, let's go.
We swept this entire place.
There's nothing here but paper.
- Did you check the basement?
- Yeah!
- Stairwells?
- Mm-hmm. More paper.
Hey. Where is he?
Where is he? Where's Sylar?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
He's not here, Parkman.
Nice going.
Oops.
The Tyrannosaurus Rex was a huge,
meat-eating dinosaur
that lived during the
late Cretaceous Period
about 65 to 85
million years ago.
Look out!
If we could go back in time,
there's no telling what
wonders we'd find...
I wish.
All the books I read
said the sword is here.
So what?
We finally make it to NewYork...
and all you care
about is a sword.
What about your mission?
I need my powers
for the mission!
But the bomb is going
off on November 8th.
We only have 3 more weeks.
I know but ever since
I lost Charlie...
my powers have gotten
weaker and weaker.
My sword will
restore my powers.
It's not your sword.
We found it!
He's burning up.
Persistent idiopathic fever.
Means  they have no
idea what's wrong.
Find the best doctors in the world,
just to have them tell me
they don't know what they're
doing in four different languages.
His heart-- they don't know
how much more he can take.
26 years old,
he's gonna die of a heart attack?
- He's not gonna die, Ma.
- He will unless I do something.
Why don't you just let the
doctors do what they do?
I wish I knew what
was going on in there.
Just before he passed out,
he said he, uh...
He felt he was absorbing
too many powers.
Peter wanted to
see that painting.
After I told you not to let him,
you knew he was
gonna  follow that thing
headfirst all the way to Texas.
He's my brother and I love him,
but we both know he shouldn't
have even been there.
- It was important to him.
- You really believe all this crap?
Future paintings?
- The end of the world?
- I know he believes it.
And I believe in him.
Fine. Then show me.
I've been in this damn
hospital room for two weeks,
waiting for
something to happen.
I'll be damned if I'm gonna sit
around and watch my brother die.
Take me to the artist.
I want to see what's
worth all this.
I love you, man.
There.
Okay, your first mistake?
Never put the peanut butter
in the refrigerator.
Mom always keeps it
at room temperature.
Well, your dad's
got his own style.
- I see that.
- It still tastes good.
Hey.
What happened to you?
Did you get in a
fight at school today?
It's nothing. Just some jerks.
Well, what happened?
Dad, they called
Mom a psycho killer.
I know,
you can lecture me about not fighting.
No. No, I...
I know how hard it
is without her.
And I wish it could be easier.
But we gonna make it.
You enjoy that. I'll be back.
I believe you were
expecting me?
The name is Malski.
Aaron Malski.
I take it you have it here?
Have the charges
against me been dropped?
Your wife's confession
took care of most of that.
Her pointing out where to
find the bodies helped too.
As for the other charges,
consider yourself a free man,
Mr. Hawkins.
So no more looking
over my shoulder?
Only if you wish to
see where you've been.
So that's it.
Linderman leaves me
and my family alone?
Oh, I wouldn't
bank on that, no.
That was the deal.
You got back your $2 million.
There is no deal, Mr. Hawkins,
unless Mr.
Linderman says there's a deal.
You  took something of his.
And he reserves the right to
let you make that up to him.
Believe me.
You'll be the first to find out
when he chooses to
call in that debt.
You have a nice day now.
Takezo Kensai.
My father used to tell me
stories about him before bed.
He was a wild savage
with great power.
All of Japan feared him.
Until one day he found...
a sacred sword
frozen in the snow.
From the moment
Kensai held it...
it focused all his strength.
He said the sword let
him control his power.
And so he became
a great leader.
A hero.
That symbol here.
It's a combination
of characters.
"Great talent"...
"Godsend".
"Great talent"... "Godsend".
Like your power.
See?
I'm like him.
The sword will give me...
the control over
my power I need.
It's my sacred object.
With it my powers will return
and I can fulfill my destiny.
What exactly are you saying?
I'm saying we take it.
We?
I'm glad the Bureau
finally decided
to take the list I
offered seriously.
Too many people showing
up dead or missing.
If you didn't have a record
showing you were in India
when some of these
people were killed,
you and I would be having a
very different conversation.
- How fortunate for me, then.
- Mm-hmm.
You say, uh...
your father compiled this list?
Yes, he was a geneticist.
All the people on the list
share a unique genetic marker
that he was able to map and track
using the Human Genome Project.
Uh-huh.
I've been trying to locate them.
To warn them?
- About this man Sylar?
- Yes, the man who killed my father.
I see. Well, we ran the name.
Nothing. Clearly an alias.
But we did follow up on
another name you said
was on the list.
Sarah Ellis?
Yes, I tried to locate
her in Los Angeles,
but she wasn't at any
of her known addresses,
and no,
I've never met her before.
Are you sure?
That's Sarah Ellis?
I know her by a different name.
Eden McCain.
She, uh--
lives across the hall right there.
She's been gone for a few weeks.
Is there a problem?
She turned up three days ago.
Well... what was
left of her, anyway.
What?
Yeah, they pulled her out
of Lake Ramsey in Sudbury.
Hundred miles out of Ontario.
Gunshot wound to the head.
Local law wrote it
up as a suicide.
The, uh...
last I heard from her,
she said she had something
to confess to me.
- You say she was your friend?
- She--
I don't know what she was.
The guy who you were
just talking to
- has Sylar in this building.
- No, Parkman.
- Yes, he--
- He doesn't.
- There's nothing in here but paper.
- But we didn't look everywhere.
Maybe-- there's a secret room.
Somewhere. Okay? Maybe--
And maybe I can whistle The
Star-Spangled Banner out of my ass.
We are lucky he hasn't threatened
to sue us for this stunt.
You want to know what's on
this tape he just handed me?
You.
Caught on the parking
lot surveillance camera.
What, you didn't think
anyone would notice
a  guy sitting in the same
car every day for two weeks?
Do you have any idea
the position you have
put this Bureau in?
- I was following a hunch.
- Whose hunch?
My hunch? The Bureau's hunch?
- Matt's hunch.
- He abducted people.
He abducted me!
He abducted Ted Sprague!
Sure, the guy with
the radioactive hands?
Well, it all makes
perfect sense.
I am going to make sure
you are benched for this.
- What, that's it?
- Obviously.
We both know he's in here.
I know--
Do we?
Because all I know is that I have wasted
the last three weeks of
my life on the crazy idea
that you can hear
people's thoughts.
I liked you, Matt.
I felt sorry for you.
And maybe that
clouded my judgment.
But now I need to
get back to reality.
And you should do the same.
Go home, Matt. We're done.
Hey.
Hey-- listen to me.
I have no idea how you're pulling
this off, but I swear to God
I'm not gonna stop until I figure
it out, you understand me?
Good luck with that.
- Zach.
- Hey, this is a public place.
Are you sure you can
be seen here with me?
Why not?
Right, I forgot.
You've been body-snatched.
Look,  I just want to talk.
Hey, I'm sorry about Jackie.
I know she was your
best friend and all.
No, I actually discovered that
someone else was my best friend.
But I lost him too.
What happened to
you at Homecoming?
I can't remember.
Can't remember a lot of things lately.
Yeah, it's, uh...
That's funny, 'cause lately,
I can't remember...
Must be something in
the water, right?
Zach, look at me.
Do you feel like we
could be friends?
Us?
No.
We wouldn't play well together.
I gotta tell you, Ms. Sanders,
the outbursts are not helping.
Kind of getting
tired of them myself.
Look, I just want to
do my time in peace.
Yeah, about that.
It seems the D.A. is going to
file for special circumstances
in the homicides.
They're gonna seek the death penalty.
- Death penalty?
- Look, I know it's a long shot.
But it might help if
you cooperated a little.
And how am I
supposed to do that?
The $2 million.
Things might go a little smoother
if you tell the
police where it is.
I've told you.
I don't know anything about that.
Who are you trying to fool?
You know exactly where it is.
I'm sorry?
He's right, Niki.
We should tell them.
Stop it!
Don't pay any attention to her.
Pay attention to who?
God, who am I gonna have to
screw to get out of this place?
I said stop it!
What is this?
What's it look like, dipstick?
Wait, you're going psych on me?
If that's what it takes.
Multiple personality disorders
are a real hard sell.
When I want your opinion,
I will ask for it.
Just get us a damn shrink.
I'm not crazy.
No, I'm not crazy.
Don't listen to her.
Please, I'm telling
you the truth.
Of course you are.
No, don't listen to her.
Listen to me, please.
- I'm not lying to you.
- Of course you're not.
I'm telling you
the truth! Don't--
Which way to gift store?
Thank you.
There's security everywhere.
Stealing isn't exactly part
of Bushido code, you know.
It's one antique.
If I don't have my powers...
this whole museum
will explode anyway.
It's a good deal for them.
What happened?
Did  you get it?
No. My power. It's not working.
Maybe you need the sword
to steal the sword.
Good enough.
Hiro?
That was amazing!
You did it, Hiro!
Never doubt me again.
With this sword...
there's no limit to
what I can accomplish.
Our life of legend begins.
It's a fake!
Linderman?
I'm gonna take it back.
Isaac was obsessed, ranting about
a bomb coming to explode New York.
The painting on the floor.
Yeah, and he just left.
Someone came and
took his paintings.
And I don't understand.
He's been gone a few weeks.
Then I came back.
Isaac.
I'm waiting for
the shock to clear
so I can tell if
you're glad to see me.
Well... I'm just
going to, uh...
You look...
you look healthy.
I got back a few days ago.
I wasn't sure when to call you.
I was in a clinic.
I...
I barely remember
any of it, but
when I woke up, I was in Texas.
And I was clean.
- That's great.
- I mean it.
I don't need the drugs anymore,
I can paint without it.
Well, I'm glad for you.
I'm only alive because
of you, Simone.
I still love you.
All right, uh, this painting...
That's like he's exploding.
Like he's a bomb.
How did you know about this?
Did you talk to
my brother Peter?
I painted what I saw.
The last thing Peter said
before he collapsed was that he
was the cause of the explosion.
Look, I may not get everything.
That's fine, but this...
I mean,
these things can't be connected.
And the world doesn't
work like this.
Mr. Isaac. Bad news, sword not there.
It was replica.
Original owned by
man named Linderman.
Did he say Linderman?
Flying Man!
Save the cheerleader,
save the world.
What does that even mean?
Have I been saved,
or do I still need saving?
You're saved for
the time being.
I wanna talk to Peter Petrelli.
You're not supposed to
remember Peter Petrelli.
He's being watched.
If you try to contact him,
your father will know.
You have to give me something.
Nothing in my life
has been real.
My dad obviously doesn't
work in a paper factory.
I don't know what he does.
And what about my
biological parents?
He didn't find them through
the adoption agency, did he?
They work for your father.
Like I do.
Everything has been a lie.
The only person I could trust was Zach,
and you took him from me.
That was your father's doing.
Not mine.
Then give him back
his memories.
I don't wanna be alone.
You are not alone, Claire.
And I cannot give your
friend back his memories.
It's not how my gift works.
Your gift?
Is that what you call it?
What do you call it?
My own private freak show.
What you can do,
what I can do,
that is God.
Respect it accordingly.
The bomb,
it comes from the street.
Destroy everything,
everything turn into dust. Poof!
Your English is a lot better.
- I met a waitress in Texas.
- Oh, yeah?
- She teach me many things.
- Good for you.
So, uh, look, I can't believe
I'm about to say this, you...
teleported here...
back from the future.
Yes, my power let me come
back here so I can stop it.
Right.
- Because "you hero."
- You will help too.
Me? What makes you so sure?
You're flying man. Whoosh!
- Would you keep it down?
- Whoosh.
What do you think it is that
makes this bomb thing go off?
Don't know... probably bad guy?
- Bad guy?
- Yes.
- Like villain.
- What's that?
- Villain.
- Villain?
- Vee.
- Vee-yun.
Like the guy in the painting?
You think a human being can
actually cause an explosion?
I have power, you have power.
- Maybe he has power too.
- Bad guy.
- We must stop him.
- I think I can help.
Somewhere in the Nevada desert.
We've been here before.
You, me, the video camera.
Is it at all familiar?
What are you doing, auditioning
for America's Next Top Model?
You made that joke
the first time.
Look, just keep the
camera on me, okay?
- Why don't you just use a tripod?
- I can't do this by myself.
And I know you can keep a secret,
you did.
You did,
until you forgot what it was.
When we were best friends.
You ready?
Claire, hold on a second.
I'm sure you told me this...
before, but, um, why are we
videotaping this? Whatever this is.
Actually, I didn't
tell you that before.
The first time I did this,
I did it to show my parents.
My real parents.
I wanted them to see what I was.
I thought they could
help me understand.
But I don't think I'm
ever gonna meet them.
They may not even
be alive anymore.
- So why do you wanna tape it now?
- For me.
So I never forget what I am.
No matter what happens to me.
Look, just don't
freak out, okay?
- I won't.
- You said that last time.
Camera's ready for whatever.
Okay, I'm ready.
Keep the camera on me.
What are you doing?
Aah!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God-- Claire!
This is Claire Bennett.
And as far as you know,
that was attempt number one.
I don't know how much
longer I'm gonna be here.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
They're sending me
to the psych ward.
For an evaluation
with a shrink.
She's here. Jessica.
She came out, she
tried to escape,
she hurt one of the guards.
Well, maybe a shrink can
help you deal with her.
- Get rid of her.
- This isn't in my head, D.L.
She is real.
I should've never
let you do this, Nik,
get yourself thrown in here.
I shoulda kept that
money to help you out.
No. You had to give it back,
or else this would never be over.
Let me talk to Micah.
I want you to come home.
I know, sweetie. But I can't.
It's hard to
understand right now.
But I hope that
one day you will.
Your daddy,
he's gonna take real good
care of you while I'm gone.
I need you to be the strong one
because I'm not strong right now, okay?
Mom, that's not fair.
That's my son.
Can I just give him a hug?
Just for a second, I promise.
Baby, it's all right.
It's all right.
No, he needs me.
He needs me.
Just let me hold him.
- Stay right there.
- He needs me.
- I said stay there!
- Please.
- I'm warning you.
- Please. Just for a moment.
Mom!
I just wanted to see my son.
I don't even know
what she fed you.
They eat crickets.
Lots of crickets.
You.
Hope you don't mind,
I let myself in.
Have you come to kill me now?
That depends.
I'd like to talk
to you about Eden.
- She worked for me.
- Don't you mean Sarah Ellis?
She gave up that name and
that life a long time ago.
And she was a good person.
Yes, of course, all spies are very
good people. Just misunderstood.
She cared about you more
than she should've.
She was... special.
She had an ability?
What was it?
Suffice it to say,
she learned how to use it wisely.
Not everyone who has these
abilities deserves them.
And who are you to judge?
In fact, who are you, period?
I made a mistake.
And I should've come to
you a long time ago.
You've been spying
on me for weeks.
In India, my cab,
bugging my phone.
We need to help each other,
Dr. Suresh.
And why would I help you?
You need me, don't you?
My father,
he knew more than you do.
From what we could
observe, yes.
Well, if you've been watching,
then you know my father's
formula doesn't work.
We both know that he
generated a list.
Who's on that list is a
matter of grave importance.
You've come for it?
You want to find them?
Why do you seem so worried?
Are you on the list?
You've no doubt realized
things can go terribly wrong
with these abilities. If you work
with me, we can control that.
If and when I do
figure out this list,
the first thing I'm going
to do is warn these people.
About you.
Together, we could actually
make a difference.
Sorry, not interested.
Contact me when you
change your mind.
The access number's
on the back.
Are you back?
Yeah.
I took out that
suitcase this morning.
But I haven't packed it yet.
Um, I know that
we're in trouble.
And I know that a
lot of it is my--
most of it is my fault.
Janice, we need to start being
completely honest with each other,
- come clean about everything.
- Okay.
'Cause there's something
I gotta tell you.
Something has happened to me.
Something that's...
- really hard to explain.
- Just say it.
I can hear people's thoughts.
Meaning what?
I hear their thoughts.
What they're thinking.
It started a few weeks ago.
That's why I've been with
the FBI all this time.
What? What do you mean?
- Like, a psychic or something?
- I don't know. I guess.
- You can't be serious.
- Yeah.
You don't believe me.
Okay, that's all right.
Here, come here. Come here.
Um... All right.
Pick a number between one...
and a million.
- Come on, bring it on.
- Uh...
I took his power, Nathan.
- I can't control it.
- Let me help you, Peter.
You can't.
I'm not leaving you.
No!
Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Ma?
Where is he?
I have no idea. He woke up.
- He woke up?
- Yes. He was raving.
After two weeks spent
sitting at his bedside,
thinking he could die,
he says he's gotta get away.
- You just let him leave?
- No, I just did not let him leave.
And when I see him,
I will kill him.
Mom... all right, look.
Just go home, okay?
Get some rest.
I'll take care of it.
You're really Hiro Nakamura
-from Isaac's comic book?
Yes, I worked there,
at Yamagato,
and we fly here,
and we drive that car everywhere.
Blue Nissan Versa.
It's parked outside right now.
I'm just like Mr.
Isaac draw me,
except my face not so round.
Okay, yeah. I give up.
The world is insane,
I'm not gonna keep fighting it.
You can paint the future!
And he needs a sword.
This guy Linderman?
He's a client of mine.
Huge collector.
He buys every painting
of Isaac's he can.
I can get you in there.
Get your car,
you're going back to Vegas.
Yeah, I need the first flight
out of New York into the desert.
Uh, I don't know.
Nevada, maybe?
That's where they did all those
nuclear bomb tests, right?
Okay.
Uh, yeah, Las Vegas.
Las Vegas is good. Yeah, whatever.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Hey!
What are you do-- hey!
- You can see me.
- You--
Nobody sees me! Do you hear me?
Nobody sees me! I'm invisible!
In the beginning,
there was discovery.
A confusion of elements,
the first snowfall of
impossible change.
Old lives undone, left behind.
Strange faces made familiar...
new nightmares to
challenge sleep.
New friends to feel safe with.
Only then comes control.
The need to impose
order onto chaos,
through determination,
through study, through struggle...
She's gonna be okay.
You know that, right?
You'd tell me the truth, right?
All in defiance of
a thundering truth.
They're here.
And the earth shudders underfoot.
Oh, God...
Lights out.
Please help me.
Who needs God when
you've got me?
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net